<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 01:55:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 01:55:07 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[日本警告避免日元过度波动，并再次进行口头干预]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本财务大臣铃木俊一周五表示，过度的汇率波动是不可取的，并重申政府决心采取适当行动防止日元大幅下跌。【原文：Japanese Finance Minister Shunichi Suzuki said on Friday excessive exchange-rate moves were undesirable, reiterating the government's resolve to take appropriate actions against sharp yen falls.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/japan-warns-against-excessive-yen-moves-repeats-verbal-intervention-2024-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7IAMEHC6UZLCDNUWK6QFKOBOFE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 01:25:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受地缘政治紧张局势和供应担忧影响，油价将迎来第二周上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[受欧洲和中东地缘政治紧张局势、对供应收紧的担忧以及对经济改善带来的全球燃料需求增长的乐观情绪的支撑，周五油价扩大涨幅，并实现了第二次单周上涨。【原文：Oil prices extended gains on Friday and headed for a second weekly gain, supported by geopolitical tensions in Europe and the Middle East, concerns over tightening supply, and optimism about global fuel demand growth as economies improve.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/oil-prices-bound-second-weekly-gain-geopolitical-tension-supply-concerns-2024-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y4S3CS7MIBMEVPA2EPHLMVOBWU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 01:16:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[就业数据公布前美元持稳；日元创两周新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，美元兑其他货币在从两周低点反弹后持稳，交易员为当天晚些时候将发布的一份关键就业报告做准备，并对中东紧张局势持谨慎态度。【原文：The U.S. dollar held steady against peer currencies on Friday after rebounding from a two-week low, as traders braced for a key jobs report due later in the day and grew cautious over tensions in the Middle East.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-steady-ahead-jobs-data-yen-hits-two-week-high-2024-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FZDAE7C3UJLCLI4AJ6RSFY37TQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 01:13:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[耶伦就中国生产过剩威胁召开有争议的会议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部长珍妮特-耶伦（Janet Yellen）周五将与中国高级官员展开为期四天的会谈，预计会谈将重点讨论中国制造业产能过剩的外溢效应以及美国企业面临的日益严峻的商业环境。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen on Friday kicks off four days of talks with senior Chinese officials expected to focus heavily on spillovers from China's excess manufacturing capacity and an increasingly challenging business climate for U.S. firms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/yellen-launches-contentious-meetings-chinese-excess-production-threat-2024-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RC5RG7SHCRP4TARMEDXY2EPIEE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 01:01:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国在与中国的会晤中提出商业和市场准入问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部表示，美国官员周四在与中国官员的会晤中提出了影响美国公司的商业和市场准入问题，讨论的议题包括跨境数据流动和监管透明度。【原文：U.S. officials on Thursday raised commercial and market access issues impacting American companies in a meeting with Chinese officials on Thursday, the U.S. Commerce Department said, with cross-border data flows and regulatory transparency among topics discussed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us-raises-commercial-market-access-issues-with-china-meeting-2024-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">57TDUWBMOVLMPDD4EBXX2DB6DY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 00:21:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[芯片价格回升，三星第一季度利润增长 10 倍]]></title><description><![CDATA[三星电子周五预计其第一季度营业利润将增长 10 倍以上，原因是半导体价格的反弹使其盈利从一年前芯片需求严重下滑时的低点回升。【原文：Samsung Electronics estimated on Friday a more than 10-fold rise in its first-quarter operating profit, as rebounding semiconductor prices lifted earnings from a low base a year ago when there was a severe downturn in chip demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/samsung-flags-931-rise-first-quarter-profit-chip-prices-recover-2024-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LXXTROGOWZNFDGDTCTTTJX733I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 23:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meta 回击美国联邦贸易委员会修改 2020 年隐私协议的要求]]></title><description><![CDATA[Meta Platforms 拒绝了美国联邦贸易委员会修改 2020 年隐私和解协议的企图，并指出该公司已主动向该机构披露了与 Messenger Kids 应用程序有关的两个技术错误。【原文：Meta Platforms has rebuffed an attempt by the U.S. Federal Trade Commission to amend a 2020 privacy settlement, noting that it had voluntarily disclosed two technical errors related to its Messenger Kids app to the agency.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/meta-pushes-back-us-ftcs-bid-amend-2020-privacy-settlement-2024-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M2XB2S2WGFOZPP7Z64HETSUODQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 23:09:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Humira生物仿制药销售滞后，勃林格将裁减销售人员]]></title><description><![CDATA[勃林格殷格翰公司（Boehringer Ingelheim）周四表示，由于艾伯维（AbbVie）的关节炎治疗大片 Humira 的生物仿制药在美国销售不佳，该公司将裁减部分销售人员。【原文：Boehringer Ingelheim on Thursday said it will lay off some of its salesforce due to poor U.S. sales of its biosimilar version of AbbVie’s blockbuster arthritis treatment Humira.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/boehringer-lay-off-salespeople-humira-biosimilar-sales-lag-2024-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">72IHDIXWOBOJ5IQBF65OSCDKRM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 22:52:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贝莱德称首席执行官劳伦斯-芬克 2023 年薪酬将减少 18]]></title><description><![CDATA[据贝莱德公司周四提交的监管文件显示，该公司首席执行官劳伦斯-芬克 2023 年的薪酬总额为 2690 万美元，低于去年同期的 3270 万美元。【原文：BlackRock CEO Laurence Fink's total pay for 2023 was $26.9 million, down from $32.7 million a year earlier, according to the company's regulatory filings on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/blackrock-says-ceo-laurence-finks-pay-reduced-18-2023-2024-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZSVWMNVFZBNATHQQX4Z7D5BCEI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 22:49:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[J&J 建议股东拒绝 TRC Capital Investment 的 "迷你投标 "要约]]></title><description><![CDATA[强生公司（Johnson &amp; Johnson）周四表示，建议其股东拒绝 TRC Capital Investment Corporation 主动提出的收购其约 0.04% 普通股的 "迷你要约"。【原文：Johnson &amp; Johnson said on Thursday it has recommended its shareholders to reject an unsolicited "mini-tender" offer by TRC Capital Investment Corporation for about 0.04% of its common stock.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/jj-recommends-shareholders-reject-mini-tender-offer-by-trc-capital-investment-2024-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DFE4OTCGDRLKHGN3GBM76PTNY4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 21:59:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标：美联储言论刺伤情绪，印度提供利率指导]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲市场前瞻【原文：A look at the day ahead in Asian markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-markets-view-asia-graphic-pix-2024-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5NK5T3G6VJO75CSSIKDNSWWTTE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 21:49:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道美联储主席巴金降息的信心需要通胀的广度收窄]]></title><description><![CDATA[里士满联储主席托马斯-巴尔金表示，他正密切关注商品和服务业通胀的持续广泛性，并认为价格上涨放缓需要更加普遍，然后他才能放心地降息。【原文：Richmond Federal Reserve President Thomas Barkin said he is focused intently on the persistent breadth of inflation across goods and services, and feels slower price increases need to be more widespread before he is comfortable cutting interest rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-barkin-confidence-cut-rates-requires-breadth-inflation-narrow-2024-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZIUAZVV63FMPJFMNMAL3XEHZHQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 21:39:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cboe Global Markets 寻求美国证券交易委员会批准上市 ETF 股份类别结构]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国证券交易所（Cboe Global Markets）周四表示，已向美国证券交易委员会（SEC）提出申请，要求监管部门批准其修改规则，允许发行人在现有共同基金中增加交易所交易基金（ETF）份额类别。【原文：Cboe Global Markets filed a request with the SEC for regulatory approval to change its rules and allow issuers to add an exchange-traded fund (ETF) share class to existing mutual funds, the exchange said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/cboe-global-markets-seeks-sec-approval-list-etf-share-class-structure-2024-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FSWZ3UT7HJKWBODIV7LDHVWAL4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 21:36:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约州法官宣布纽约州大麻法规无效]]></title><description><![CDATA[在一起质疑大麻广告规则的案件中，纽约州一名法官宣布该州大部分大麻法规无效。【原文：A New York state judge has invalidated most of the state’s cannabis regulations in a case that challenged marijuana advertising rules.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/new-york-cannabis-regulations-invalidated-by-state-judge-2024-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HW46XLSWW5KE7AHPJFYQWIY23Q</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 21:23:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国希望航空公司提高军人的旅行福利]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国运输部长皮特-巴蒂吉格（Pete Buttigieg）周四敦促美国最大的客运航空公司改善现役军人及其家属的旅行福利。【原文：U.S. Transportation Secretary Pete Buttigieg on Thursday urged the nation's largest passenger airlines to improve travel benefits for active-duty military personnel and their families.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-wants-airlines-boost-travel-benefits-military-personnel-2024-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DB62GADKYBNSLGHPUCSWQXZJ6A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 20:19:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道美国司法部将会见波音空难受害者律师]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社通讯报道，美国司法部下周将与2018年和2019年造成346人死亡的两起波音737 MAX致命空难的受害者家属的律师会面，政府将决定是否继续推进刑事案件。【原文：The U.S. Justice Department next week will meet with lawyers for families of victims of two fatal Boeing 737 MAX crashes that killed 346 people in 2018 and 2019, as the government decides whether to move ahead with a criminal case, according to correspondence Reuters reviewed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-justice-department-meet-boeing-fatal-crash-victims-lawyers-2024-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PZJQ4TUHCJKZPOPBV2YEQ3B7ZA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 19:55:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储古尔斯比称房价压力构成最大通胀风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[芝加哥联储主席奥斯汀-古尔斯比（Austan Goolsbee）周四表示，美国中央银行努力将通胀率恢复到 2% 目标值的最大障碍是住房服务业的价格涨幅持续过大。【原文：The largest impediment to the U.S. central bank's efforts to return inflation to its 2% target rate is the persistence of outsized price increases in the housing services sector, Chicago Federal Reserve President Austan Goolsbee said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-goolsbee-says-housing-price-pressures-pose-biggest-inflation-risk-2024-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XSJEAKTGS5IMXGSTIKVFSYADRU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 19:09:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储卡什卡利称，如果通胀继续停滞不前，2024 年降息将面临威胁]]></title><description><![CDATA[明尼阿波利斯联邦储备银行行长尼尔-卡什卡利（Neel Kashkari）周四表示，在上个月的美国央行会议上，他为今年的两次降息埋下了伏笔，但如果通胀继续停滞不前，年底前可能不需要降息。【原文：Minneapolis Federal Reserve Bank President Neel Kashkari said on Thursday that at the U.S. central bank's meeting last month he penciled in two interest rate cuts this year but if inflation continues to stall, none may be required by year end.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-kashkari-says-2024-rate-cuts-under-threat-if-inflation-continues-stall-2024-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7LKIK3KC7RO4LIUC2C2FP5HP44</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 19:04:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国银行称主动型美国基金取得 2007 年以来最佳季度业绩]]></title><description><![CDATA[博雅全球研究公司（BofA Global Research）的策略师表示，第一季度主动管理型美国股票基金取得了自 2007 年以来的最佳季度业绩。【原文：Actively managed U.S. equity funds in the first quarter posted their best quarterly out-performance since 2007, BofA Global Research strategists said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/active-us-funds-tally-best-quarterly-outperformance-since-2007-bofa-says-2024-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2ESOW3MGKBOC5OUPSKHE7EXVGY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 18:46:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国小型企业联合会（NFIB）称，美国小型企业再次缩减招聘计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四公布的一项调查显示，3月份美国小型企业的招聘计划是自2020年5月大流行病停摆导致经济陷入衰退以来最弱的一次，低于一些经济学家视为更广泛就业市场风向标的关键门槛。【原文：Hiring plans among U.S. small businesses in March were the weakest since May 2020 when pandemic shutdowns threw the economy into recession, dropping below a key threshold some economists see as a bellwether for the wider job market, a survey out on Thursday showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-small-businesses-dial-back-hiring-plans-again-nfib-says-2024-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">45AQRTVEGJKNFMS2BZ626UTYUM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 18:37:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛和摩根士丹利必须面对投资者就 Archegos 倒闭提起的诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约州一家上诉法院表示，前 ViacomCBS 投资者可以起诉高盛、摩根士丹利和其他为该媒体公司两次股票发行提供担保的银行，维持了银行担心可能会颠覆资本市场的一项裁决。【原文：A New York state appeals court said former ViacomCBS investors may sue Goldman Sachs , Morgan Stanley and other banks that underwrote two stock offerings for the media company, upholding a ruling that banks fear could upend capital markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/goldman-morgan-stanley-must-face-investors-lawsuit-over-archegos-collapse-2024-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">35Z3U23LAVOS7CE62XR7I7DE2M</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:54:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国针对华为的刑事案件将于 2026 年开审]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部指控中国华为公司在伊朗业务方面误导银行等罪名的刑事案件即将于 2026 年 1 月开庭审理。【原文：The U.S. Justice Department's criminal case accusing China's Huawei of misleading banks about the tech company's business in Iran, among other charges, is heading toward a January 2026 trial.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-criminal-case-against-huawei-heads-toward-2026-trial-2024-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QBWHDOMIXBIEPJSA4MQQBKOV5E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:45:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通重组全球银行业领导层：备忘录]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社周四看到的一份备忘录，摩根大通重组了全球银行部门的领导层。【原文：JPMorgan Chase reorganized its leadership in the global banking division, according to a memo seen by Reuters on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/jpmorgan-reorganizes-leadership-global-banking-memo-2024-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EVV4IROZZVJHLJTPU6R46JKHGA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:16:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普将在与媒体公司联合创始人的纠纷中接受质询]]></title><description><![CDATA[共和党总统候选人唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）定于本月晚些时候接受其社交媒体公司联合创始人律师的质询，这是上周上市的特朗普媒体与科技集团（Trump Media &amp; Technology Group）所有权纠纷的一部分。【原文：Republican presidential candidate Donald Trump is scheduled to be deposed later this month by lawyers for co-founders of his social media company as part of a dispute over ownership in Trump Media &amp; Technology Group , which went public last week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/trump-be-deposed-dispute-with-media-company-co-founders-2024-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NN6ZZJDWB5NXXDZRH3O56WPD7E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:16:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sigma Lithium 首席执行官不会在当前锂价下出售公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[Sigma Lithium 的首席执行官在接受路透社采访时表示，不会在目前的锂价水平上出售这家矿商，而是专注于近期的扩张计划。【原文：Sigma Lithium's chief executive won't sell the miner at current lithium price levels and is concentrating on its near-term expansion plans, she told Reuters in an interview.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/sigma-lithium-ceo-wont-sell-company-current-lithium-prices-2024-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BED3BM23D5MODH3MATA7PPEL4E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:07:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴尔金称，面对 "不那么令人鼓舞 "的数据，美联储有时间考虑降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[里士满联储主席托马斯-巴尔金（Thomas Barkin）周四表示，在开始降息之前，美国央行有 "时间让通胀的乌云散去"。【原文：The U.S. central bank has "time for the clouds to clear" on inflation before starting to cut interest rates, Richmond Fed President Thomas Barkin said on Thursday, comments that endorsed a careful approach to the start of a monetary easing cycle.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/fed-has-time-mull-rate-cut-face-less-encouraging-data-barkin-says-2024-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N5Y3UWCORVLLZJMSKFPYVQCAVI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 16:07:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家消息消息人士称，波音和空客正在探讨分割 Spirit Aero 公司业务的框架]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的人士称，波音和空客正逐步达成一项潜在的协调协议，分拆陷入困境的供应商 Spirit AeroSystems 的业务，接管支持其顶级喷气机项目所需的工厂。【原文：Boeing and Airbus are edging towards a potentially coordinated deal to split operations of troubled supplier Spirit AeroSystems , taking on plants needed to support their top jet programs, people familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/boeing-airbus-exploring-framework-divvy-up-spirit-aeros-operations-sources-say-2024-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GOR35UTKKFK3NL5DS7WLU2TOEM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 16:02:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Glass Lewis 建议投资者投票反对 Spirit Aero 公司的两名董事]]></title><description><![CDATA[代理咨询公司 Glass Lewis 建议 Spirit AeroSystems 股东在 2024 年年会上投票反对选举两名董事，其中包括这家航空零部件供应商风险委员会的负责人罗纳德-卡迪什（Ronald Kadish）。【原文：Proxy advisory firm Glass Lewis has recommended Spirit AeroSystems shareholders vote against the election of two directors, including the head of the aero parts supplier's risk committee, Ronald Kadish, at the 2024 annual meeting.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/glass-lewis-recommends-investors-vote-against-two-spirit-aero-directors-2024-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CR6QUX6MQZMMJKIV42H7UD7PV4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 15:56:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国券商开始红迪覆盖范围，盈利前景存疑]]></title><description><![CDATA[两家美国券商在开始报道 Reddit 时，对该社交媒体平台实现盈利的能力持怀疑态度，并对其可能进入 "meme 股票 "俱乐部表示担忧。【原文：Two U.S. brokerages began coverage of Reddit by taking a skeptical stance on the social media platform's ability to turn profitable and raised concerns over its potential entry into the 'meme stock' club.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-brokerages-start-reddit-coverage-with-doubts-over-turning-profit-2024-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JWDRTRFPEJJZTPKFCGDS6OFQ3Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 15:40:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[家乐福与百事可乐之争揭示零售商广告业务的关键作用]]></title><description><![CDATA[家乐福和百事公司刚刚解决的为期三个月的价格争议，揭示了此类谈判的一个新方面，它正在改变零售商和供应商之间的关系。【原文：Carrefour and PepsiCo's just resolved three-month price dispute has shed light on a new aspect of such negotiations which is changing the relationship between retailers and suppliers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/carrefour-pepsico-dispute-sheds-light-key-role-retailers-ad-business-2024-04-04/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K6Y7IZJCCNLXDNBTCPUPSFTBSE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 15:37:27 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>