<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 18:30:12 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 18:30:12 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉在诉讼中被控拖欠加州工人工资]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉正面临一项新的集体诉讼提案，指控这家电动汽车制造商在加利福尼亚州的工厂和仓库工人违反了一系列工资法，而该公司已经面临工作场所偏见和破坏工会的指控。【原文：Tesla is facing a new proposed class action lawsuit accusing the electric carmaker of a slew of wage law violations against factory and warehouse workers in California, as the company is already facing allegations of workplace bias and union busting.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/tesla-accused-lawsuit-cheating-california-workers-out-wages-2024-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">X5RLW7KY25NYDPML6SGCVC5AB4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 17:41:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：美联储经济数据流图表]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦储备委员会在 3 月 19-20 日的政策会议上将基准隔夜利率稳定在 5.25%-5.50% 的区间内，官员们继续预计将在 2024 年底前批准三次季度性降息。【原文：The U.S. Federal Reserve held its benchmark overnight interest rate steady in the 5.25%-5.50% range at its March 19-20 policy meeting, and officials continued to anticipate approving three quarter-percentage-point rate cuts by the end of 2024.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/charting-feds-economic-data-flow-2024-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SPMYLAGNXZLUNPJD4VEZMECS7U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 17:33:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[就业报告发布后，PIMCO 将 2024 年美联储降息预期下调至 2 次]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国债券巨头 PIMCO 的一位投资组合经理表示，在上周五的数据显示美国经济上个月创造的就业岗位多于预期之后，PIMCO 已将美联储今年降息的预期下调至两次。【原文：U.S. bond giant PIMCO has trimmed its expectations for interest rate cuts by the Federal Reserve this year to two after data on Friday showing the U.S. economy created more jobs than expected last month, said a portfolio manager.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/pimco-trims-2024-fed-rate-cut-expectations-2-after-jobs-report-2024-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4XNXTXXH2RLBRLP5JMIIWXQSNA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 17:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储鲍曼称降息时机未到]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储理事米歇尔-鲍曼（Michelle Bowman）表示，现在还不是美国央行考虑削减利率目标的时候，并指出如果降低通胀的进展停滞不前，可能会有更多的加息。【原文：Federal Reserve Governor Michelle Bowman said it’s not time for the U.S. central bank to consider cutting its interest rate target and noted that more hikes could be on the table if progress on lowering inflation stalls out.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/feds-bowman-says-time-hasnt-arrived-cutting-rates-2024-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XXTV77LSH5PLROUIW3U4OKJMFQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 16:35:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国人追逐罕见天象，日食带动旅游热潮]]></title><description><![CDATA[即将到来的日食对旅游公司来说是个好兆头，因为美国一些位于 "日全食路径 "上的地区出现了空前的住宿需求，这些美国人都迫不及待地想一睹这一天象的风采。【原文：The upcoming solar eclipse is proving to be a good omen for travel firms, as some parts of the United States that fall in the "path of totality" see unprecedented demand for lodging from eager Americans waiting to catch a glimpse of the celestial event.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/eclipse-boosts-travel-americans-chase-rare-celestial-event-2024-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LJRQDGN2FRMM5N5WGIECM7YLRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 16:20:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[VIEW 中国电动汽车竞争激烈，特斯拉取消低成本汽车计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[据三位熟悉内情的消息人士和路透社看到的公司信息称，特斯拉已经取消了长期承诺的廉价汽车，而投资者一直指望这款汽车能推动特斯拉成长为一家大众市场汽车制造商。【原文：Tesla has canceled the long-promised inexpensive car that investors have been counting on to drive its growth into a mass-market automaker, according to three sources familiar with the matter and company messages seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/view-tesla-scraps-low-cost-car-plans-amid-fierce-chinese-ev-competition-2024-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AGPJWL6OKVI4ZD6R35NHORII4U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 16:14:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[五张图表记录特斯拉的坎坷历程]]></title><description><![CDATA[据报道，特斯拉取消了低成本汽车计划，这标志着投资者对该公司的最新失望，他们今年因担心需求放缓、汽车产品老化和中国竞争加剧而抛售了该公司的股票。【原文：Tesla's reported move to scrap plans for a low-cost car marks the latest disappointment for investors who have dumped shares of the automaker this year on worries over slowing demand, an aging vehicle line-up and rising Chinese competition.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/teslas-bumpy-ride-captured-five-charts-2024-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XMLZLARVABMA3JZAMHAZQPLB5M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 15:46:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大众汽车首席执行官告诉报社，大众电动汽车在中国 "跟不上 "市场的步伐]]></title><description><![CDATA[大众汽车公司首席执行官周五告诉德国报纸《FAZ》，大众汽车希望避免为其在中国的市场份额设定 "乌托邦式 "的目标，并补充说，鉴于竞争激烈，超过10%的市场份额是 "非常值得尊敬的"。【原文：Volkswagen wants to avoid setting "utopian" goals for its market share in China, its CEO told German newspaper FAZ on Friday, adding that anything above 10% was "very respectable" given the intense competition.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/volkswagen-evs-cant-keep-up-china-ceo-tells-newspaper-2024-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TCOVMBJQPVLIREUA35JKHL5SHA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 15:37:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道中国电动汽车竞争激烈，特斯拉取消低成本汽车计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[独家-特斯拉取消低价汽车计划-消息人士【原文：EXCLUSIVE-TESLA CANCELS LOW-COST CAR PLANS-SOURCES】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-scraps-low-cost-car-plans-amid-fierce-chinese-ev-competition-2024-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">L5WBCF2P5BJ73IA4WEM4PKNKIY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 15:07:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储罗根：现在考虑降息为时尚早]]></title><description><![CDATA[达拉斯联邦储备银行行长洛里-洛根（Lorie Logan）周五表示，当前的通胀形势表明，央行不会马上推动更宽松的货币政策。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of Dallas President Lorie Logan said on Friday that the current inflation landscape argues against any imminent push toward easier monetary policy by the central bank.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-logan-too-soon-start-thinking-about-rate-cuts-2024-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MIUPJXZ76FMMHHMFF23OTGQ3OA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 15:03:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[宝洁公司因安全问题在美国召回820万个问题洗衣袋]]></title><description><![CDATA[汰渍生产商宝洁公司周五表示，由于包装缺陷可能对儿童造成伤害，该公司将在美国召回820万袋有缺陷的部分洗衣粉豆荚。【原文：Procter &amp; Gamble is recalling 8.2 million defective bags of some of its laundry detergent pods in the U.S. due to a packaging flaw that could pose a risk of injury to children, the Tide maker said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/pg-recalls-82-mln-defective-laundry-pod-bags-us-amid-safety-concerns-2024-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ST33W6SUJFJC7FXLA5WTZOUWDY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 15:00:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟从新的强迫劳动法中看到美国矿产交易的希望]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧盟贸易主管瓦尔蒂斯-东布罗夫斯基斯（Valdis Dombrovskis）周五表示，欧盟将禁止使用强迫劳动制造产品的新规定提高了与美国就关键矿产品达成协议的前景。【原文：New European Union rules that will ban products made using forced labour have raised the prospect of concluding a deal on critical minerals with the United States, EU trade chief Valdis Dombrovskis said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/eu-sees-hope-us-minerals-deal-new-forced-labour-law-2024-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B7O7FZX26NKONNMPYRVN6OTGFM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 15:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席巴金"这是一份相当强劲的就业报告"]]></title><description><![CDATA[里士满联邦储备银行行长托马斯-巴尔金（Thomas Barkin）周五表示，3 月份就业人数的意外激增和失业率的下降使这份就业报告 "相当强劲"。【原文：Richmond Federal Reserve Bank President Thomas Barkin on Friday said the unexpected surge in employment in March and drop in the unemployment rate made for a "quite strong jobs report."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/feds-barkin-thats-quite-strong-jobs-report-2024-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZEUQBYPTYVLALBWG45OVBK6BLU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 14:36:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在新关税实施前，巴西进口的中国电动汽车数量激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[2024 年第一季度，在旨在保护本地生产的进口关税上升之前，来自中国的大量电动汽车推动了巴西的汽车进口。【原文：A flood of electric vehicles from China boosted Brazilian car imports in the first quarter of 2024, ahead of rising import tariffs aimed at protecting local production.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/brazil-imports-chinese-electric-vehicles-surge-ahead-new-tariff-2024-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AHQCRXCC2FOF5DIJDRTKJ6M5Z4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 14:32:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[UAW 称阿拉巴马州梅赛德斯奔驰工厂工人申请参加工会选举]]></title><description><![CDATA[位于阿拉巴马州万斯的梅赛德斯奔驰工厂的工人向美国监管机构提交了一份请愿书，要求举行选举以加入美国汽车工人工会（United Auto Workers）。【原文：Workers at a Mercedes Benz factory in Vance, Alabama, filed a petition with U.S. regulators to hold an election to join the United Auto Workers, the union said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/alabama-mercedes-benz-plant-workers-file-union-election-uaw-says-2024-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WHJVTTQTWFJWTAD6HV4DUEOTO4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 14:06:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[元全面修订关于深度伪造和其他篡改媒体的规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国大选之前，Facebook 的所有者 Meta 周五宣布对其有关数字创建和篡改媒体的政策进行重大调整，这将考验其对新人工智能技术产生的欺骗性内容进行监管的能力。【原文：Facebook owner Meta announced major changes to its policies on digitally created and altered media on Friday, ahead of U.S. elections poised to test its ability to police deceptive content generated by new artificial intelligence technologies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/meta-overhauls-rules-deepfakes-other-altered-media-2024-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G7ZRCU46CBJGFC5VG4WT4ME3BE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 14:02:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[安联以 14 亿美元出售美国保险部门]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国保险公司安联（Allianz）周五表示，同意以 14 亿美元的价格将其面向中型企业和娱乐业客户的美国保险部门 Fireman's Fund 出售给 Arch Insurance。【原文：Allianz agreed to sell Fireman's Fund, its U.S. insurance unit for mid-sized corporations and entertainment industry clients, to Arch Insurance for $1.4 billion, the German insurer said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/allianz-sells-us-insurance-unit-14-billion-2024-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6SLXMEODWRIRHNSPQKROLTJFZQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 13:57:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 3 月就业人数好于预期；工资稳步增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国雇主在 3 月份雇佣的工人数量远超预期，同时还提高了工资，这表明第一季度的经济基础稳固，并有可能推迟美联储今年的降息预期。【原文：U.S. employers hired far more workers than expected March while raising wages, suggesting the economy ended the first quarter on solid ground and potentially delaying anticipated interest rate cuts from the Federal Reserve this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/view-march-us-payrolls-beat-expectations-wages-increase-steadily-2024-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z44AFKOREZNLBC3GP7W4AQJQHU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 12:55:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[降息时机不明朗，全球股票基金资金外流]]></title><description><![CDATA[在截至4月3日的一周里，投资者减持了全球股票基金，因为他们权衡了在美国经济报告强劲、劳动力需求稳健的情况下，美联储降息次数可能少于预期的可能性。【原文：Investors trimmed their holdings in global equity funds in the week ending April 3 as they weighed the possibility of the Federal Reserve delivering fewer interest rate cuts than expected, amid strong U.S. economic reports and solid labor demand.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-flows-graphic-pix-2024-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OUCW3Y22VFJVDIUFCPQEJC6S2A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 12:52:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[WiWo 报道称，美国商人是竞购破产德国连锁商场的买家之一]]></title><description><![CDATA[据商业媒体 WirtschaftsWoche 周五报道，美国商人理查德-贝克（Richard Baker）的投资公司（NRDC）是德国最著名的连锁百货公司 Galeria Karstadt Kaufhof 的两个剩余竞标者之一。【原文：The investment firm of US businessman Richard Baker (NRDC) is among the two remaining bidders for Germany's most prominent department store chain Galeria Karstadt Kaufhof, business outlet WirtschaftsWoche reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/us-businessman-among-bidders-bankrupt-german-mall-chain-wiwo-reports-2024-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OO5E3JBNZZP75MVO7M6JNUTQKE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 12:50:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[壳牌与阿美石油公司展馆能源谈判进入最后阶段--消息人士]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位知情人士称，壳牌和沙特阿美正在竞相收购淡马锡旗下液化天然气（LNG）贸易公司 Pavilion Energy 的资产，在完成尽职调查程序后，双方目前正在进行价格谈判。【原文：Shell and Saudi Aramco , which are competing to buy the assets of Temasek-owned liquefied natural gas (LNG) trading firm Pavilion Energy, are now locked in price negotiations after completing the due diligence process, three sources with knowledge of the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/shell-aramco-final-stage-pavilion-energy-talks-sources-2024-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VGN7QV3MOFMBRES2CSJKYVSTFE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 12:45:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 3 月份就业增长超出预期；工资稳步增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国雇主在 3 月份雇佣的工人数量远超预期，同时还提高了工资，这表明第一季度的经济基础稳固，并有可能推迟美联储今年的降息预期。【原文：U.S. employers hired far more workers than expected March while raising wages, suggesting the economy ended the first quarter on solid ground and potentially delaying anticipated interest rate cuts from the Federal Reserve this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-job-growth-beats-expectations-march-wages-increase-steadily-2024-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UB5NTFDT6JLE7CWC44NLZLXUDU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 12:43:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国和欧盟在新的半导体协议中盯上了中国的传统芯片]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国和欧盟承诺将合作期限延长三年，以查明半导体行业的干扰因素，并特别强调来自中国的主流 "传统 "芯片。【原文：The United States and the European Union committed to extend by three years their cooperation on identifying disruptions in the semiconductor sector, with a particular emphasis on mainstream "legacy" chips from China.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-eu-eye-chinese-legacy-chips-renewed-semiconductor-accord-2024-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P25JN3DBTJOPPBKRFZ3B3HKHWU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 11:40:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[商业团体投诉后，印尼审查进口规则]]></title><description><![CDATA[印尼贸易部一位高级官员周五表示，印尼正在评估旨在抑制3000多种产品进口的法规，因为业界担心这些法规可能会扰乱国内供应链并影响出口。【原文：Indonesia is evaluating regulations designed to curb imports of more than 3,000 products, a senior trade ministry official said on Friday, following industry concerns the rules could disrupt the domestic supply chain and disrupt exports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/indonesia-reviews-import-rules-after-business-group-complaints-2024-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YXSOELTHP5JMBIBEC5APRA2ZMU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 11:17:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[数据显示，英国金融业女性的收入比男性同事少三分之一]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社查阅的 21 家公司的薪酬数据显示，英国一些顶级金融公司支付给女性的薪酬平均比男性少 28.8%，尽管这些公司表示正在努力聘用更多女性担任高薪、高级职位。【原文：Some of Britain's top financial firms pay women 28.8% less on average than male counterparts, salary data from 21 companies reviewed by Reuters shows, even though they say they are striving to hire more females for higher-paid, senior roles.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/women-uk-finance-earn-third-less-than-male-colleagues-data-shows-2024-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">INI2XBF6HJMGLPWGIWV55USKFQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 11:16:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管闪电般上涨，黄金多头仍期待再创新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周，瑞士黄金精炼厂 MKS PAMP 金属战略主管尼基-希尔斯（Nicky Shiels）对 2024 年金价预测的上调引来了市场参与者意想不到的追问。这个问题是"黄金是否会'变可可'？【原文：An upgraded gold price forecast for 2024 from Nicky Shiels, head of metals strategy at Swiss gold refinery MKS PAMP, drew an unexpected follow-up question this week from market participants. The enquiry was: "Will or can gold 'go cocoa'?"】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/gold-bulls-eye-more-record-highs-despite-lightning-gains-2024-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WVBOJ7ACCBOWZLO2Y3S64GGU34</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 11:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[一次险些失手的网络攻击为何让美国官员和科技行业人心惶惶？]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国软件开发人员安德烈斯-弗罗因德（Andres Freund）上个月在进行一些详细的性能测试时，发现一个鲜为人知的程序出现了奇怪的行为。他在调查中发现的情况令整个软件世界为之震惊，并引起了技术主管和政府官员的关注。【原文：German software developer Andres Freund was running some detailed performance tests last month when he noticed odd behavior in a little known program. What he found when he investigated has sent shudders across the software world and drawn attention from tech executives and government officials.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/why-near-miss-cyberattack-put-us-officials-tech-industry-edge-2024-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5IWB4YFMMBOAVI6PVANOQCHKVM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 11:02:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[意大利顶级银行股价对账面价值的折让收窄]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利银行的股价已飙升至多年来的高点，因为利率上升使利润激增，贷款成本上升，而存款利率却远远落后。【原文：Italian banks have seen their share prices soar to multi-year highs as rising interest rates turbocharge profits, driving up lending costs while deposit rates lag far behind.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/italys-top-banks-narrow-share-price-discount-book-value-2024-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4CD3C2LI3JKNPAIAZ2G3M4TKZI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 10:44:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿玛尼集团公司因劳工剥削调查被接管]]></title><description><![CDATA[意大利一家法院周五对意大利时装集团阿玛尼旗下的一家公司实施司法管理，原因是该公司间接将生产分包给剥削工人的中国公司。【原文：An Italian court on Friday placed under judicial administration a company owned by Italian fashion group Armani for indirectly subcontracting its production to Chinese companies that exploited workers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/armani-group-company-receivership-over-labour-exploitation-probe-2024-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PQQY37VS5NP7PBTYFJ4E4CUBAA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 10:40:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[强生公司将以 125 亿美元收购冲击波医疗公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[强生公司（Johnson &amp; Johnson）周五同意以 125 亿美元的价格收购冲击波医疗公司（Shockwave Medical），这笔交易将有助于扩大其用于治疗心脏病的医疗设备产品组合。【原文：Johnson &amp; Johnson on Friday agreed to buy Shockwave Medical for $12.5 billion, in a deal that would help broaden its portfolio of medical devices used in treating heart diseases.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/johnson-johnson-buy-shockwave-medical-125-bln-deal-2024-04-05/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RLC5KSFE7NN67CPMMVZBXN5554</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 10:39:15 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>