<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 18:42:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 18:42:52 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊就法国监管机构有关员工监控的 3460 万美元罚款提出上诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[电子商务巨头亚马逊公司（Amazon.com）周五表示，已就法国监管机构 CNIL 对该公司处以 3200 万欧元（约合 3458 万美元）罚款的决定提出上诉。【原文：E-commerce giant Amazon.com said on Friday it has appealed French regulator CNIL's decision to fine the company 32 million euros ($34.58 million) for setting up a system to monitor employee activity and performance.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/amazon-appeals-346-mln-fine-by-french-regulator-over-staff-monitoring-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AFY36DJQJ5PM3HTSU56ZLF7MSE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 18:34:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员美国对苹果公司的诉讼可能会让 iPhone 的使用体验更贴近消费者]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国已对苹果公司提起诉讼，目的是加强 iPhone 的竞争，并为那些其应用程序可与无处不在的设备配合使用的小公司提供有利条件。【原文：The U.S. has filed a lawsuit against Apple with the aim of increasing competition for the iPhone and giving a leg up to smaller companies whose apps work with the ubiquitous device.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-lawsuit-against-apple-could-make-iphone-experience-more-consumer-friendly-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3ZHG2PEKJBNSNAGEYUNUBNWUDY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 18:01:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ASML 供应商 Neways 将在马来西亚新建工厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[荷兰计算机芯片设备制造商 ASML 的主要供应商 Neways 周五表示，它将在马来西亚巴生新建一座工厂。【原文：Neways, a key supplier to Dutch computer chip equipment maker ASML , said on Friday it will build a new plant in Klang, Malaysia.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/asml-supplier-neways-build-new-plant-malaysia-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EV7V4JL4KJIKFIH7LQLY2GJ22M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 17:55:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[绿街公司称，美国办公室占用率面临远程办公的 "黑洞]]></title><description><![CDATA[房地产分析公司 Green Street 表示，远程办公已造成美国办公室占用率的 "黑洞"，使需求大大低于大流行前的水平，空置率降至历史最低点，多年内都不可能恢复到以前的使用率。【原文：Remote work has caused a "black hole" in U.S. office occupancy, knocking demand significantly below pre-pandemic levels and vacancy rates to historic lows, with a recovery to prior usage unlikely for years, said real estate analysis firm Green Street.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-office-occupancy-faces-black-hole-remote-work-says-green-street-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NTNE6PCR3RJTDGPEZ65BW44Y6I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 16:59:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报纸称加拿大监管机构将为高负债借款人设定抵押贷款上限]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《环球邮报》周五报道，加拿大银行业监管机构正在限制银行住宅抵押贷款组合中高杠杆贷款的数量，这些贷款随着房价的上涨而膨胀，使加拿大借款人成为世界上负债最多的国家之一。【原文：Canada's banking regulator is limiting the number of highly leveraged loans in banks' residential mortgage portfolios, which have ballooned alongside house prices to make Canadian borrowers among the most indebted in the world, the Globe and Mail reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/canada-banking-regulator-cap-mortgages-highly-indebted-borrowers-newspaper-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HB6A6G6YHZLSJNFHVDYSWU7FMM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 16:36:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管欧盟采取了安全行动，马士基仍将避开红海]]></title><description><![CDATA[航运公司马士基周五表示，尽管欧盟倡议加强红海地区的安全，但由于风险水平持续升高，恢复红海航线为时尚早。【原文：Shipping company Maersk said on Friday it was too early to resume sailings through the Red Sea due to a continued elevated risk level, despite an initiative by the European Union to increase safety in the region.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/maersk-will-avoid-red-sea-despite-eu-security-operation-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4JT3HT5UABO3LA6HUNCVWDU73Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 16:29:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[克莱斯勒母公司 Stellantis 在美国裁员约 400 人]]></title><description><![CDATA[克莱斯勒母公司斯特兰蒂斯公司周五表示，在努力削减成本、提高效率和加强电动汽车生产计划的同时，该公司将裁减约 400 名美国工人。【原文：Chrysler-parent Stellantis said Friday it will lay off about 400 U.S. workers as it works to cut costs, boost efficiency and ramp up electric vehicle production plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chrysler-parent-stellantis-laying-off-about-400-us-workers-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5YXYEJGIGVMHFITNSORSAMWPBQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 16:20:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国称盖茨支持的反应堆公司的计划申请需要改进]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国监管机构本周告诉一家由比尔-盖茨创立的核电公司，该公司计划为一座高科技反应堆申请施工许可，但还需要做更多的工作。【原文：U.S. regulators this week told a nuclear power company founded by Bill Gates that its planned construction permit application for a high-tech reactor needs more work, an issue that a critic of the technology said could delay development of the plant in Wyoming.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-says-gates-backed-reactor-companys-planned-application-needs-work-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YHGUISSXBROFVK2OWBBA7UIFWU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 16:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[银行家称欧洲首次公开募股（IPO）市场受挫，但仍在复苏过程中]]></title><description><![CDATA[银行家们说，在德国零售商道格拉斯（Douglas）上市后一天，瑞士护肤品公司 Galderma 周五的强势上市稳定了欧洲 IPO 市场的神经。【原文：A strong debut by Swiss skincare company Galderma on Friday is steadying nerves around Europe's IPO market, a day after a poorly received listing from German retailer Douglas , bankers said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/europes-ipo-market-hits-bump-recovery-still-course-bankers-say-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QUDB6QFGJNJU7BVQ2TYG4JJEQ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 14:40:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[利润创纪录后，Zara 商店工人在西班牙商店外举行抗议活动]]></title><description><![CDATA[时尚巨头 Inditex 旗下 Zara、Bershka 和其他服装店的工人周五在西班牙各地的店外举行抗议活动，要求改善条件，此前该集团公布了创纪录的利润并提高了股东报酬。【原文：Workers from Zara, Bershka and other clothing stores owned by fashion giant Inditex protested outside their shops across Spain on Friday to demand better conditions after the group reported record profits and raised shareholder payouts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/zara-shop-workers-protest-outside-spanish-stores-after-record-profit-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M4FSVBCY2FP6RL4RSKT63L233Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 14:35:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者为特朗普价值 60 亿美元的社交媒体交易开绿灯]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，在一家空头支票收购公司的投资者批准了一项目前价值约 60 亿美元的合作后，美国前总统唐纳德-特朗普距离从其社交媒体公司获得巨额暴利又近了一步。【原文：Former U.S. President Donald Trump came a step closer on Friday to reaping a major windfall from his social media firm after investors in a blank-check acquisition company approved a tie-up currently worth about $6 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/investors-greenlight-trumps-6-billion-social-media-deal-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SPZ64RWH6FO63JCFRFJXZ2WEAA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 14:23:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国股票基金创九个月来最大单周流入量]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至 3 月 20 日的七天内，受华尔街持续反弹和美联储今年晚些时候降息预期的推动，美国股票基金需求强劲。【原文：U.S. equity funds witnessed robust demand in the seven days to March 20, buoyed by Wall Street's continued rally and expectations of Federal Reserve rate cuts later this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-equity-funds-draw-biggest-weekly-inflow-nine-months-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LFRZTOZU3FI7BP2RIYG7B4RYDE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 14:00:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席鲍威尔称大流行病对经济产生了持久影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储主席杰罗姆-鲍威尔（Jerome Powell）周五在 "美联储倾听"（Fed Listens）活动开幕式上就美国人对经济的感受发表讲话，称大流行病已经产生了 "持久的 "影响，美国央行要制定良好的政策，就不能仅仅依赖宏观经济数据，而是需要直接听取民众和企业的意见。【原文：Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell on Friday opened a "Fed Listens" event on how Americans are experiencing the economy, saying the pandemic has had "lasting" effects and that to make good policy the U.S. central bank cannot rely only on macroeconomic data but needs to hear directly from people and businesses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/fed-chair-powell-says-pandemic-has-had-lasting-effects-economy-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">37IZGPK5R5OHXPPBNBDOC6AEYU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 13:17:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[加拿大 1 月份零售额下降，但 2 月份略有回升]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的数据显示，由于商品价格下降以及汽车和零部件销售减少，加拿大一月份的零售额萎缩幅度略低于预期。【原文：Canada's retail sales contracted a little less than expected in January as lower goods prices and lower sales of motor vehicle and parts weighed down on the number, data showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/canadas-january-retail-sales-decline-slight-rebound-seen-february-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5RJRPIKISJJVFHJWE2P6LPZ3MA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 12:50:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国数据和美联储降息预期令全球股票基金大量流入]]></title><description><![CDATA[受中国强劲的工业和零售数据以及对美国联邦储备委员会今年晚些时候降息预期的乐观情绪推动，全球股票基金在截至3月20日的一周内吸引了大量资金流入。【原文：Global equity funds attracted substantial inflows in the week to March 20, driven by strong industrial and retail data from China and optimism about anticipated rate cuts by the U.S. Federal Reserve later in the year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-flows-graphic-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4VKEEBGYVFNIDIT4THNSSHYJ2Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 12:41:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，苹果公司与中国百度就其设备的人工智能问题举行了会谈]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周五报道，苹果公司已与百度 9888.HK 就在中国市场的设备中使用该公司的人工智能生成技术举行了初步会谈。【原文：Apple has held preliminary talks with Baidu 9888.HK about using the Chinese company's generative artificial-intelligence technology in its devices in China, the Wall Street Journal reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-held-talks-with-chinas-baidu-over-ai-use-its-devices-wsj-reports-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XCVD62QLPRJYTL6JB4SXIMIJHI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 12:30:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道中国 Leapmotor 公司将在波兰 Stellantis 工厂开始生产小型电动汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位知情人士周五告诉路透社，中国的 Leapmotor 公司将开始在波兰的 Stellantis 工厂生产小型电动汽车，这是两家汽车制造商合资企业的一部分。【原文：China's Leapmotor will start producing small electric cars at a Stellantis plant in Poland as part of a joint venture between the two carmakers, two people close to the matter told Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chinas-leapmotor-start-production-small-ev-polish-stellantis-plant-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OMKBH5H3RNJNTEHCPY7XFVA4SQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 12:03:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛称，美国公司通过回购和并购购买股票的数量将在 2024 年创下 6 年新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛集团（Goldman Sachs）表示，美国公司通过增加股票回购和企业收购来购买国内股票的规模今年将达到 6,250 亿美元，创下六年来的新高，与共同基金和养老金机构的卸载规模相当。【原文：U.S. companies' purchases of domestic equities through more stock buybacks and corporate acquisitions will hit a six-year high of $625 billion this year, about as much as mutual funds and pension houses will offload, Goldman Sachs said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/us-companies-stock-purchases-via-buybacks-ma-hit-6-year-high-2024-goldman-says-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z5C6USUGQJNXPOVKT4HBXFOQFQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 11:53:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[耐克股价下滑，因转向新款式挤压收入]]></title><description><![CDATA[耐克公司股价周五收盘前下跌超过 6%，原因是这家 Air Jordan 制造商预测上半年销售额将下降，因为它在与新品牌争夺市场份额的过程中，用更时尚的运动鞋取代了旧款式的运动鞋。【原文：Nike shares fell more than 6% before the bell on Friday after the Air Jordan maker forecast a drop in sales in its first half as it replaces older styles with trendier sneakers in its fight for market share with newer brands.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/nike-shares-skid-switch-newer-styles-squeeze-revenue-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7EJHKF3LVNJB5FBPLSOBWCZTFE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 11:35:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[多伦多证券交易所期货在国内经济数据公布前上涨；股市有望实现周涨幅]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，加拿大主要股指期货走高，股市在上一交易日创下历史新高后继续上涨，投资者正在等待更多的经济数据来判断加拿大经济的健康状况。【原文：Futures for Canada's main stock index advanced on Friday, with stocks continuing to rise after notching record highs in the previous session, while investors await for more economic data to gauge the health of the Canadian economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/tsx-futures-rise-ahead-domestic-economic-data-stocks-eye-weekly-gain-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GPHYCLYXSVIRDACSGY53VAM4LI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 10:53:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[蒙特利尔银行和凯雷在加拿大推出私募股权投资战略]]></title><description><![CDATA[蒙特利尔银行全球资产管理公司（BMO Global Asset Management）周五表示，该公司已与美国私募股权公司凯雷集团（Carlyle Group）合作，扩大加拿大投资者进入私募市场的机会。【原文：BMO Global Asset Management said on Friday it had partnered with U.S. private equity firm Carlyle Group to broaden access to private markets for Canadian investors.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/bmo-carlyle-launch-private-equity-strategy-canada-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CCT33Y4GERLG3HXA6QKLVTEULM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 10:11:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[1-2 月流入中国的外资萎缩 19.9]]></title><description><![CDATA[商务部周五公布的数据显示，1-2月流入中国的外资同比减少19.9%，为2,151亿元人民币（300亿美元）。【原文：Foreign investment flows into China shrank 19.9% in January-February from a year earlier to 215.1 billion yuan ($30 billion), data from the commerce ministry showed on Friday, even as the government gears up to woo foreign firms.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/foreign-investment-flows-into-china-shrink-199-jan-feb-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5WSR3AO575NILKBLBBT2LHIKWE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 10:11:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 央行抨击后美元大涨 苹果受挫]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HVQZ5MCBPNMD3KAFRU3KKCQTWM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 10:08:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Reddit 在纽约证交所强势上市后下跌一天]]></title><description><![CDATA[社交媒体平台 Reddit 的股价在周五收盘前下跌了 2.6%，而在此之前的一天，它在纽约证券交易所的首次亮相就取得了 48% 的涨幅。【原文：Social media platform Reddit's shares ticked down 2.6% before the bell on Friday, a day after it notched a 48% gain in its debut on the New York Stock Exchange.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/reddit-dips-day-after-strong-nyse-debut-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GPNNTS6HD5N3NHIMRRTALNS3SE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 10:05:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果反垄断诉讼照搬击败微软的策略，但科技行业已发生变化]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国政府对苹果公司的反垄断诉讼借鉴了 1998 年的分水岭案件，该案打破了微软对台式机软件的垄断，但事实可能证明，该案并不是解决智能手机竞争问题的完美蓝图。【原文：The U.S. government's antitrust lawsuit against Apple draws on the watershed 1998 case that broke Microsoft's stranglehold on desktop software, but that may prove to be an imperfect blueprint for addressing smartphone competition.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/apple-antitrust-suit-mirrors-strategy-that-beat-microsoft-tech-industry-has-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QCPWWKE5AZN5HP6TCRJEHBKLD4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 10:03:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博社报道：电动汽车销量增长放缓，特斯拉削减在华汽车产量]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五报道，随着美国电动汽车制造商努力应对缓慢的需求和激烈的市场竞争，特斯拉已经减少了其在中国工厂的汽车产量。【原文：Tesla has reduced its car production at its plant in China, Bloomberg News reported on Friday, as the U.S. electric vehicle-maker grapples with slow demand and strong competition in the market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-trims-output-cars-china-amid-slower-ev-sales-growth-bloomberg-reports-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">62GR5Q7WV5JSBBI7KIJGTWY2PM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 09:52:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行在五年战略计划中提出加强研究和分析的必要性]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行周五在由学者出身的行长上田一夫（Kazuo Ueda）于去年 4 月上任后编制的首个中期战略计划中强调了加强研究和分析能力的必要性。【原文：The Bank of Japan on Friday highlighted the need to enhance its research and analytical capabilities in the first medium-term strategic plan compiled under academic-turned governor Kazuo Ueda, who took office in April last year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/boj-lays-out-need-beef-up-research-analysis-5-year-strategic-plan-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5LCVKPHOURKKLHAQPV4VEKHS2I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 09:47:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局称克莱斯勒将因安全气囊气体发生器问题召回约 28.6 万辆美国汽车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（NHTSA）周五表示，克莱斯勒将在美国召回近28.6万辆汽车，原因是存在可能导致侧帘式安全气囊气体发生器破裂的制造缺陷。【原文：Chrysler is recalling nearly 286,000 vehicles in the United States over a manufacturing defect that might cause the side curtain airbag inflators to rupture, the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA) said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chrysler-recall-about-286000-vehicles-due-air-bag-inflators-nhtsa-says-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">63IH7FSSW5I7VJ27ZHBF4HGTGE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 09:42:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街创下历史新高后期货微涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于投资者对美联储坚持其宽松利率立场欢呼雀跃，并等待着美联储主席鲍威尔在当天晚些时候发表评论，周五美国股指期货走高，使华尔街有望实现强劲的周涨幅。【原文：U.S. stock index futures inched higher on Friday, setting Wall Street on course for strong weekly gains as investors cheered the Federal Reserve sticking to its rate-easing stance and awaited commentary from Chair Powell later in the day.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/futures-tick-up-after-wall-street-hits-record-highs-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">77FCNWZTONLKHDN4DK2HYB4HDY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 09:39:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联邦快递因利润增长、最大部门利润率提高而跳涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，联邦快递股价在盘前交易中大涨，原因是这家包裹巨头的季度利润超出预期，而且其最大部门快递公司的营业利润率也有所提高。【原文：FedEx shares surged in premarket trading on Friday after the parcel giant beat estimates for quarterly profit and reported a higher operating margin at Express, its largest unit.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/fedex-jumps-profit-beat-improved-margins-its-largest-unit-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VPMMEQ4QR5JADHBCYWJIWHS4HI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 09:09:04 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>