<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 19:41:46 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 19:41:44 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[耐克失去市场份额，投资者担心相关性]]></title><description><![CDATA[耐克越来越依赖其标志性篮球鞋来提高销售额，但随着这家运动服装巨头的市场份额被新品牌夺走，一些分析师和投资者开始怀疑这是否是个错误。【原文：Nike has increasingly leaned on its iconic basketball shoes to boost sales, but as the sportswear giant bleeds market share to newer brands, some analysts and investors are wondering if that is a mistake.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/nike-its-gotta-be-shoes-could-be-thing-past-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KBLE3SBLPVL5PD6EIRW37WDOPE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 19:21:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[西南航空运输工人批准新劳动合同]]></title><description><![CDATA[西南航空公司周四表示，机坪、运营、供应和货运代理批准了一份为期五年的新劳动合同。【原文：Southwest Airlines said on Thursday ramp, operations, provisioning and cargo agents approved a new five-year labor contract.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/southwest-airlines-transport-workers-approve-new-labor-contract-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3XUCB7YSKVLOBAL6SBVTPI4NIE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 19:10:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[内容创作者担心在没有 TikTok 的世界里会出现教育误区]]></title><description><![CDATA[2020 年 12 月，正值 COVID-19 大流行期间，南方一个农村小镇上的公立学校教师 "詹姆斯女士 "意识到，她的虚拟学生并没有观看她布置的语法课程。直到她把这些内容发布到 TikTok 上。【原文：It was December 2020 during the height of the COVID-19 pandemic when "Ms. James", a public school teacher in a small rural Southern town, realized that her virtual students were not watching the grammar lessons she assigned them. That is, until she posted them on TikTok.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/lifestyle/content-creators-worry-about-miseducation-world-without-tiktok-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UHU3AA37GBPPFAUZ434PUPPAI4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 18:49:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[世贸组织推进争端解决改革谈判遇阻]]></title><description><![CDATA[贸易消息人士称，世界贸易组织正在努力寻找一位大使来领导有关在年底前修复其陷入困境的争端解决体系的谈判，该机构的负责人敦促各国继续努力达成协议。【原文：The World Trade Organization is struggling to find an ambassador to lead negotiations on fixing its hobbled dispute system by the year-end, trade sources said, as the body's chief urged countries to keep striving for a deal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/wto-hits-road-block-over-advancing-dispute-reform-talks-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">INVQZBWJERKA7JRFUCQXXACBIE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 18:41:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国机构称 SpaceX 公司强迫工人签署非法离职协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）的太空探索技术公司（SpaceX）被美国一家劳工机构指控，该公司要求被火箭和卫星制造商解雇或开除的员工签署非法协议，禁止他们诋毁公司和加入针对公司的集体诉讼。【原文：Elon Musk's SpaceX has been accused by a U.S. labor agency of requiring employees who were laid off or fired from the rocket and satellite maker to sign unlawful agreements barring them from disparaging the company and joining class-action lawsuits against it.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/spacex-forced-workers-sign-illegal-severance-agreements-us-agency-claims-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IGPMDC24RFJ3XJ3N5BV2EQFRLQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 18:36:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国上诉法院称，Meta Platforms 必须面对广告商的集体诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国上诉法院出现分歧，法院称 Meta Platforms 必须面对广告商的集体诉讼，这些广告商指控 Facebook 和 Instagram 的所有者欺诈性地夸大广告可能到达的人数，从而向他们多收费用。【原文：A divided U.S. appeals court said Meta Platforms must face a class action by advertisers that accused the Facebook and Instagram owner of overcharging them by fraudulently inflating the number of people their ads might reach.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/meta-platforms-must-face-advertisers-class-action-us-appeals-court-says-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UZR7CWKP2RLRJMTBGQY4NN2INE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 18:31:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Reddit 如何与社交媒体同行相媲美]]></title><description><![CDATA[社交媒体平台 Reddit 周四的首次上市结束了长达两年多的等待，但它与其他上市同行的比较将成为人们关注的焦点。【原文：Social media platform Reddit's market debut on Thursday ended a more than two year-long wait but shifts the focus to how it will compare with the other publicly listed peers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/how-reddit-stacks-up-against-social-media-peers-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DAKISI3UY5K4PA2P3LUUKVZCSY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 17:44:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道文件显示：ADM在政府调查期间向高管支付奖金]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社看到的一封内部电子邮件和美国证券交易委员会的文件显示，因会计问题受到政府调查的粮食贸易商 Archer-Daniels-Midland Co 公司的高管将获得数百万美元的奖金补偿。【原文：Senior executives at Archer-Daniels-Midland Co , the grain trader under government investigation for accounting issues, will receive millions of dollars in bonus compensation, according to an internal email seen by Reuters and Securities and Exchange Commission filings.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/adm-pays-bonuses-senior-executives-midst-government-investigation-documents-show-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CUERH4GO55NZTHYETTPCXIZ6D4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 17:31:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 Information 报道，微软同意向 Inflection 支付 6.5 亿美元，同时雇佣其员工]]></title><description><![CDATA[据 The Information 周四援引一位参与该交易的人士的话报道，微软已同意向 Inflection 支付约 6.5 亿美元，同时雇佣这家人工智能初创公司的员工。【原文：Microsoft has agreed to pay Inflection about $650 million while hiring the AI startup's staff, the Information reported on Thursday, citing a person involved in the deal.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/microsoft-agreed-pay-inflection-650-mln-while-hiring-its-staff-information-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XZS5PFUG4BMKRCSEAMZYYZPZOQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 16:56:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[耐克与阿迪达斯-DFB 合作七十年后，将于 2027 年成为德国供应商]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国足协（DFB）宣布，美国运动服装巨头耐克将从 2027 年起成为其官方供应商，结束与德国阿迪达斯长达数十年的合作关系。【原文：The German Football Association (DFB) announced that American sportswear giant Nike would become their official supplier from 2027 onwards, ending a decades-long partnership with German firm Adidas.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sports/soccer/nike-become-germany-supplier-2027-after-seven-decades-with-adidas-dfb-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">45Y5WWUJYJN6JF3QQDGDCJ7K5Y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 16:40:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合国通过首个全球人工智能决议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国官员说，联合国大会周四通过了首个关于人工智能的全球决议，鼓励保护个人数据、监测人工智能风险和保障人权。【原文：The United Nations General Assembly on Thursday adopted the first global resolution on artificial intelligence to encourage protecting personal data, monitoring AI for risks, and safeguarding human rights, U.S. officials said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/un-adopts-first-global-artificial-intelligence-resolution-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5FIGIA5BHFN2HOZOLSPZOZDCGQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 16:38:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[航空公司和信用卡首席执行官拒绝在美国参议院听证会上作证]]></title><description><![CDATA[参议院司法委员会主席周四表示，美国航空公司、联合航空公司、维萨公司和万事达公司的首席执行官将不会在 4 月 9 日举行的信用卡竞争听证会上作证。【原文：The CEOs of American Airlines, United Airlines, Visa and Mastercard will not testify at an April 9 hearing on credit card competition, the chair of the Senate Judiciary Committee said Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/airline-credit-card-ceos-refuse-testify-us-senate-hearing-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZHVR3WQIBNPFNL3IC3RKBWGH44</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 16:29:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国向苹果发起挑战，遏制大型科技公司的努力蓄势待发]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果公司周四遭到美国司法部的起诉，这是监管机构针对大型科技公司采取的最新反垄断行动，这些公司被指控垄断经营和滥用权力。【原文：Apple was on Thursday sued by the U.S. Department of Justice, the latest antitrust action against Big Tech firms accused by regulators of operating monopolies and abusing their power.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-takes-apple-efforts-curtail-big-tech-gather-momentum-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CO4CX3PDM5KWRLDGQOZPT4LDYM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:58:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，苹果、Meta、谷歌将面临欧盟数字市场法案调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士透露，苹果公司、Meta Platforms 和 Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司将接受调查，以确定它们是否未能遵守欧盟的《数字市场法》。【原文：Apple , Meta Platforms and Alphabet's Google are set to be investigated on whether they have fallen short in complying with the European Union's Digital Markets Act, people with direct knowledge of the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-meta-google-set-face-eu-digital-markets-act-probes-sources-say-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P6WPBFTB2BKSBMZFZ5CMNALGHQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:48:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛资产管理公司为新基金筹资逾 7 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛资产管理公司（Goldman Sachs Asset Management）周四表示，它已为一个新基金筹集了超过 7 亿美元的资金，该基金将与外部经理人合作，在公共和私人市场上寻找投资机会。【原文：Goldman Sachs Asset Management said on Thursday it had raised over $700 million for a new fund that will work with external managers to identify investment opportunities in both public and private markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/goldman-sachs-asset-management-raises-over-700-mln-new-fund-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2TBI2WOWVFMEVO5PF6QVU4CATU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:40:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博法律报道：根据欧盟新数字法，苹果和谷歌将面临调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博法律周刊周四报道，苹果公司和 Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司将面临欧盟对其遵守针对大型科技公司的新法律的调查，这将为可能的巨额罚款铺平道路。【原文：Apple and Alphabet's Google are set to face European Union investigations into their compliance with a new law for Big Tech firms, paving the way for potentially hefty fines, Bloomberg Law reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-google-set-face-probes-under-new-eu-digital-law-bloomberg-law-reports-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GUEEI3SNQBPPTPQ6D4SCE6CBNE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:34:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国债主要收益率曲线反转时间创历史最长纪录]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管美国经济远未出现增长萎缩的迹象，但债券市场即将出现衰退的一个关键信号已经连续闪烁了有史以来最长的时间。【原文：A key bond market signal of an upcoming recession has flashed red continuously for the longest time ever, even if the U.S. economy is far from showing signs of a growth contraction.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/us-treasury-key-yield-curve-inversion-becomes-longest-record-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3HOFPPRUINPX7GSTBBYLNQKFDA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:32:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，西方银行警告欧盟攫取俄罗斯资产计划的风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[业内资深人士说，一些西方银行已经开始游说欧盟，反对重新分配被冻结的俄罗斯资产所赚取的数十亿欧元利息的建议，担心这会导致代价高昂的诉讼。【原文：Some western banks have begun lobbying against EU proposals to redistribute billions of euros in interest earned on frozen Russian assets, senior industry sources said, fearing it could lead to costly litigation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/western-banks-warn-risks-eu-plan-grab-russian-assets-sources-say-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PF6F3P33K5NFJPBFBOHGL35Z6E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:25:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国中芯国际可能违反美国出口禁令生产华为芯片--官方报道]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部一位高级官员在周四的听证会上表示，中国受制裁最严重的芯片制造商中芯国际可能违反了美国的出口法规，因为它生产的芯片为华为 Mate 60 Pro 手机提供了动力。【原文：China's top sanctioned chipmaker SMIC may have violated U.S. export regulations by producing a chip to power Huawei's Mate 60 Pro phone, a senior Commerce Department official said during a hearing on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chinas-smic-may-have-violated-us-export-curbs-make-huawei-chip-official-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VROX6ZIDDNO3XNFBMO2YJE3RZY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:17:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士开始降息，市场已做好准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士周四意外降息后，市场竞相押注大型央行降低借贷成本，但分析师警告说，其他国家的决策者不会轻易放弃抗击通胀的努力。【原文：Markets are racing ahead to bet on big central banks lowering borrowing costs after Switzerland on Thursday delivered a surprise rate cut, but analysts cautioned that policymakers elsewhere won't find it as easy to call time on the inflation fight.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/markets-ready-more-switzerland-starts-clock-rate-cuts-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KSZSK4BHDJMWFGYK36WI3TUSRQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:11:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国监管机构敦促国会调查杂货店利润]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会周四建议，政策制定者应进一步调查食品杂货店经营者自大流行病以来持续走高的利润，以及消费品制造商向零售商提供的促销活动。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission recommended Thursday that policymakers look further into profits at grocery store operators that remain elevated since the pandemic and promotions that consumer products makers offer retailers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-regulators-urge-congress-look-into-grocery-profits-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LX3QRCMGDBNPRODKSKOMBLARTM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:04:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[麦当劳与法国足球甲级联赛签署为期三年的赞助协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国快餐连锁店周四签署了一份为期三年的赞助协议，法国顶级足球联赛将从 7 月 1 日起成为麦当劳法甲联赛。【原文：France's top soccer league will become the McDonald's Ligue 1 from July 1 after the U.S. fast food chain signed a three-year sponsorship deal on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sports/soccer/mcdonalds-signs-three-year-sponsorship-deal-with-french-soccers-ligue-1-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MGU2TBEMCZKZRG5X62VYXVAUCM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:02:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[降息在即，加拿大银行存款争夺战白热化]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师和高管表示，随着利率可能降低，客户将存放在高收益固定收益产品中的资金转向风险更高的投资以寻求更好的回报，加拿大银行之间争夺客户存款的竞争预计将加剧。【原文：Competition for customer deposits among Canadian banks is expected to intensify with the likely onset of lower interest rates as clients divert funds parked in high-yielding fixed income products to riskier investments in search of better returns, analysts and executives say.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/battle-canadian-bank-deposits-seen-heating-up-rate-cuts-loom-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QSMO3KFUVNKXTNUGI6URV2ZZW4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 14:57:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高乐氏将出售部分拉美业务，收费 2.33 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[漂白剂生产商高乐氏（Clorox）周四表示，将向私募股权基金 Apex Capital 出售其在阿根廷、乌拉圭和巴拉圭的业务，因为该公司希望收紧投资组合以提高盈利能力，并将为此一次性支出约 2.33 亿美元。【原文：Bleach maker Clorox said on Thursday that it would sell its operations in Argentina, Uruguay and Paraguay to private equity fund Apex Capital, as it looks to tighten its portfolio to be more profitable, and take a one-time charge of about $233 million related to the sale.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/clorox-sell-some-latin-american-operations-take-233-mln-charge-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7TEXC4AWAFPCTGLYMPDCUJ3JVI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 14:49:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦存款保险公司（FDIC）提案草案：超过 1000 亿美元的银行兼并需接受额外审查]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据美国联邦存款保险公司（U.S. Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation）周四发布的指导草案，可能导致资产超过 1,000 亿美元的银行兼并应受到该机构更严格的审查。【原文：Mergers that could result in banks with more than $100 billion in assets should expect heightened scrutiny from the U.S. Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation, according to draft guidance the agency released Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-fdic-draft-proposal-bank-mergers-above-100-bln-get-extra-scrutiny-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">25HW5SXPWBKZHCLVZXPCFZCMBE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 14:42:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国在反垄断诉讼中起诉苹果公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部周四起诉苹果公司，这是拜登政府针对这家 iPhone 制造商的首次重大反垄断行动，指控其垄断智能手机市场。【原文：The U.S. Department of Justice on Thursday sued Apple , the first major antitrust effort against the iPhone maker by the Biden administration, alleging it monopolized smartphone markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-takes-apple-antitrust-lawsuit-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">45JGEZ4IBZINFN6R3AOB7AQEB4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 14:33:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高管表示，美国必须加快许可证发放速度以促进可再生能源增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国政府高管周四在休斯顿举行的一次会议上表示，美国政府需要简化可再生能源项目的审批程序，包括发展输电基础设施和电网连接，以支持所需的增长。【原文：The U.S. government needs to streamline permitting for renewable energy projects, including development of power transmission infrastructure and grid connectivity, to support needed growth, executives said on Thursday at a conference in Houston.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/ceraweek-permitting-reform-needed-spur-faster-renewable-growth-nrg-ceo-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N6DLUU5TDJNLPI4J5I4JVFEARA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 14:25:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：参议员伊丽莎白-沃伦敦促美国证券交易委员会调查特斯拉董事会独立性问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周四援引一封信报道，美国参议员伊丽莎白-沃伦（Elizabeth Warren）敦促美国证券交易委员会调查特斯拉是否违反了有关上市公司董事会独立性的规定。【原文：U.S. Senator Elizabeth Warren has urged the Securities and Exchange Commission to investigate whether Tesla violated regulations over board independence at public companies, the Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday, citing a letter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/senator-elizabeth-warren-urges-sec-probe-tesla-over-board-independence-wsj-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DSR4GSXLARMD3JTAQHJP2ODI7I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 14:14:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[流媒体订阅推动 2023 年录制音乐收入增长--报告]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四的一份报告称，2023 年全球录制音乐收入连续第九年增长，增长了 10.2%，达到 286 亿美元，这主要得益于付费流媒体用户的增加。【原文：Global recorded music revenues grew for the ninth year running in 2023, increasing 10.2% to $28.6 billion mainly thanks to a rise in paid streaming subscribers, a report said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/streaming-subscriptions-boost-2023-recorded-music-revenues-report-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OYGBGBEKBJNYZNC3DHK2AKYRAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 14:11:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 2 月成屋销售升至一年新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着供应量的增加，2 月份美国现房销售量创下一年来的新高，这一趋势加上抵押贷款利率的下降，可能会支持春季销售旺季的活动。【原文：U.S. existing home sales increased to a one-year high in February as supply improved, a trend that together with retreating mortgage rates could support activity during the spring selling season.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-existing-home-sales-rise-one-year-high-february-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3HAYFLNPRJNAJDNAQUA4P33AG4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 14:03:23 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>