<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 14:20:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 14:20:33 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：参议员伊丽莎白-沃伦敦促美国证券交易委员会调查特斯拉董事会独立性问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周四援引一封信报道，美国参议员伊丽莎白-沃伦（Elizabeth Warren）敦促美国证券交易委员会调查特斯拉是否违反了有关上市公司董事会独立性的规定。【原文：U.S. Senator Elizabeth Warren has urged the Securities and Exchange Commission to investigate whether Tesla violated regulations over board independence at public companies, the Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday, citing a letter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/senator-elizabeth-warren-urges-sec-probe-tesla-over-board-independence-wsj-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DSR4GSXLARMD3JTAQHJP2ODI7I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 14:14:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[流媒体订阅推动 2023 年录制音乐收入增长--报告]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四的一份报告称，2023 年全球录制音乐收入连续第九年增长，增长了 10.2%，达到 286 亿美元，这主要得益于付费流媒体用户的增加。【原文：Global recorded music revenues grew for the ninth year running in 2023, increasing 10.2% to $28.6 billion mainly thanks to a rise in paid streaming subscribers, a report said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/streaming-subscriptions-boost-2023-recorded-music-revenues-report-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OYGBGBEKBJNYZNC3DHK2AKYRAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 14:11:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 2 月成屋销售升至一年新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着供应量的增加，2 月份美国现房销售量创下一年来的新高，这一趋势加上抵押贷款利率的下降，可能会支持春季销售旺季的活动。【原文：U.S. existing home sales increased to a one-year high in February as supply improved, a trend that together with retreating mortgage rates could support activity during the spring selling season.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-existing-home-sales-rise-one-year-high-february-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3HAYFLNPRJNAJDNAQUA4P33AG4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 14:03:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士意外降息，下一个会是谁？]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士国家银行周四启动了降息，这是继不按常理出牌的日本央行 17 年来首次加息之后，本周第二个重要的央行决策。【原文：The Swiss National Bank kicked off rate cuts on Thursday, the week's second momentous central bank decision after the non-conformist Bank of Japan delivered its first rate hike in 17 years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/switzerland-surprises-with-rate-cut-whos-next-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LVCDDIUUYNOHRIQFI64PK36OSU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 13:59:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lyft 与尼尔森签订协议，测量应用内广告]]></title><description><![CDATA[数据分析公司尼尔森（Nielsen）周四表示，尼尔森与 Lyft 已签署协议，将对该打车公司移动应用程序上的广告进行测量。【原文：Nielsen and Lyft have signed an agreement to measure advertisements on the ride-hailing company's mobile app, the data analytics firm said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/lyft-inks-deal-with-nielsen-measure-in-app-ads-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UG46DEC3BNISZFVUFXQ7R7FFYE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 13:54:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 3 月商业活动稳定；通胀回升]]></title><description><![CDATA[3 月份，美国商业活动保持稳定，但物价全面上涨，表明通胀在年初回升后可能继续走高。【原文：U.S. business activity held steady in March, but prices increased across the board, suggesting that inflation could remain elevated after picking up at the start of the year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-business-activity-stable-march-inflation-picks-up-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KIXFVNO6MBIZVL6IQACD5RNRHY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 13:51:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在激烈的代理权争夺战中，ISS 支持激进分子佩尔茨进入迪士尼董事会]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，激进分子纳尔逊-佩尔茨（Nelson Peltz）获得了强有力的支持，代理咨询公司机构股东服务公司（ISS）建议迪士尼股东选举他进入这家娱乐集团的董事会，这对该公司是一个打击。【原文：Activist Nelson Peltz received a powerful endorsement on Thursday when proxy advisory firm Institutional Shareholder Services (ISS) recommended Disney shareholders elect him to the entertainment conglomerate's board, in a blow to the company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/proxy-advisory-firm-iss-recommends-disney-shareholders-elect-nelson-peltz-board-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6PNPSX7HNJM5ZKZ7NT6XZAJVIU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 13:47:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国迫使 Raiffeisen 放弃俄罗斯交易，Raiffeisen 股票和债券再次下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社本周早些时候报道，华盛顿正在向这家奥地利银行施压，要求其取消与一名受制裁的俄罗斯富豪达成的交易，此后，该银行的股票和债券在周四再次下跌。【原文：Raiffeisen's share and bonds fell again on Thursday, after Reuters reported earlier this week that Washington was pressing the Austrian bank to cancel a deal with a sanctioned Russian tycoon.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/raiffeisen-shares-bonds-fall-again-us-presses-bank-drop-russia-deal-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XE5TJYPMSRODRC6VFG5VIQXOA4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 13:37:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CalPERS 称埃克森公司应撤销针对气候意识投资者的诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最大的公共养老基金计划要求埃克森美孚撤销对投资者的诉讼，因为投资者提交了一份股东决议，要求这家美国石油巨头更快地控制温室气体排放。【原文：The largest U.S. public pension fund plans to ask Exxon Mobil to drop a lawsuit against investors that filed a shareholder resolution asking the U.S. oil major to curb greenhouse gas emissions faster.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/calpers-says-exxon-should-drop-lawsuit-against-climate-conscious-investors-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A57BPXN7VZNBVCWKJKNQEELHQQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 13:24:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告显示，3月份美国新车销量将有所增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[据行业咨询公司J.D. Power和GlobalData周四联合发布的一份报告称，受强劲需求和车辆供应的推动，3月份美国新车销量预计将增长12.1%。【原文：U.S. new vehicle sales are expected to rise 12.1% in March, fueled by strong demand and vehicle availability, according to a joint report by industry consultants J.D. Power and GlobalData on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-new-vehicles-sales-set-rise-march-report-shows-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HQUSHJ4FHNOFDCCAW3LQPK33LM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 13:20:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国第四季度经常账户赤字收窄]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国政府周四公布的数据显示，由于二次收入增加，美国第四季度经常账户赤字收窄至近三年来的最低水平。【原文：The U.S. current account deficit narrowed in the fourth quarter to the lowest level in nearly three years amid an increase in secondary income, government data showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-current-account-deficit-narrows-fourth-quarter-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">75QSHU6VIJLPXK3WIPPSWH3AEA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 13:18:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Shake Shack 任命约翰爸爸首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[Shake Shack 周四表示，该公司已任命约翰爸爸国际公司首席执行官罗布-林奇（Rob Lynch）为首席执行官，接替在这家汉堡连锁店工作了二十多年后即将退休的兰迪-加鲁蒂（Randy Garutti）。【原文：Shake Shack said on Thursday it has named Papa John's International's CEO Rob Lynch as its chief, succeeding Randy Garutti, who is retiring after spending more than two decades at the burger chain.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/shake-shack-names-papa-johns-chief-its-ceo-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WWXOZ54VPFOFXJDRCL5DURYFAU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 12:51:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，美国航空公司首席执行官要求与波音董事会会面，以解决生产问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周四援引知情人士的话报道，美国主要航空公司负责人已要求与波音公司董事会会面，以表达对阿拉斯加航空公司事故和生产问题的担忧。【原文：Major U.S. airline chiefs have requested a meeting with Boeing's board to express concerns over an Alaska Airlines accident and production problems, the Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-airline-ceos-request-meeting-with-boeing-board-address-production-problems-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G6KJEBM2RBK7HJ2CCEBBIYEIU4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 12:45:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国每周申请失业救济人数意外下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[上周新申请失业救济的美国人数意外下降，表明 3 月份就业增长依然强劲。【原文：The number of Americans filing new claims for unemployment benefits unexpectedly fell last week, suggesting that job growth remained strong in March.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-weekly-jobless-claims-unexpectedly-fall-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JZK3I4P36VL3JDIELUKVET4CEM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 12:41:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[长江实业集团李嘉诚称香港需要维护金融中心地位]]></title><description><![CDATA[企业集团长江实业集团（CK Group）主席李泽钜（Victor Li）周四表示，经过多年动荡之后，香港政府需要保护香港的国际金融中心地位。【原文：The Hong Kong government needs to protect the city's international financial hub status after years of upheaval, chairman of conglomerate CK Group Victor Li said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/ck-groups-li-says-hong-kong-needs-safeguard-financial-hub-status-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VDPDL63I4VJVTA3L747MY5GAD4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 12:35:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国央行认为经济 "朝着正确方向发展 "有利于降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国央行行长安德鲁-贝利（Andrew Bailey）表示，英国经济正 "朝着正确的方向发展"，英国央行可以开始降息，他的两位同事放弃了对加息的投票。【原文：Britain's economy is "moving in the right direction" for the Bank of England to start cutting interest rates, Governor Andrew Bailey said as two of his colleagues dropped their vote for a rate hike.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/bank-england-sees-economy-moving-right-direction-rate-cuts-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W4JHQJFVBRJCFMNINJHZSV7UJY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 12:03:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯称乌克兰关于 30 美元油价上限的想法 "超越了所有界限"]]></title><description><![CDATA[俄罗斯周四表示，美国不太可能同意乌克兰提出的将俄罗斯石油价格上限降至每桶30美元的建议，因为这将扰乱全球能源市场并损害美国经济。【原文：Russia said on Thursday that the United States was unlikely to agree to a Ukrainian proposal to lower the price cap on Russian oil to $30 a barrel because it would roil global energy markets and damage the U.S. economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/russia-says-ukraines-idea-30-oil-price-cap-beyond-all-bounds-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NOSLKQ4G7FPY7MGTOWQ7B27TAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 12:00:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞银全球研究将美联储降息预期推迟至 6 月]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞银全球研究公司（UBS Global Research）周四表示，目前预计美联储将从6月开始降息，比之前的预测晚一个月，与其他券商的预测一致，此前美联储基本坚持了其货币政策轨迹。【原文：UBS Global Research now expects the Federal Reserve to start cutting interest rates from June, a month later that its previous prediction and in line with other brokerages' forecasts, it said on Thursday, after the central bank broadly stuck to its monetary policy trajectory.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/ubs-global-research-pushes-back-fed-rate-cut-expectation-june-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WWAVV7HAOVJOHBBPVRLLMSBWRY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 11:32:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果公司首席执行官库克在上海开设新店]]></title><description><![CDATA[据中国社交媒体上的帖子称，苹果公司首席执行官蒂姆-库克周四在上海为苹果新店开业吸引了大量人群，有些人通宵排队。【原文：Apple CEO Tim Cook opened Apple's new store in Shanghai drawing a large crowd on Thursday, with some people queuing overnight, according to posts on Chinese social media.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apples-ceo-cook-opens-new-store-shanghai-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OYFC4OJU6FP2VF2B3JSLQREBBY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 11:19:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ETFS Capital 批评 WisdomTree 战略，对董事会发起 "扣留运动]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社看到的一封信，ETFS Capital 要求 WisdomTree 的股东在重新选举这家美国资产管理公司的部分董事会成员时弃权，并称如果该公司经营得更好，其股价至少可以飙升 70%。【原文：ETFS Capital asked shareholders of WisdomTree to abstain from re-electing some board members of the U.S. asset manager, saying its stock could surge at least 70% if it were run better, according to a letter seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/etfs-capital-criticizes-wisdomtree-strategy-launches-withhold-campaign-vs-board-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LCPXUVTNGRJFXBUU3KRPPXKFVA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 11:08:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[聚焦：哥伦比亚政策摇摆不定，投资受挫，经济增长面临风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[哥伦比亚总统古斯塔沃-彼得罗（Gustavo Petro）的政策摇摆不定，导致投资急剧下降，预计今年仍将继续，因为一些企业主抱怨战略规划几乎变得不可能。【原文：Colombian President Gustavo Petro's track record of unpredictable policy lurches has contributed to a sharp drop in investment that is expected to continue this year, as some business owners complain strategic planning has become almost impossible.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/colombia-policy-lurches-chill-investment-risk-economic-growth-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2P64LS2IBZNHHBJKKAUYYINOFM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 11:07:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[埃森哲下调年度收入预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[IT服务提供商埃森哲周四下调了2024财年的收入预期，原因是不确定的经济形势促使客户削减了对其咨询服务的支出。【原文：IT services provider Accenture cut its fiscal-year 2024 revenue forecast on Thursday, as an uncertain economy prompts clients to cut spending on its consulting services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/accenture-cuts-annual-revenue-forecast-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KAYRPCJUINKLRLLWHIHV2WUHGA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 10:47:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西咖啡产量将出现罕见的连续增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社汇编的数据，巴西今年的咖啡产量预计将实现第三次年度增长，在这个世界上最大的咖啡豆种植国和出口国 144 年的咖啡历史中，这种罕见的情况仅出现过七次。【原文：Brazil is expected to post its third annual increase in coffee production this year, a rare sequence seen only seven times in 144 years of coffee history in the world's largest grower and exporter of the beans, according to data compiled by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/brazil-heading-rare-sequence-rising-coffee-crops-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LHJLU4IFJ5IK5HNIXMJTIVCJ7E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 10:41:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大多数券商坚持美联储 6 月开始降息的预测]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国央行在 3 月 19-20 日的会议上维持利率不变，并维持今年降息三次的预测，大多数主要券商坚持美联储将从 6 月开始降息的预期。【原文：Most major brokerages stuck by their expectations that the Federal Reserve will start lowering interest rates from June after the U.S. central bank left interest rates unchanged at its March 19-20 meeting and maintained its projection of three cuts this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/most-brokerages-stick-by-forecast-fed-rate-cuts-starting-june-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">N6VB7O66QNOHREJWFINIMABVLY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 10:38:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Reddit 首次公开募股定价在区间最高点，将迎来炙手可热的首次亮相]]></title><description><![CDATA[社交媒体平台 Reddit 周四在纽约证券交易所高调上市，为其他希望在今年上市的公司创造了条件，同时也检验了投资者对新股的偏好。【原文：Social media platform Reddit geared up for its high-profile market debut on the New York Stock Exchange on Thursday, setting the stage for other companies looking to go public this year, while testing investor appetite for new issues.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/reddit-set-hotly-anticipated-debut-after-pricing-ipo-top-range-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">R2WLNN6SAJJUJFMFX2J6DOHUNM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 10:34:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博新闻社称，塔吉特今年有望将奖金翻番]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周四援引知情人士的话报道，大型零售商塔吉特（Target）今年将把受薪员工的奖金提高一倍。【原文：Big-box retailer Target is doubling the bonuses for its salaried employees this year, Bloomberg News reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/target-looks-double-bonuses-this-year-bloomberg-news-says-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GAGBG2VSHVO2NJIQ5KS6MHPICU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 10:28:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[香港外企警惕新安保法，加强应急计划]]></title><description><![CDATA[香港新国家安全法中有关国家机密和与外国实体联系的模糊条款，让这个金融中心的许多全球企业惶恐不安，一些咨询公司和对冲基金更新了应急计划，并寻求法律建议，以应对这一政治风险。【原文：Vague provisions in Hong Kong's new national security law around state secrets and links to foreign entities have put on edge many global businesses in the financial hub, with some consultants and hedge funds updating contingency plans and seeking legal advice in a bid to counter this political risk.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/wary-new-security-law-foreign-firms-hong-kong-bolster-contingency-plans-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IHFCBVDZMZK6FOTO7XLJ4FFKNI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 10:09:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高银行监管机构将公布合并政策提案]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦存款保险公司周四将成为最新一家提出银行兼并新政策的美国监管机构，因为中型贷款机构仍处于不稳定状态。【原文：The U.S. Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation on Thursday is set to become the latest American regulator to propose new policies for mergers among banks amid the instability that continues to rattle midsize lenders.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/top-us-bank-overseer-unveil-merger-policy-proposal-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6VWAWE6JRVPNXDLLRR64JYXZ2U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 10:08:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织总裁格奥尔基耶娃敦促央行在大选年降息压力下保持独立性]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织总裁克里斯塔琳娜-格奥尔基耶娃（Kristalina Georgieva）周四警告说，在大选年，各国央行面临着越来越大的降息政治压力，但决策者需要保持其独立性。【原文：International Monetary Fund Managing Director Kristalina Georgieva warned on Thursday that central banks face growing political pressure to cut interest rates during a major election year but policymakers need to maintain their independence.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/imfs-georgieva-urges-central-bank-independence-amid-election-year-rate-cut-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YNQQ6OJFH5O4VH2TYWWZCM5ASM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 10:06:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道消息人士称，CapOne 告诉监管机构 Discover 交易将促进竞争和稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[据熟知内情的人士透露，Capital One 在其监管申请中表示，该公司与 Discover Financial 353 亿美元的合并将促进竞争，并有利于金融稳定。【原文：Capital One's $35.3 billion merger with Discover Financial will boost competition and be good for financial stability, the bank says in its regulatory application, according to people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/capone-tells-regulators-discover-deal-will-boost-competition-stability-sources-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">22TPR42DRBLHZP3YQRXDLNKQSI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 10:05:30 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>