<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 07:46:41 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 07:46:39 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[中国 3 月出口可能重回收缩态势]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周四的一项民意调查显示，中国出口在今年前两个月以好于预期的速度增长后，3月份可能出现下降，这凸显了世界第二大经济体复苏的不平衡。【原文：China's exports likely declined in March after they grew at a better-than-expected pace in the first two months of this year, a Reuters poll showed on Thursday, highlighting an uneven recovery in the world's second-biggest economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/chinas-exports-likely-swung-back-contraction-march-2024-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QTTIG2CETRMFNPHM34GWYKZUH4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 07:31:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国第一季度 GDP 增速将放缓至 4.6%，继续面临更多刺激政策的压力--路透调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周四的一项民意调查显示，中国第一季度经济可能同比增长4.6%，为一年来最慢，尽管有初步企稳迹象。【原文：China's economy likely grew 4.6% in the first quarter from a year earlier - the slowest in a year despite tentative signs of steadying, a Reuters poll showed on Thursday, maintaining pressure on policymakers to unveil more stimulus measures.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/chinas-q1-gdp-growth-set-slow-46-keeps-pressure-more-stimulus-2024-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YKQNRSHM6BK5ZDMBLVUZWOV26A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 06:48:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿斯利康在股东大会表决首席执行官薪酬前宣布上调股息]]></title><description><![CDATA[阿斯利康（AstraZeneca）公司周四表示，公司打算将2024年的年度股息提高7%，达到每股3.10美元，希望凭借其大片药物和最近的几项收购，实现强劲的业绩和现金流。【原文：AstraZeneca said on Thursday it intends to increase annual dividend for 2024 by 7% to $3.10 per share, betting on strong performance and cash generation on the back of its blockbuster drugs and several recent acquisitions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/astrazeneca-increase-2024-dividend-by-7-strong-growth-2024-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FRMXUU5VKFITTEFIAUIL25HEX4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 06:30:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士银行计划让瑞银 "如释重负"，立即脱离火线]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士政府制定了旨在约束这家 "怪兽银行 "的计划，但这些计划的细节并不详尽，而且预示着将这些计划写入法律的政治进程将十分曲折，因此瑞银可能需要数年时间才能感受到新法规的影响。【原文：UBS could take years to feel the bite of new regulations after the Swiss government set out plans aimed at keeping the "monster bank" in line that were light on detail and heralded a tortuous political process to enshrine them in law.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/swiss-banking-plan-leaves-relieved-ubs-out-immediate-firing-line-2024-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">C7SDG2AGK5J35LUAG45OP2OXDM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 05:10:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国降息押注破灭刺激投资者转移投资组合]]></title><description><![CDATA[对通胀反弹的担忧正迫使投资者为 2024 年可能出现的情况做好准备：这一年美国不会降息。【原文：Fears of rebounding inflation are forcing investors to prepare for a scenario few expected to confront in 2024: a year without U.S. interest rate cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/unraveling-us-rate-cut-bets-spur-investor-portfolio-shifts-2024-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">37PFP4BLF5PCHAS3GWMZERUFBU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 05:04:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[耐克寄希望于奥运会，争夺市场份额]]></title><description><![CDATA[耐克公司将为其赞助的美国和肯尼亚等奥运国家队推出新款运动服，以增强其作为顶级运动员和普通消费者的高性能装备品牌的实力。【原文：Nike is set to unveil new kits for the Olympic national teams it sponsors including the U.S. and Kenya, seeking to bolster its credentials as a performance gear brand for top athletes as well as everyday consumers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/nike-pins-hopes-olympics-race-take-back-market-share-2024-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XZIBBIFPKFP77CKKRSGAWA7ELY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 05:03:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标：夏季削减渐行渐远？]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tom Westbrook 展望欧洲和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in European and global markets from Tom Westbrook】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/global-markets-view-europe-2024-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GBZW2JWZCZJVZOPVGWTDJSMYV4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 04:31:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[平安信托以中国房地产市场困境为由推迟还款]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国平安保险的一家子公司未能按时偿还约 1.07 亿美元的信托产品，理由是房地产市场出现危机，并表示正在起诉其投资该笔款项的开发商振罗地产。【原文：A subsidiary of China's Ping An Insurance failed to repay a roughly $107 million trust product on time, citing the property market crisis and adding that it is suing developer Zhenro Properties with which it invested the sum.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/ping-an-trust-delays-repayment-citing-china-property-market-woes-2024-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SCPLETUSNROADAYLKZ6FTXQQQE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 04:06:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日元创 34 年新低，日本称不排除采取任何外汇行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本财务大臣铃木俊一周四表示，在美元兑日元汇率飙升至 34 年新高后，政府不排除采取任何措施来应对汇率的过度波动。【原文：Japanese Finance Minister Shunichi Suzuki said on Thursday that authorities would not rule out any steps to deal with excessive exchange-rate swings after the dollar surged to a 34-year high against the yen.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/japan-says-it-wont-rule-out-any-fx-action-yen-hits-34-year-low-2024-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JDDDJPQXYZLBREEINUBHOCQ4LM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 03:00:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国将在贸易制裁决定中考虑对中国 "辉煌 "的担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部表示，拜登政府在决定将哪些公司列入贸易制裁名单时，将考虑共和党参议员马可-鲁比奥（Marco Rubio）对中国芯片设计商博瑞半导体公司（Brite Semiconductor）的担忧。【原文：The Biden administration will consider concerns about Chinese chip designer Brite Semiconductor flagged by Republican Senator Marco Rubio as it decides what firms to add to a trade sanction list, the Commerce Department said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-consider-concerns-about-chinas-brite-trade-sanction-decisions-2024-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HYDLOYRHCJMLHL5DPJSKVY7D3A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 02:39:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球利率恐慌导致亚洲股市下跌，日元暴跌至 34 年低点]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，亚洲股市追随华尔街走低，原因是美国通胀率持续走高迫使市场削减了对美联储今年可能采取多少宽松政策的押注，这一结果使得美元兑日元汇率飞升至34年来的新高。【原文：Asian shares tracked Wall Street lower on Thursday as sticky U.S. inflation forced markets to slash bets on how much Federal Reserve easing might come this year, a result that sent the dollar flying to a 34-year high against the beleaguered yen.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-wrapup-1-2024-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BAIGZPTW6VO2ZPOH3H54EEDFFU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 02:15:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国居民消费价格连续两个月上涨，工厂通货紧缩依然存在]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国 3 月份的消费价格连续第二个月上涨，而生产者价格通货紧缩依然存在，这表明尽管有迹象表明陷入困境的经济正在恢复一些动力，但需求依然疲软。【原文：China's consumer prices in March rose for a second straight month while producer price deflation persisted, pointing to still weak demand despite signs that the struggling economy is regaining some momentum.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-consumer-prices-rise-2nd-month-factory-deflation-persists-2024-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4N7CD7KI3NPVFIN5JKCLNPFD5A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 01:43:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中东危机恶化引发担忧，石油巩固涨势]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于投资者担心中东危机恶化，欧佩克第三大产油国伊朗可能卷入其中，油价在周四亚洲早盘交易中持稳。【原文：Oil prices held steady in early Asian trading on Thursday after gaining a dollar a barrel in the prior session as investors braced for a worsening of the Middle East crisis, potentially involving Iran, the third-largest oil producer in OPEC.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/oil-consolidates-gains-amid-concerns-worsening-middle-east-crisis-2024-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">37EQFHDE25PH7GT4ZT6J56EOCE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 01:30:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储减息预期破灭，美元走强，日元下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国通胀数据好于预期，压制了美联储在 6 月份启动降息周期的预期，美元在周四走强，而日元则在 1990 年中期的水平上徘徊。【原文：The dollar was firm on Thursday after hotter-than-expected U.S. inflation data squashed lingering expectations of the Fed starting its rate-cutting cycle in June, while the yen languished at the levels last seen in the middle of 1990.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-firms-yen-skids-fed-cut-wagers-crumble-2024-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G5VPMFZ5JFKVNBCYOH2SC6236U</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 01:27:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国陪审团称亚马逊在云存储专利战中欠款 5.25 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国伊利诺伊州联邦陪审团周三表示，全球最大的云服务提供商亚马逊公司旗下的亚马逊网络服务公司（Amazon Web Services）因侵犯其数据存储技术专利权而拖欠科技公司 Kove 5.25 亿美元。【原文：Amazon.com's Amazon Web Services, the world's largest cloud-service provider, owes tech company Kove $525 million for violating its patent rights in data-storage technology, an Illinois federal jury said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/amazon-owes-525-mln-cloud-storage-patent-fight-us-jury-says-2024-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UCGHMDBVMZMYVLQVHYRGY5CHB4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 00:56:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用电气航空航天集团的斯莱特里将于 6 月卸任，但仍将担任顾问]]></title><description><![CDATA[通用电气航空航天集团首席执行官拉里-卡尔普（Larry Culp）周三表示，通用电气航空航天集团首席商务官约翰-斯莱特里（John Slattery）将于今年 6 月从这家喷气发动机制造商离职，并将继续担任顾问。【原文：The chief commercial officer of GE Aerospace , John Slattery, will step down from the jet engine maker in June and will remain an adviser, CEO Larry Culp said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/ge-aerospaces-slattery-step-down-june-remain-adviser-2024-04-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HT4H7NVVA5PQJEA6MIVEFHQCPA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 00:19:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[什么产能过剩？中国称其产业只是更具竞争力]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国务卿珍妮特-耶伦（Janet Yellen）访华行程的最后一天，恰逢中国政府官员对她声称中国正在用廉价商品充斥全球市场，尤其是在新兴绿色产业领域的说法进行最强烈的反驳。【原文：The last day of U.S. Secretary Janet Yellen's trip to China coincided with the strongest retort yet from Beijing officials over her claims that China is flooding global markets with cheap goods, particularly in the new green industries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/what-overcapacity-china-says-its-industries-are-simply-more-competitive-2024-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BHRFUDVXWBNJDJYJ7QIOPAOONE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 23:31:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[苹果公司新泽西州专卖店工人申请成立工会]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国各行各业推动成立工会的背景下，苹果公司位于新泽西州肖特希尔斯的专卖店的一名员工周三表示，该专卖店的工人已经申请加入工会，他是组织委员会的成员之一。【原文：Workers at Apple's store in Short Hills, New Jersey, have filed for union representation, a staff member who is part of the organizing committee said on Wednesday amid a push for unionization across sectors in corporate America.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apples-new-jersey-store-workers-file-petition-unionization-2024-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FPTDJ346BNMA7GYZADZ7K42XZY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 22:24:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价美国通胀冲击日元，下一个是中国 CPI]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲市场前瞻【原文：A look at the day ahead in Asian markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-markets-view-asia-graphic-pix-2024-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FY5FED6UN5P5JAEWODRWGTJGIU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 21:49:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据 Politico 报道，美国司法部对新日铁与美国钢铁公司的交易展开深入调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部已对新日铁公司斥资 141 亿美元收购美国钢铁公司一事展开深入的反垄断调查。【原文：The U.S. Justice Department has opened up an in-depth antitrust investigation into Nippon Steel's $14.1 billion takeover of U.S. Steel , the Politico reported on Wednesday citing two people with direct knowledge of the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/us-justice-department-opens-in-depth-probe-into-nippon-steels-us-steel-deal-2024-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2EKUVWXYHNMEZDAUFEZORI2PJE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 21:36:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[空中客车公司面临支持喷气机增产的前期成本问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[空中客车公司（Airbus）财务总监周三表示，在准备提高喷气机产量的过程中，该公司正在产生前期成本，并计划在达到产量目标后留出喘息空间来消化这些成本。【原文：Airbus is incurring up-front costs as it prepares for higher jet production and plans a breathing space to absorb them once it reaches its output goal, its finance chief said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/airbus-facing-upfront-costs-support-jet-output-increase-2024-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NXOAZLHLAJOPDEHQBRKLN3BIZE</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 21:09:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国司法部对 Regeneron 提起诉讼，指控其药品定价存在欺诈行为]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部周三表示，已对 Regeneron 制药公司提起虚假索赔诉讼，称该公司提交了虚假的平均销售价格报告。【原文：The U.S. Justice Department said on Wednesday it had filed a false claims act complaint against Regeneron Pharmaceuticals , claiming the company filed false average sales price reports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-justice-department-files-complaint-against-regeneron-alleges-fraudulent-drug-2024-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OPZHX7QQ3NPULMF6BENXCAVSYA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 20:59:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国证券交易委员会警告 Uniswap Labs 可能采取执法行动]]></title><description><![CDATA[Uniswap Labs 是全球最大的加密货币交易所之一，该公司在周三的一篇博文中表示，美国证券交易委员会已通知可能对其采取执法行动。【原文：The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission has notified of potential enforcement action against Uniswap Labs, the main developer behind one of the world's largest cryptocurrency exchanges, the company said in a blog post on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/sec-warns-uniswap-labs-potential-enforcement-action-2024-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O2KZQFGW7FLAHJKVUE3Q2OEZGY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 20:43:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家运输安全委员会调查费城福特Mach-E致命车祸]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家运输安全委员会（NTSB）周三表示，正在对 3 月 3 日发生在费城 I-95 州际高速公路上的福特野马 Mach-E 与两辆静止汽车之间的致命车祸展开调查。【原文：The U.S. National Transportation Safety Board (NTSB) said on Wednesday it was opening an investigation into a March 3 fatal crash between a Ford Mustang Mach-E and two stationary cars on the I-95 interstate highway in Philadelphia.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-ntsb-probes-fatal-ford-mach-e-crash-philadelphia-2024-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VBOSOXF22FJRBL5IGZ2F52APQ4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 20:41:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Vertex 制药公司将以 49 亿美元收购阿尔卑斯免疫科学公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[Vertex Pharmaceuticals 公司周三表示，将以每股 65 美元或约 49 亿美元的现金收购疗法开发商 Alpine Immune Sciences 公司。【原文：Vertex Pharmaceuticals will acquire therapy developer Alpine Immune Sciences for $65 per share, or about $4.9 billion in cash, the companies said on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/vertex-pharmaceuticals-buy-alpine-immune-sciences-49-bln-2024-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6OFIUAMXFBJF3FPMA255LYEZIY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 20:20:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家运输安全委员会称西南航空发动机盖丢失系维修问题所致]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家运输安全委员会（NTSB）主席表示，西南航空公司一架波音 737-800 飞机周日在丹佛起飞时发动机盖脱落并击中机翼襟翼，这是维修问题造成的。【原文：The chair of the National Transportation Safety Board (NTSB) said the loss of an engine cover on a Southwest Airlines Boeing 737-800 on Sunday that fell off during takeoff in Denver and struck the wing flap was the result of a maintenance issue.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/ntsb-says-southwest-engine-cover-loss-caused-by-maintenance-issue-2024-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">COTCBBLINNL2PGPLW2LY7M564E</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 18:59:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国政府对苹果公司的反垄断诉讼案在法官回避后换了新法官]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部指控苹果公司非法垄断智能手机市场的大案周三被重新分配给新泽西州的美国地区法官朱利安-尼尔斯（Julien Neals）审理，此前另一位法官表示由于潜在的利益冲突他不能审理此案。【原文：The U.S. Justice Department's blockbuster case accusing Apple of unlawfully monopolizing the smartphone market was reassigned to U.S. District Judge Julien Neals in New Jersey on Wednesday after another judge said he could not hear it due to a potential conflict of interest.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-governments-apple-antitrust-suit-gets-new-judge-after-recusal-2024-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QW5YAT2S35NITFANGRM3SASA6Q</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 18:46:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储官员准备放缓资产负债表缩减步伐]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储官员正准备明显放慢允许国债从美联储资产负债表中撤出的速度，为最终结束缩表做准备。【原文：Federal Reserve officials are preparing to notably slow the pace at which they allow Treasury securities to come off the Fed's balance sheet as they prepare for an eventual end to the drawdown.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/fed-officials-preparing-slow-pace-balance-sheet-runoff-2024-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">76KIEUJJXFIS5N2FRKHE4HR3PY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 18:34:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴克莱将美联储降息预期下调至 2024 年一次]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴克莱银行（Barclays）经济学团队周三表示，鉴于今天公布的消费者物价指数（CPI）数据意外上扬，该团队目前认为美国联邦储备委员会（Federal Reserve）在2024年只会降息一次，降幅为25个基点（bps）。【原文：Barclays economics team on Wednesday said it now sees the U.S. Federal Reserve cutting rates just one time in 2024, by 25 basis points (bps), in light of the upside surprise to the consumer price index (CPI) data released today.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/barclays-reduces-fed-rate-cut-view-one-2024-2024-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">E3376IKYZZNQTMMDXCPLPCMKAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 18:30:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[会议纪要显示，美联储对通货紧缩的 "信心 "并未因近期数据而增强]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据美国中央银行 3 月 19-20 日的会议纪要，政策制定者保持了在 2024 年降息三次的基线观点。【原文：Federal Reserve officials worried last month that progress on inflation might have stalled and a longer period of tight monetary policy be needed to tame the pace of price increases, according to the minutes of the U.S. central bank's March 19-20 meeting at which policymakers kept a baseline view for three interest rate cuts in 2024.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-confidence-disinflation-not-helped-by-recent-data-minutes-show-2024-04-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BHN4VWSAXVNT3HL2KEPYATCLNQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 18:07:50 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>