<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 07:26:32 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 07:26:32 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，Salesforce 正在就收购 Informatica 进行深入谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[华尔街日报》周五援引知情人士的话报道，Salesforce 正在就收购数据管理软件提供商 Informatica 进行深入谈判。【原文：Salesforce is in advanced talks to acquire data-management software provider Informatica , the Wall Street Journal reported on Friday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/salesforce-is-advanced-talks-buy-informatica-wsj-reports-2024-04-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JN2CLG2LUVOWXIFLZ7NF4HOINQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 01:29:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Coinbase 要求就起诉美国证券交易委员会的部分案件提起上诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[Coinbase 周五请求两家法院批准对其与美国证券交易委员会（SEC）正在进行的诉讼的部分内容提起上诉，以求更快地就数字资产是否类似于投资合同做出裁决。【原文：Coinbase asked two courts for permission on Friday to appeal part of its ongoing lawsuit with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) in an effort to more quickly obtain a ruling on whether digital assets resemble investment contracts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/coinbase-asks-appeal-part-case-against-us-sec-2024-04-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O55TACTF7VNR5K4AKBUV53IW2Q</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 01:16:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华为推出搭载新型英特尔人工智能芯片的笔记本电脑后，美国议员感到愤怒]]></title><description><![CDATA[受制裁的中国电信设备巨头华为本周推出了搭载英特尔人工智能芯片的笔记本电脑，美国共和党议员周五批评拜登政府。【原文：Republican U.S. lawmakers on Friday criticized the Biden administration after sanctioned Chinese telecoms equipment giant Huawei unveiled a laptop this week powered by an Intel AI chip.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-lawmakers-angry-after-huawei-unveils-laptop-with-new-intel-ai-chip-2024-04-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OQ377KIK6VNH5GVEMQR32K4LVI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 23:54:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[SAG-AFTRA 工会与主要唱片公司达成协议，为艺术家提供人工智能保护]]></title><description><![CDATA[好莱坞表演者和媒体专业人士与华纳音乐集团和索尼音乐娱乐公司等主要唱片公司达成了一项临时协议，其中包括提高最低工资和防止使用人工智能。【原文：Hollywood performers and media professionals have reached a tentative deal with major record labels such as Warner Music Group and Sony Music Entertainment that includes increases in minimum salaries and protections against the use of AI.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/sag-aftra-union-secures-ai-protections-artists-deal-with-major-record-labels-2024-04-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O67GKCVIKZPXBPUST2YZMH7D5I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 22:52:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉下调美国和加拿大的全自动驾驶订购价格]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉电动汽车制造商周五在 X 网站上发文称，特斯拉已将其完全自动驾驶（FSD）服务在美国的订购价格降至每月 99 美元，在加拿大的订购价格降至每月 99 加元。【原文：Tesla has cut prices of its Full Self Driving (FSD) subscriptions to $99 per month in the United States and to C$99 per month in Canada, the electric vehicle maker said on Friday in a post on X.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-cuts-full-self-driving-subscription-prices-us-canada-2024-04-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HW4MEDLUOJIN3KQAJYUVKICJEE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 22:51:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约广播公司任命克雷格-吉福德（Craig Gifford）为首席财务官]]></title><description><![CDATA[陷入困境的贷款机构纽约社区银行（New York Community Bancorp）周五任命克雷格-吉福德（Craig Gifford）为首席财务官，并任命了其他高管。【原文：Embattled lender New York Community Bancorp on Friday named Craig Gifford as chief financial officer, among other executive appointments.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/nycb-names-craig-gifford-cfo-2024-04-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4I7K7A67MZOAVJHIN36QMQYCOM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 22:21:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储戴利：美国绝对没有降息的紧迫性]]></title><description><![CDATA[旧金山联储主席玛丽-戴利（Mary Daly）周五表示，仍有 "大量工作要做"，以确保通胀率按计划达到美联储2%的目标，而且 "绝对 "没有降息的紧迫性。【原文：San Francisco Federal Reserve President Mary Daly said on Friday there is still "a lot of work to do" to make sure inflation is on track to the Fed's 2% goal, and there is "absolutely" no urgency to cut rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-daly-absolutely-no-urgency-cut-us-interest-rates-2024-04-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HUW4DW6EDNL6DHONM5TD6KY22I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 20:37:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 美国能源股大涨反映强劲增长和通胀忧虑]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源股正在飙升，原因是投资者受益于油价上涨和经济强于预期，同时也在寻求保护自己的投资组合，以防担心的通货膨胀卷土重来。【原文：U.S. energy shares are soaring as investors benefit from rising oil prices and a stronger-than-expected economy, while seeking to protect their portfolios from a feared resurgence of inflation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-st-week-ahead-surging-us-energy-shares-reflect-robust-growth-inflation-2024-04-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JLJ4IDIJIRMB7BCGKRC36C5UKU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 19:50:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道波音737产量下降，精神航空系统公司限制加班和招聘]]></title><description><![CDATA[波音公司的主要供应商 Spirit AeroSystems 公司周五告诉路透社，由于 737 MAX 喷气式飞机产量下降，该公司正在限制加班和招聘。【原文：Boeing's key supplier Spirit AeroSystems is limiting overtime and hiring as production declines due to lower output of 737 MAX jets, Spirit told Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/spirit-aerosystems-limits-overtime-hiring-boeing-737-output-drops-2024-04-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GQIU7UJEQZOGVBS2RKI7462RXU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 19:48:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对冲基金 Barington 敦促派拉蒙放弃与 Skydance 的谈判]]></title><description><![CDATA[对冲基金 Barington Capital 周五敦促派拉蒙全球放弃与 Skydance Media 的独家合并谈判，认为如果该公司考虑其他潜在竞购者，所有股东都将受益。【原文：Hedge fund Barington Capital on Friday urged Paramount Global to scrap its exclusive merger talks with Skydance Media, arguing all shareholders would benefit if the company looked at other potential bidders.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/hedge-fund-barington-urges-paramount-scrap-talks-with-skydance-2024-04-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BCBGKIYK3JJCBFOZUJZVXO6FQQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 18:53:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[不到一半的美国银行准备在紧急情况下向美联储借款]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据美联储周五公布的数据，在硅谷银行倒闭一年后，只有不到一半的美国银行通过在美联储紧急借贷机制中抵押建立了借贷能力。【原文：A year after Silicon Valley Bank's failure, less than half of U.S. banks have established borrowing capacity by pledging collateral at the Federal Reserve's emergency lending facility, according to Fed data released on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/less-than-half-us-banks-ready-borrow-fed-emergency-2024-04-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5W5FXSJTYBIWNOJZAB5S56BAYY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 18:50:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[自 1 月 1 日起，美国向汽车经销商发放超过 5.8 亿美元的电动汽车退税预付款]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周五表示，自 1 月 1 日以来，美国政府已向汽车经销商偿还了超过 5.8 亿美元的销售点消费者电动汽车税收抵免预付款。【原文：The U.S. government has reimbursed auto dealers for more than $580 million in advance point-of-sale consumer electric vehicle tax credit payments since Jan. 1, the Treasury said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-issues-over-580-million-advance-ev-tax-rebates-auto-dealers-since-jan-1-2024-04-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2XIYLDG5KFJZFEFDEEZPRJ2MJY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 18:43:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消费者价格读数高企后，美联储主席古尔斯比继续将政策重点放在 PCE 上]]></title><description><![CDATA[芝加哥联储主席奥斯坦-古尔斯比（Austan Goolsbee）周五表示，消费者物价指数持续走高令人担忧，但他仍然关注美联储目标个人消费价格支出指数的表现。【原文：Chicago Federal Reserve President Austan Goolsbee said on Friday continued high consumer price index readings were concerning, but he remains focused on how the Fed's targeted personal consumption price expenditures index behaves.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-goolsbee-keeps-policy-focus-pce-after-high-consumer-price-readings-2024-04-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IOTCRJZ2GROQFKK3UEKEQJWKUI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 18:13:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[利率走势不明朗，美国银行利润前景不甚明朗]]></title><description><![CDATA[利率走势的不确定性使美国银行难以预测利润，并导致一些银行对今年剩余时间采取谨慎态度。【原文：The uncertain trajectory of interest rates is making it hard for U.S. banks to forecast profits and leading some to adopt a cautious stance for the remainder of the year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-banks-profit-picture-less-clear-with-cloudy-rates-trajectory-2024-04-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XWZ3EKAKOBOWRMYJHJ6HYN5VGU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 17:55:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[施密德：通胀率仍然过高，美联储不会降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[堪萨斯城联储主席杰夫-施密德（Jeff Schmid）周五表示，美国央行目前不应考虑降息，因为通胀率仍高于2%的目标，就业市场也很强劲。【原文：Kansas City Federal Reserve President Jeff Schmid said on Friday the U.S. central bank should not be weighing interest rate cuts at this time because inflation remains above its 2% target and the job market is strong.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/inflation-still-too-high-fed-cut-interest-rates-schmid-says-2024-04-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BRZARWGY3VMJ3BB7VNZQL3CYZ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 17:40:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博社报道，美国钢铁公司股东批准新日铁以 149 亿美元收购美国钢铁公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周五报道，美国钢铁公司的股东已经投票通过了日本新日铁公司以 149 亿美元收购美国钢铁公司的提议，从而使这一合并朝着完成又迈进了一步，尽管对这一交易的政治反对呼声日益高涨。【原文：U.S. Steel shareholders have voted to approve the proposed $14.9 billion acquisition by Japan's Nippon Steel , taking the merger one step closer towards completion even as political opposition to the deal mounts, Bloomberg News reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/us-steel-shareholders-approve-149-bln-buyout-by-nippon-steel-bloomberg-reports-2024-04-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AVBPMRHMWJK5NF74D3OSTMNS3E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 17:34:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高法院裁定，公司对有影响的趋势保持沉默不构成证券欺诈]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最高法院周五裁定，如果公司无视要求披露预计会影响公司底线的趋势的规定，股东不能以欺诈为由起诉公司，除非这种遗漏会使另一份声明具有误导性。【原文：Shareholders cannot sue companies for fraud if they flout a rule requiring disclosure of trends expected to affect their bottom line unless the omission makes another statement misleading, the U.S. Supreme Court ruled on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/corporate-silence-impactful-trends-not-securities-fraud-us-supreme-court-rules-2024-04-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6FEPB2VZZROXBKUCMUEBXZT7Z4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 17:01:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[UAW 对沃尔沃墨西哥工厂的决定 "极为失望]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国汽车工人联合会（UAW）周五表示，对卡车制造商沃尔沃集团在墨西哥建立新卡车工厂的决定 "极为失望"。【原文：The United Auto Workers (UAW) said on Friday it is "extremely disappointed" with truck maker Volvo Group's decision to set up a new truck plant in Mexico, which the company said would help supplement its U.S. production.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/uaw-extremely-disappointed-with-volvos-mexico-plant-decision-2024-04-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RM2T6QDVBNLRJELMAUTC76UIDQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 15:23:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联合信贷银行投资者支持 Orcel 的新任期，并支持加薪]]></title><description><![CDATA[联合信贷银行股东周五投票决定，再授予首席执行官 Andrea Orcel 三年任期，并支持使其成为欧洲薪酬最高银行家之一的薪酬政策。【原文：UniCredit shareholders on Friday voted to give CEO Andrea Orcel another three-year mandate and backed the remuneration policy that makes him one of Europe's best-paid bankers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/unicredit-investors-back-new-term-orcel-support-pay-rise-2024-04-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SMLHHBJ5UBKMDLMHLB2PORHJRA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 15:15:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国最高法院允许众多运输工人回避仲裁]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，美国最高法院支持了一名送货卡车司机的诉讼请求，即扩大州际贸易中免于法律纠纷强制仲裁的雇员范围，使其不局限于运输公司的工人。【原文：The U.S. Supreme Court on Friday gave a boost to a delivery truck driver's bid to expand the universe of employees in interstate commerce who are exempted from mandatory arbitration of legal disputes beyond workers at transportation companies.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-supreme-court-throws-out-ruling-arbitration-job-disputes-2024-04-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZQBOIHCPZBPHZPMDCB4XLRRPFY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 14:30:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 4 月消费者信心指数下滑；通胀预期上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的一项调查显示，美国消费者情绪在4月份有所回落，而对未来12个月及以后的通胀预期则有所上升。【原文：U.S. consumer sentiment ebbed in April while inflation expectations for the next 12 months and beyond increased, a survey showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-consumer-sentiment-slips-april-inflation-expectations-rise-2024-04-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SNSP3JQAL5LELJMLXTMCWZUV7U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 14:22:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道受伊朗相关新制裁影响，俄罗斯石油和产品被困油轮]]></title><description><![CDATA[伦敦证交所集团（LSEG）周五的数据显示，在美国对四艘油轮实施与伊朗有关的新制裁后，俄罗斯的石油和产品被困在海上。【原文：Russian oil and products have become trapped at sea on four tankers after the United States hit the vessels with fresh Iran-related sanctions, LSEG data showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/russian-oil-products-trapped-tankers-hit-by-new-iran-related-sanctions-2024-04-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GYRT4TXRR5LRRFUVS6GXXY3RNA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 14:00:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[降息希望破灭，美国股票基金资金外流]]></title><description><![CDATA[在截至 4 月 10 日的七天内，美国股票基金连续第二周出现资金外流，原因是在近期通胀和美国就业数据强劲之后，投资者权衡了美联储将利率维持在更高水平的可能性。【原文：U.S. equity funds witnessed outflows for a second successive week in the seven days to April 10 as investors weighed the possibility of the Federal Reserve keeping rates higher for longer following recent robust readings on inflation and U.S. payrolls.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-equity-funds-see-outflows-rate-cut-hopes-fade-2024-04-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZIGYZB3CMVJVPMX4GK3UOVEDW4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 13:30:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Roku 称超过 50 万个账户受到网络攻击影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[流媒体服务提供商 Roku 周五表示，继今年早些时候披露 1.5 万个用户账户受到未经授权的访问后，该公司已发现第二次网络攻击，约有 57.6 万个账户受到影响。【原文：Streaming service provider Roku said on Friday it has identified a second cyber attack that impacted about 576,000 accounts, after disclosing unauthorized access of 15,000 user accounts earlier this year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/roku-says-more-than-500000-accounts-impacted-by-cyber-attack-2024-04-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DH72KLEVGFOFFFD7A4E62KLICE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 13:24:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[耐克老板计划投入 "最大 "奥运营销费用]]></title><description><![CDATA[耐克公司高层周五表示，耐克将在本届奥运会上投入比以往任何一届奥运会都要多的资金，这家美国运动服装品牌正着手进行市场推广，希望借此重振萎靡不振的销售业绩，并与后起之秀展开竞争。【原文：Nike is spending more on this Olympics than any previous Games, top executives said on Friday, as the U.S. sportswear brand embarks on a marketing push it hopes will revive flagging sales and help compete with upstart rivals.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/nike-bosses-plan-biggest-olympics-spend-marketing-ramps-up-2024-04-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">47FYB2IWENLM7HQ67IDQWKSFUU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 13:18:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[世界银行总裁在春季会议上推动内部改革]]></title><description><![CDATA[世界银行行长阿贾伊-班加（Ajay Banga）周五表示，他计划在下周强调一系列流程改进措施，以加快发展贷款机构的贷款审批速度，提高其 16000 名员工的责任心，并吸引私人资本参与项目。【原文：World Bank President Ajay Banga said on Friday he plans to highlight a range of process improvements next week to speed up the development lender's loan approvals, improve the accountability of its 16,000 employees and attract private capital to projects.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/world-bank-chief-pushes-internal-reforms-spring-meetings-2024-04-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V4T5IBANR5MTJMVMMATF464SR4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 13:10:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 3 月进口价格连续第三个月上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于能源产品和食品成本上升，3 月份美国进口价格连续第三个月上涨，但基本的进口通胀压力不大。【原文：U.S. import prices increased for a third straight month in March amid rises in the costs of energy products and food, but underlying imported inflation pressures were tame.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-import-prices-post-third-straight-monthly-gain-march-2024-04-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PKGMSWVMZ5NCRHSDUFPMZP4WCY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 13:06:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲与美国的经济差距确实存在，但也有其局限性]]></title><description><![CDATA[正如欧洲央行行长克里斯蒂娜-拉加德（Christine Lagarde）所坚持的那样，欧元区的通货膨胀与美国不同，但该集团仍将面临许多与其他国家相同的不利因素，从而限制物价增长放缓的幅度。【原文：Inflation in the euro zone is different to that in the United States, much as ECB President Christine Lagarde insists, but the bloc will still face many of the same headwinds as others, limiting how far price growth can slow.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/europes-economic-divergence-with-us-is-real-has-its-limits-2024-04-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WWEQT4LLDBISLNCDZLJVUB6U2A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 13:00:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[独家报道OpenAI的Altman向包括部分微软客户在内的大型企业推介ChatGPT企业版]]></title><description><![CDATA[与会者告诉路透社，OpenAI 首席执行官山姆-奥特曼（Sam Altman）本月在旧金山、纽约和伦敦接待了数百名《财富》500 强企业的高管，他和 OpenAI 的其他高管为企业提供了人工智能服务，并在某些情况下与金融支持者微软正面交锋。【原文：OpenAI Chief Executive Sam Altman has hosted hundreds of Fortune 500 company executives in San Francisco, New York and London this month where he and other OpenAI executives pitched AI services for corporate use, going head to head in some cases with financial backer Microsoft, attendees told Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/openais-altman-pitches-chatgpt-enterprise-large-firms-including-some-microsoft-2024-04-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DYTP3KR6CJPI3N25CZWFTBNAFY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 12:33:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[员工遣散费和存款保险成本上升导致花旗利润下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[花旗集团第一季度利润下降，原因是该公司为下岗员工支付了更多的遣散费，并留出资金补充政府存款保险基金。【原文：Citigroup's profit fell in the first quarter as it spent more on severance payments for laid-off employees and set aside money to refill a government deposit insurance fund.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/citi-profit-drops-costs-rise-employee-severance-deposit-insurance-2024-04-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3S74PJSOU5P7TD3KYTKALS6RM4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 12:05:03 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>