<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 02:25:39 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 02:25:39 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[新西兰称扣押了拉美航空波音 787 的黑匣子]]></title><description><![CDATA[新西兰交通事故调查委员会周二表示，在造成 50 多人受伤的事故发生后，该委员会正在扣押拉塔姆航空公司一架波音 787 飞机的驾驶舱语音记录器和飞行数据记录器。【原文：New Zealand's Transport Accident Investigation Commission said on Tuesday it was seizing the cockpit voice recorder and flight data recorder of a LATAM Airlines Boeing 787 after an incident that left more than 50 people injured.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/new-zealand-says-seizing-black-boxes-latam-boeing-787-2024-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WNVCH2EQNRL6NL3CJMJYRTVDQE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 01:51:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美元保持警惕；日本央行的猜测使日元继续受到支撑]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二，在当天晚些时候将公布的美国关键通胀数据公布之前，美元大体持稳，而日元则在一个月高点附近走强，原因是人们对日本央行最早可能在下周退出负利率的预期不断升温。【原文：The dollar held broadly steady on Tuesday ahead of key U.S. inflation data due later in the day, while the yen firmed near a one-month high on mounting expectations the Bank of Japan could exit negative interest rates as early as next week.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/dollar-guard-boj-speculation-keeps-yen-supported-2024-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2Z6R6BWO3ZIGFIDS5BQCDPIHPA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 01:46:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[穆迪启动评级审查，中国万科港股低开 1]]></title><description><![CDATA[穆迪（Moody's）表示，中国万科的房地产公司评级将被考虑降至垃圾级后，该公司股价周二在香港开盘下跌了 1%。【原文：China Vanke's shares are have opened down 1% in Hong Kong on Tuesday after Moody's said the property company's rating would now be considered for junk status.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/china-vankes-hong-kong-shares-open-1-lower-after-moodys-starts-ratings-review-2024-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PDQUYX2EJFMF5BQWJR6MBAQEOE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 01:40:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Blackwells 称迪士尼未披露 ValueAct 的资金管理职责]]></title><description><![CDATA[Blackwells Capital 周一表示，华特迪士尼没有告诉股东 ValueAct Capital Management 投资了这家美国娱乐业巨头超过 3.5 亿美元的养老基金资产，这造成了利益冲突。【原文：Blackwells Capital said on Monday Walt Disney failed to tell shareholders that ValueAct Capital Management had invested more than $350 million of the U.S. entertainment giant's pension fund assets, creating a conflict of interest.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/blackwells-says-disney-failed-disclose-valueacts-money-management-role-2024-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y4M6EX53ZROSJHUCNLQBPKKIVY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 01:01:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约市银行完成 10 亿美元注资交易]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约社区银行（New York Community Bancorp）周一表示，该公司已完成上周与一个投资者团体达成的 10 亿美元注资交易，并计划向股东提交普通股一拆三的反向拆股方案。【原文：New York Community Bancorp said on Monday it had closed the $1 billion capital infusion deal that was agreed last week with an investor group and plans to submit one-for-three reverse stock split of its common stock to shareholders.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/nycb-closes-1-billion-capital-infusion-deal-2024-03-12/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2KF5YXSQ7ZL3RMIDRCFYTTXYFI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:36:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[新西兰航空公司暂停奥克兰至芝加哥直飞航班服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[新西兰航空公司（Air New Zealand）周二表示，由于罗尔斯-罗伊斯公司（Rolls-Royce）的遄达1000（Trent 1000）发动机在可用性方面一直面临挑战，该公司计划从今年3月31日至10月25日暂停奥克兰至芝加哥的直飞航线。【原文：Air New Zealand said on Tuesday it plans to pause its Auckland to Chicago non-stop service from March 31 to Oct. 25 this year due to ongoing challenges with the availability of serviceable Rolls-Royce Trent 1000 engines.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/air-new-zealand-pauses-auckland-chicago-non-stop-service-2024-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3MO7P5N2ONMMBFC4Y7WWW3XQXM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 23:15:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国法官将于 8 月 26 日审理联邦贸易委员会对克罗格阿尔伯森交易的质疑]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦地区法官阿德里安娜-尼尔森（Adrienne Nelson）周一将 8 月 26 日定为美国联邦贸易委员会（Federal Trade Commission）申请初步禁令的听证会开始日，该禁令旨在阻止连锁超市克罗格（Kroger）斥资 246 亿美元收购较小竞争对手阿尔伯森（Albertsons）的交易。【原文：U.S. District Judge Adrienne Nelson on Monday set Aug. 26 as the start of a hearing on the Federal Trade Commission's bid for a preliminary injunction to block supermarket chain Kroger's $24.6 billion deal to buy smaller rival Albertsons .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/us-judge-hear-ftc-challenge-kroger-albertsons-deal-aug-26-2024-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4OHNZLTNBBIVVEIRGX6KQ4QTLM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 23:14:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔格林就纽约对其抬高婴儿配方奶粉价格的指控达成和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约州总检察长莱蒂娅-詹姆斯（Letitia James）指控沃尔格林在雅培实验室召回导致全国范围内婴儿配方奶粉短缺后，于 2022 年严重抬高了至少 20 种婴儿配方奶粉的价格，沃尔格林已就这一指控达成和解。【原文：Walgreens has settled charges by New York Attorney General Letitia James that the pharmacy chain grossly inflated prices on at least 20 infant formula products in 2022 after a recall by Abbott Labs led to a nationwide shortage.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/walgreens-settles-new-york-charges-it-inflated-prices-infant-formula-2024-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QEVHHOZS5ZKV7J45HVFEQI7PEA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 21:51:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞价：股市再次走低，印度CPI即将公布]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚洲市场前瞻【原文：A look at the day ahead in Asian markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/global-markets-view-asia-graphic-pix-2024-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TCRORBU7QJL4XL55XLSCAPWYLE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 21:48:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[泰森食品公司将关闭拥有 1200 名工人的爱荷华州猪肉工厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[泰森食品公司（Tyson Foods）周一表示，将永久关闭位于爱荷华州佩里（Perry）的一家猪肉工厂，届时将裁员约 1200 人。【原文：Tyson Foods will permanently close a pork plant in Perry, Iowa, the meatpacker said on Monday, eliminating jobs for about 1,200 workers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/tyson-foods-close-iowa-pork-plant-with-1200-workers-2024-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2TNC76K3RZK47HJEMABQU6AUSA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 21:04:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社报道，默多克的新闻集团希望与竞争对手联合竞购《每日电讯报]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周一援引知情人士的话报道，鲁珀特-默多克（Rupert Murdoch）的新闻集团和《每日邮报》的所有者已经就阿联酋支持的投资基金 RedBird IMI 联合收购《每日电讯报》的可能性进行了谈判。【原文：Rupert Murdoch's News Corp and the owner of the Daily Mail have held talks about a potential joint takeover of the Telegraph alongside the UAE-backed investment fund RedBird IMI, Bloomberg News reported on Monday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/murdochs-news-corp-eyes-joint-telegraph-bid-with-rivals-bloomberg-news-reports-2024-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NOTQNK3REZNBHLQ7X5FU2A2W4M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 20:46:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[甲骨文季度营收不及预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[甲骨文公司周一公布的第三季度营收不及预期，原因是经济前景不明朗和云计算行业的激烈竞争影响了对其服务的需求。【原文：Oracle missed third-quarter revenue estimates on Monday, as an uncertain economic outlook and strong competition in the cloud-computing industry weighed on demand for its services.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/oracle-misses-quarterly-revenue-estimates-2024-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5SIWLEFC6VO4BDBBFI5LMTBT5Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 20:18:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国运输部长希望波音在 737 MAX 调查中与司法部和 NTSB 合作]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国运输部长皮特-巴蒂吉格（Pete Buttigieg）周一表示，他希望波音公司能配合司法部和国家运输安全委员会对阿拉斯加航空公司737 MAX 9型客机1月5日空中紧急事故的调查。【原文：U.S. Transportation Secretary Pete Buttigieg said Monday he expects Boeing to cooperate in investigations by the Justice Department and National Transportation Safety Board into the Alaska Airlines 737 MAX 9 mid-air emergency on Jan. 5.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-transport-chief-expects-boeing-cooperate-with-doj-ntsb-737-max-probes-2024-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HC363E5MXNPVPLSN7YQTZJYIPY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 20:03:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[福特在美国进口关税逃税案中支付 3.65 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[福特汽车公司将支付 3.65 亿美元，以解决美国指控其违反联邦关税法，对数十万辆 Transit Connect 汽车进行错误分类并低报价值的问题。【原文：Ford Motor will pay $365 million to resolve U.S. allegations it violated a federal tariff law by misclassifying and understating the value of hundreds of thousands of its Transit Connect vehicles.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-pay-365-million-us-import-tariff-evasion-case-2024-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I57JCIPNMRKHVGP72I75YYCWC4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 19:53:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，道达尔能源公司德克萨斯炼油厂因泄漏关闭了 CDU 和焦化装置]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉工厂运营情况的人士周一表示，道达尔能源公司（TotalEnergies）位于得克萨斯州阿瑟港的日产 23.8 万桶炼油厂的汽油生产流化催化裂化装置（FCC）发生泄漏，导致焦化装置和小型原油蒸馏装置（CDU）关闭。【原文：The coker and small crude distillation unit (CDU) were shut by a leak on the gasoline-producing fluidic catalytic cracker (FCC) at TotalEnergies' 238,000 barrel-per-day (bpd) Port Arthur, Texas, refinery, people familiar with plant operations said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/cdu-coker-shut-by-leak-totalenergies-texas-refinery-sources-say-2024-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NZ4UCVSFDRIIBM5OR4IKXVFWHM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 19:17:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国央行曼恩：通胀压力要与 2% 的目标保持一致还有很长的路要走]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国央行政策制定者之一凯瑟琳-曼（Catherine Mann）周一表示，英国要使通胀压力符合英国央行 2% 的目标，还有很长的路要走。【原文：Britain has a long way to go for inflation pressures to be consistent with the Bank of England's 2% target, one of the central bank's policymakers, Catherine Mann, said on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/boes-mann-long-way-inflation-pressures-be-consistent-with-2-target-2024-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5MSRXVYK4BJURBKN63XXEDLT7Q</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:41:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国通胀数据公布后，期权参与者已为市场波动做好准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[周二将公布可能左右美联储货币政策走向的通胀数据，在此之前，美国股票期权市场的交易员们已经开始变得畏首畏尾。【原文：Traders in the U.S. equity options market have grown skittish ahead of Tuesday's release of inflation data that could sway the Federal Reserve's monetary policy trajectory.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/options-players-ready-market-swings-after-us-inflation-data-2024-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">RTVP6KXEEBPNDPZYTWZWON46E4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:38:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛策略师称，美国股市和科技股的市场主导地位日益增强]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛集团（Goldman Sachs）的策略师认为，全球股市越来越集中，包括美国股票和科技股的比重越来越大，虽然不一定没有必要，但可能需要进行一些分散。【原文：Global stock markets are increasingly concentrated, including a greater weight of U.S. equities and technology stocks, and, while not necessarily unwarranted, could call for some diversification, according to Goldman Sachs strategists.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us-equities-tech-growing-market-dominance-goldman-strategists-say-2024-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XNYMONXTUFNARB43KN6IUYXLCA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 17:01:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高超音速武器初创公司 Castelion 首次进行完整武器测试]]></title><description><![CDATA[试图为五角大楼制造高超音速武器的初创公司Castelion周一告诉路透社，它首次测试了自己的系统，越来越多的小型高超音速武器制造商正以成本更低、生产更快的产品挑战大型国防承包商。【原文：Castelion, a startup trying to build a hypersonic weapon for the Pentagon, told Reuters on Monday it tested its system for the first time, as a growing group of small hypersonic arms makers challenge large defense contractors with less expensive, rapidly produced products.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/hypersonic-weapon-startup-castelion-has-first-full-weapon-test-2024-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NNI2HAB4WZKI3GNBGB2Y6NFAP4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 17:01:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员：纽约立法者再次解决主权债务重修问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约州立法机构正在进行另一项简化主权债务重组解决方案的尝试，华尔街再次注意到了这一点。【原文：Another attempt to streamline the resolution of sovereign debt restructurings is making its way through the New York State legislature, and Wall Street is again taking note.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/new-york-lawmakers-tackle-sovereign-debt-reworks-again-2024-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4I2F4LBK5BK77E53PO24SXWXL4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 16:51:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[迪士尼攻击投资者纳尔逊-佩尔茨的动机和资质]]></title><description><![CDATA[华特迪士尼周一在一段视频中回应了亿万富翁纳尔逊-佩尔茨（Nelson Peltz）和他的特里亚基金（Trian Fund）为赢得两个董事会席位而发起的竞选活动，该视频攻击了激进股东的动机和资格。【原文：Walt Disney responded on Monday to billionaire Nelson Peltz and his Trian Fund's campaign to win two board seats in a video that attacks the activist shareholder's motivations and qualifications.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/disney-attacks-investor-nelson-peltzs-motivations-qualifications-2024-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P3ENMQHKO5LVTERW5JQRNAPCZ4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 15:58:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普称 TikTok 是一种威胁，但表示如果没有它，一些孩子可能会 "发疯]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统候选人唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）周一表示，TikTok 是对国家安全的威胁，但他同时也表示，禁止这一流行应用会伤害一些孩子，只会加强 Meta Platforms 的 Facebook，而共和党人曾严厉批评过 Facebook。【原文：U.S. presidential candidate Donald Trump said on Monday TikTok was a national security threat but also said a ban on the popular app would hurt some kids and only strengthen Meta Platforms' Facebook, which the Republican has harshly criticized.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/tiktok-us-security-threat-says-trump-similar-facebook-cnbc-2024-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EJIHHQ2WF5PHFAYDBXBYZ2IGG4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 15:09:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[纽约联储：消费者对长期通胀的展望在 2 月份受阻]]></title><description><![CDATA[纽约联邦储备银行周一发布报告称，2月份公众对长期通胀轨迹的预期有所恶化。【原文：The public’s expectations around the longer-run trajectory of inflation deteriorated in February, a report from the Federal Reserve Bank of New York said Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/ny-fed-consumer-outlook-longer-term-inflation-hit-snag-february-2024-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">74KMNHQRGBLSRIYSPO3MDLGJ7M</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 15:03:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟成员国批准稀释后的临时工权利规则草案]]></title><description><![CDATA[本周一，欧洲向给予 Uber 和 Deliveroo 等在线平台的所谓 "零工经济 "工人更多的社会和劳工权利迈进了一步，尽管这些公司表示，在这些被淡化的规则下，几乎不会有什么变化。【原文：Europe moved a step closer to giving so-called gig economy workers at online platforms such as Uber and Deliveroo greater social and labour rights on Monday, although companies said little would change under the watered-down rules.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/eu-countries-back-draft-rules-gig-workers-rights-2024-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TIEUFV4EDRJTLNBLCRGO3OBNU4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 14:53:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储将于 6 月开始降息；今年降息的风险较小：路透调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社最新民意调查显示，绝大多数经济学家认为，美国联邦储备委员会将在 6 月份下调其关键利率，因为该央行正在等待更多数据来确认通胀率是否正令人信服地朝着 2% 的目标迈进。【原文：The U.S. Federal Reserve will cut its key interest rate in June, according to a stronger majority of economists in the latest Reuters poll, as the central bank waits for more data to confirm whether inflation is headed convincingly toward its 2% target.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/fed-start-rate-cuts-june-risk-fewer-delivered-this-year-2024-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5Y3HXXRSDNIFZCJQTKCBK6VUXQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 14:47:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谁是 OpenAI 的新董事会成员？]]></title><description><![CDATA[山姆-奥特曼（Sam Altman）将与三位新董事一起重新加入 ChatGPT 制造商 OpenAI 的董事会，这家初创公司正试图摆脱他在 11 月突然下台这一震惊科技界的事件。【原文：Sam Altman is rejoining the board of ChatGPT-maker OpenAI along with three new directors, as the startup tries to move past his sudden ouster in November that had shocked the tech industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/who-are-openais-new-board-members-2024-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KTI2JEWHCJONRL5AZWCSBBSAHE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 14:45:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国石油产量连续六年居全球首位--EIA]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源信息署（EIA）周一发布消息称，美国原油产量连续第六年领跑全球石油产量，日均产量达到 1290 万桶（bpd），打破了历史纪录。【原文：U.S. crude oil production lead global oil production for a sixth straight year, with a record breaking average production of 12.9 million barrels per day (bpd), the Energy Information Administration (EIA) said in a release on Monday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/us-leads-global-oil-production-sixth-straight-year-eia-2024-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V3UMBU6FCROWRHSVIRTMYXZGFU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 14:29:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧佩克与国际能源署在石油需求问题上的分歧至少是 2008 年以来最大的一次]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据路透社的研究，欧佩克（OPEC）生产国集团和国际能源机构（International Energy Agency）--世界上最受关注的石油需求增长预测机构--在对燃料使用的看法上的分歧比至少 16 年前更大了。【原文：Producer group OPEC and the International Energy Agency, the world's most closely watched forecasters of oil demand growth, are further apart than they have been for at least 16 years in their views on fuel use, according to Reuters research.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/opec-iea-most-divided-oil-demand-since-least-2008-2024-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">O3X3VEZJSNNQPMCSWKKS42PHOI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 14:29:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汇丰将在美国招聘近 50 名银行家为初创企业和风险企业提供贷款服务]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一位高级管理人员透露，汇丰银行正计划在其美国商业银行增聘约 50 名银行家，为初创公司提供贷款，这些公司主要集中在科技和医疗保健领域。【原文：HSBC is planning to recruit about 50 more bankers in its U.S. commercial bank to lend to startup companies, mainly in the technology and healthcare sectors, according to a senior executive.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/hsbc-hire-almost-50-bankers-startup-venture-lending-us-2024-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HUACNWZCL5PNHISZLWCLPVLRTM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 13:04:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西 2 月月度通胀率预测为一年来最高 路透社调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社的一项民意调查显示，巴西的月通胀率在 2 月份可能加速上升至一年来的最高点，由于农产品供应充足和经济形势疲软，未来几个月的通胀率应该会从这一水平开始回落。【原文：Brazil's monthly inflation rate likely accelerated to a one-year high in February, a Reuters poll found, from where it should begin to fall back again in coming months due to abundant supplies of farm products and softer economic conditions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/brazil-feb-monthly-inflation-forecast-one-year-high-2024-03-11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z4RYI6KNIVO2PAZQ22VFUCEBFE</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 12:09:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>