<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 04:24:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 04:24:49 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[中国计划制定新的市场准入规则：李总理致全球首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国国务院总理李强周日对全球首席执行官和中国政策制定者表示，中国将认真研究市场准入和跨境数据流动问题，并将很快在这些领域出台新的法规。【原文：China will carefully study issues of market access and cross-border data flows and will soon issue new regulations in these areas, Premier Li Qiang told an audience of global CEOs and Chinese policymakers on Sunday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-plans-new-rules-market-access-data-flows-premier-li-tells-global-ceos-2024-03-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MVLXVBDNBVKPXAA5DG7MEMKDGA</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 02:51:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[全球监管机构将矛头指向科技公司，谷歌和苹果的分手已提上日程]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着大西洋两岸的反垄断监管机构严厉打击涉嫌反竞争的行为，大型科技公司正面临数十年来最大的挑战。【原文：Big Tech is facing its biggest challenge in decades as antitrust regulators on both sides of the Atlantic crack down on alleged anti-competitive practices that could result in break-up orders to Apple and Alphabet's Google, a first for the industry.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/google-apple-breakups-agenda-global-regulators-target-tech-2024-03-24/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XRUPTHITLRIDNCPQVWWQZVPRKU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 01:04:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据彭博社报道，在发生安全事故后，美国联邦航空局考虑限制美联航的新航线]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社（Bloomberg News）周六报道，在发生一系列安全事故后，美国联邦航空管理局（Federal Aviation Administration）正在考虑采取措施抑制美国联合航空公司（United Airlines）的增长，包括阻止该航空公司增加新航线。【原文：The U.S. Federal Aviation Administration is considering measures to curb growth at United Airlines , including preventing the carrier from adding new routes, following a series of safety incidents, Bloomberg News reported on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-faa-weighs-curbing-new-routes-united-after-safety-incidents-bloomberg-reports-2024-03-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7K7O27KJHVINNPGQYR3NMEWBE4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 17:41:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[德国风电行业欢迎政府为离岸码头提供资金]]></title><description><![CDATA[德国海上风能基金会表示，政府决定资助一个海上码头的扩建，这对实现海上风能的扩建目标非常重要。【原文：The German Offshore Wind Energy Foundation said the government's decision to help fund the expansion of an offshore terminal is important to achieve expansion goals for wind energy at sea.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/german-wind-power-sector-welcomes-government-offshore-terminal-funding-2024-03-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CWF3GIJW4JPUFFX4Z3KQ6HEYZM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 12:06:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[联邦调查局告诉阿拉斯加航空公司 737 MAX 9 乘客他们可能是犯罪受害者]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社看到的信件称，美国联邦调查局已告知阿拉斯加航空公司一架波音737 MAX 9客机上的乘客，他们可能是一起犯罪的受害者。【原文：The U.S. Federal Bureau of Investigation has told passengers who were on an Alaska Airlines Boeing 737 MAX 9 that suffered a Jan. 5 mid-air emergency that they may be victims of a crime, according to letters seen by Reuters.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/fbi-tells-alaska-airlines-737-max-9-passengers-they-may-be-crime-victims-2024-03-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HMXQBI34M5MENBHRRBUN3QLFTA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 03:51:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[天齐公司在智利 SQM-Codelco 锂交易中寻求股东投票权]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国天齐锂业公司周五敦促智利SQM公司就正在与国营铜矿商Codelco讨论的锂交易举行股东投票，并批评谈判缺乏明确性。【原文：China's Tianqi Lithium Corp on Friday urged Chile's SQM to hold a shareholders vote over a lithium deal under discussion with state-run copper miner Codelco, and criticized a lack of clarity in the negotiations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/tianqi-seeks-shareholder-voting-power-chiles-sqm-codelco-lithium-deal-2024-03-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T6QOBJO24FOQ5HJSHVM7NHUV74</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 01:28:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[为什么我需要一个全黑人演员阵容？迪士尼批评佩尔茨的言论]]></title><description><![CDATA[华特迪士尼公司（Walt Disney Co）周五表示，激进投资者纳尔逊-佩尔茨（Nelson Peltz）批评该公司拍摄以女性和黑人演员为主的电影的言论，证明他不应该进入迪士尼董事会。【原文：Walt Disney Co on Friday said that remarks by activist investor Nelson Peltz criticizing the company for making movies dominated by female and Black actors is evidence that he shouldn't be on Disney's board.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/lifestyle/disney-criticizes-peltz-remarks-about-casting-black-panther-the-marvels-2024-03-23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PGVKGOSZN5NDBNRMP5EFN5KHOE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 00:07:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[鸽派美联储提振美国股市涨势]]></title><description><![CDATA[令人欣慰的经济前景和美联储发出的鸽派信号正鼓励投资者将目光投向过去一年推动美国股市上涨的大型成长股和科技股之外。【原文：A reassuring economic outlook and dovish signals from the Federal Reserve are encouraging investors to look beyond the massive growth and technology stocks that have fueled the U.S. stock market’s gains over the past year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-st-week-ahead-broadening-us-market-rally-gets-boost-dovish-fed-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HY4CCC5SKVIUHL5RIJB7ZKNKEA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 22:47:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[近期事件发生后，美国联邦航空局将加强对美国联合航空公司的审查]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联合航空公司周五晚些时候表示，在最近发生一系列安全事故后，联邦安全监管部门将在未来几周内加强对该航空公司的审查。【原文：United Airlines said late on Friday that federal safety regulators will boost scrutiny of the airline in the next several weeks after a series of recent safety incidents.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/faa-step-up-scrutiny-united-airlines-after-recent-incidents-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DM6GMLCZK5NITNMDUD47UUREFQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 22:35:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席博斯蒂克将年内降息幅度由之前的两次缩减为一次]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚特兰大联邦储备银行行长拉斐尔-博斯蒂克（Raphael Bostic）周五表示，他现在预计今年只会降息四分之一个百分点，而之前预计的降息幅度为两次。【原文：Atlanta Federal Reserve bank President Raphael Bostic said on Friday he now expects just a single quarter-point interest rate cut this year versus two cuts that he had projected previously, a change in his outlook driven by persistent inflation and stronger-than-anticipated economic data.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-bostic-scales-back-single-rate-cut-year-versus-two-previously-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I7YBTHBFO5NFVMGXSXJ2N4HSXA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 22:10:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拜登政府敦促美国最高法院驳回马斯克就 SEC 争议提出的上诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[乔-拜登总统的政府周五敦促美国最高法院驳回亿万富翁、商人埃隆-马斯克（Elon Musk）与美国证券交易委员会（Securities and Exchange Commission）的纠纷。【原文：President Joe Biden's administration on Friday urged the U.S. Supreme Court to turn away billionaire businessman Elon Musk's dispute with the Securities and Exchange Commission.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/biden-administration-urges-us-supreme-court-reject-musk-appeal-sec-dispute-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EDZR54WFGVN67GWF46BGW5UOLE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 21:43:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[B.年度报告延迟后，B. Riley 遭纳斯达克警告]]></title><description><![CDATA[精品投资银行 B. Riley Financial 周五在一份声明中说，纳斯达克已通知 B. Riley Financial 由于延迟提交年度报告而不符合该交易所的上市规则。【原文：Nasdaq has notified B. Riley Financial of non-compliance with the exchange operator's listing rules due to a delay in the filing of its annual report, the boutique investment bank said in a statement on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/b-riley-gets-nasdaq-warning-after-annual-report-delay-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WGH6WHVH7FI4VMHVGDDRDXCI74</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 21:21:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[UnitedHealth 称单位变更时处理医疗报销的几项服务将上线]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联合健康集团（UnitedHealth Group）周五表示，继上月发生黑客攻击事件后，预计该公司旗下的 Change Healthcare 将在未来几周内逐步上线几项与处理医疗索赔相关的服务。【原文：UnitedHealth Group said on Friday it expects several services related to handling medical claims by its unit Change Healthcare to gradually be online over the next few weeks following a hack last month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/cybersecurity/unitedhealth-says-several-services-handling-medical-claims-unit-change-will-go-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Y56ARCBV6FI3VCQAIRHC5CGDTE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 19:47:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[H&M 新老板埃尔弗面临重启销售的战斗]]></title><description><![CDATA[H&amp;M 新任首席执行官丹尼尔-埃尔弗（Daniel Erver）将于本周三公布其领导下的首份季度财报，投资者希望他能再次保证，他制定了重新启动收入增长的正确计划。【原文：Investors will be looking for reassurances from new H&amp;M CEO Daniel Erver that he has the right plan to reboot revenue growth when the fast fashion retailer reports its first quarterly earnings under his leadership on Wednesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/hms-new-boss-erver-faces-battle-reboot-sales-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MFGUXJBYORP6VGQAT7ESTBE4BQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 19:46:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[洛兹敦汽车公司前首席执行官与美国证券交易委员会就声明达成和解]]></title><description><![CDATA[Lordstown Motors Corp 前首席执行官斯蒂芬-伯恩斯（Stephen Burns）周五与美国证券交易委员会（U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission）达成和解，原因是他曾就电动汽车制造商旗舰卡车 Endurance 的需求发表过言论。【原文：Ex-Lordstown Motors Corp CEO Stephen Burns settled with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission on Friday over his statements about demand for the electric vehicle maker's flagship truck, the Endurance.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/sec-sues-ex-lordstown-motors-ceo-over-merger-statements-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ODIRIWYHCBO7JHSPMRMXVGYHDA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 19:43:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Chick-fil-A 撤回无抗生素鸡肉承诺]]></title><description><![CDATA[Chick-fil-A 宣布允许在鸡肉中使用某些抗生素，推翻了它在 2014 年做出的承诺。【原文：Chick-fil-A announced it is allowing certain antibiotics in its chicken, overturning a commitment it made in 2014.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/chick-fil-a-rolls-back-commitment-antibiotic-free-chicken-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">73PCBSD5RNIQFFSNYZ2ATAVGCM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 19:28:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[沃尔玛支持的技术公司 Ibotta 申请在美国上市]]></title><description><![CDATA[沃尔玛支持的 Ibotta 科技公司在周五提交的一份文件中说，该公司已申请在美国上市。【原文：Walmart-backed Ibotta has filed to go public in the United States, the technology company said in a filing on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/walmart-backed-technology-firm-ibotta-files-go-public-us-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HCZXMLXIMVLKPMFZETK56XRDMI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 19:27:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ELFA 称，2 月份美国商业设备借款增长 4]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国设备租赁与融资协会（ELFA）周五称，与一年前相比，2月份美国公司的设备投资融资借贷增加了4%。【原文：U.S. companies borrowed 4% more to finance equipment investments in February compared to a year ago, industry body Equipment Leasing and Finance Association (ELFA) said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-business-equipment-borrowings-up-4-february-elfa-says-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7ATKNQDNUNOLDK35LZUCWGMXXI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 19:03:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行丹观调查显示第一季度制造商乐观情绪略有下降，服务业有所改善 - 路透社调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周五对经济学家进行的一项调查显示，由于一些汽车生产中断，日本制造商的商业乐观情绪在第一季度可能略有下降，但服务业景气进一步改善、【原文：Business optimism among Japanese manufacturers likely eased slightly in the first quarter due to some auto production disruptions, but service-sector sentiment improved further, a Reuters poll of economists showed on Friday,】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/japan/boj-tankan-show-q1-manufacturers-optimism-eased-slightly-services-improved-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IZ3C4ES3WFKXXGVQ3LSOLQSSJA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 18:59:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊就法国监管机构有关员工监控的 3460 万美元罚款提出上诉]]></title><description><![CDATA[电子商务巨头亚马逊公司（Amazon.com）周五表示，已就法国监管机构 CNIL 对该公司处以 3200 万欧元（约合 3458 万美元）罚款的决定提出上诉。【原文：E-commerce giant Amazon.com said on Friday it has appealed French regulator CNIL's decision to fine the company 32 million euros ($34.58 million) for setting up a system to monitor employee activity and performance.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/amazon-appeals-346-mln-fine-by-french-regulator-over-staff-monitoring-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AFY36DJQJ5PM3HTSU56ZLF7MSE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 18:34:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[解说员美国对苹果公司的诉讼可能会让 iPhone 的使用体验更贴近消费者]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国已对苹果公司提起诉讼，目的是加强 iPhone 的竞争，并为那些其应用程序可与无处不在的设备配合使用的小公司提供有利条件。【原文：The U.S. has filed a lawsuit against Apple with the aim of increasing competition for the iPhone and giving a leg up to smaller companies whose apps work with the ubiquitous device.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-lawsuit-against-apple-could-make-iphone-experience-more-consumer-friendly-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3ZHG2PEKJBNSNAGEYUNUBNWUDY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 18:01:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ASML 供应商 Neways 将在马来西亚新建工厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[荷兰计算机芯片设备制造商 ASML 的主要供应商 Neways 周五表示，它将在马来西亚巴生新建一座工厂。【原文：Neways, a key supplier to Dutch computer chip equipment maker ASML , said on Friday it will build a new plant in Klang, Malaysia.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/asml-supplier-neways-build-new-plant-malaysia-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EV7V4JL4KJIKFIH7LQLY2GJ22M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 17:55:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[绿街公司称，美国办公室占用率面临远程办公的 "黑洞]]></title><description><![CDATA[房地产分析公司 Green Street 表示，远程办公已造成美国办公室占用率的 "黑洞"，使需求大大低于大流行前的水平，空置率降至历史最低点，多年内都不可能恢复到以前的使用率。【原文：Remote work has caused a "black hole" in U.S. office occupancy, knocking demand significantly below pre-pandemic levels and vacancy rates to historic lows, with a recovery to prior usage unlikely for years, said real estate analysis firm Green Street.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-office-occupancy-faces-black-hole-remote-work-says-green-street-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NTNE6PCR3RJTDGPEZ65BW44Y6I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 16:59:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报纸称加拿大监管机构将为高负债借款人设定抵押贷款上限]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《环球邮报》周五报道，加拿大银行业监管机构正在限制银行住宅抵押贷款组合中高杠杆贷款的数量，这些贷款随着房价的上涨而膨胀，使加拿大借款人成为世界上负债最多的国家之一。【原文：Canada's banking regulator is limiting the number of highly leveraged loans in banks' residential mortgage portfolios, which have ballooned alongside house prices to make Canadian borrowers among the most indebted in the world, the Globe and Mail reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/canada-banking-regulator-cap-mortgages-highly-indebted-borrowers-newspaper-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HB6A6G6YHZLSJNFHVDYSWU7FMM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 16:36:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[尽管欧盟采取了安全行动，马士基仍将避开红海]]></title><description><![CDATA[航运公司马士基周五表示，尽管欧盟倡议加强红海地区的安全，但由于风险水平持续升高，恢复红海航线为时尚早。【原文：Shipping company Maersk said on Friday it was too early to resume sailings through the Red Sea due to a continued elevated risk level, despite an initiative by the European Union to increase safety in the region.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/maersk-will-avoid-red-sea-despite-eu-security-operation-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4JT3HT5UABO3LA6HUNCVWDU73Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 16:29:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[克莱斯勒母公司 Stellantis 在美国裁员约 400 人]]></title><description><![CDATA[克莱斯勒母公司斯特兰蒂斯公司周五表示，在努力削减成本、提高效率和加强电动汽车生产计划的同时，该公司将裁减约 400 名美国工人。【原文：Chrysler-parent Stellantis said Friday it will lay off about 400 U.S. workers as it works to cut costs, boost efficiency and ramp up electric vehicle production plans.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/chrysler-parent-stellantis-laying-off-about-400-us-workers-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5YXYEJGIGVMHFITNSORSAMWPBQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 16:20:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国称盖茨支持的反应堆公司的计划申请需要改进]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国监管机构本周告诉一家由比尔-盖茨创立的核电公司，该公司计划为一座高科技反应堆申请施工许可，但还需要做更多的工作。【原文：U.S. regulators this week told a nuclear power company founded by Bill Gates that its planned construction permit application for a high-tech reactor needs more work, an issue that a critic of the technology said could delay development of the plant in Wyoming.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/us-says-gates-backed-reactor-companys-planned-application-needs-work-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YHGUISSXBROFVK2OWBBA7UIFWU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 16:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[银行家称欧洲首次公开募股（IPO）市场受挫，但仍在复苏过程中]]></title><description><![CDATA[银行家们说，在德国零售商道格拉斯（Douglas）上市后一天，瑞士护肤品公司 Galderma 周五的强势上市稳定了欧洲 IPO 市场的神经。【原文：A strong debut by Swiss skincare company Galderma on Friday is steadying nerves around Europe's IPO market, a day after a poorly received listing from German retailer Douglas , bankers said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/europes-ipo-market-hits-bump-recovery-still-course-bankers-say-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QUDB6QFGJNJU7BVQ2TYG4JJEQ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 14:40:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[利润创纪录后，Zara 商店工人在西班牙商店外举行抗议活动]]></title><description><![CDATA[时尚巨头 Inditex 旗下 Zara、Bershka 和其他服装店的工人周五在西班牙各地的店外举行抗议活动，要求改善条件，此前该集团公布了创纪录的利润并提高了股东报酬。【原文：Workers from Zara, Bershka and other clothing stores owned by fashion giant Inditex protested outside their shops across Spain on Friday to demand better conditions after the group reported record profits and raised shareholder payouts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/zara-shop-workers-protest-outside-spanish-stores-after-record-profit-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">M4FSVBCY2FP6RL4RSKT63L233Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 14:35:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者为特朗普价值 60 亿美元的社交媒体交易开绿灯]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，在一家空头支票收购公司的投资者批准了一项目前价值约 60 亿美元的合作后，美国前总统唐纳德-特朗普距离从其社交媒体公司获得巨额暴利又近了一步。【原文：Former U.S. President Donald Trump came a step closer on Friday to reaping a major windfall from his social media firm after investors in a blank-check acquisition company approved a tie-up currently worth about $6 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/investors-greenlight-trumps-6-billion-social-media-deal-2024-03-22/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">SPZ64RWH6FO63JCFRFJXZ2WEAA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 14:23:25 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>