<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 21:26:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 21:26:38 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，Vanguard 在董事会之争中投票支持迪士尼董事]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士周二透露，华特-迪士尼最大的投资者先锋集团（Vanguard Group）已投票支持该娱乐巨头的所有 12 名董事，帮助该公司在与两家对冲基金（包括纳尔逊-佩尔茨的特里亚基金管理公司（Trian Fund Management））的激烈董事会斗争中取得领先。【原文：Walt Disney's largest investor Vanguard Group has voted to back all of the entertainment giant's 12 directors, helping the company pull ahead in its bitter board-room fight with two hedge funds, including Nelson Peltz's Trian Fund Management, sources said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/vanguard-votes-disney-directors-boardroom-battle-sources-say-2024-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2BQ4YYNUL5KUNAC3VQ6PANEYZA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 21:09:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华盛顿邮报》称，审查委员会将发布报告，详述微软在中国黑客攻击事件中的失误]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华盛顿邮报》周二报道，网络安全审查委员会预计将发布一份报告，详细说明科技巨头微软在去年导致中国黑客有针对性地入侵美国政府高官电子邮件方面的失误。【原文：The Cyber Safety Review Board is expected to issue a report detailing lapses by the tech giant Microsoft that led to a targeted Chinese hack of top U.S. government officials' emails last year, the Washington Post reported on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/review-board-issue-report-detailing-microsofts-lapses-china-hack-washington-post-2024-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QC3VEUZPPJNTJPXWI3E7JPPBZI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:34:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英特尔披露芯片制造部门运营亏损 70 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[半导体公司英特尔周二向美国证券交易委员会（SEC）提交的一份监管文件显示，其代工业务的运营亏损不断增加。【原文：Semiconductor company Intel disclosed increasing operating losses for its foundry business on Tuesday, according to a regulatory filing with the U.S. SEC.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/intel-discloses-financials-foundry-business-2024-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TBL7746BIVIXJPRULZGP2CI6JU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:11:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，白宫对结束液化天然气出口暂停以推动乌克兰援助持开放态度]]></title><description><![CDATA[两位白宫消息人士周二表示，美国官员对结束乔-拜登总统暂停液化天然气出口审批的做法持开放态度，以争取国会通过乌克兰援助方案，但希望在看到整个方案后再做决定。【原文：U.S. officials are open to ending President Joe Biden's pause on approvals of liquefied natural gas exports to get a Ukraine aide package passed in Congress but want to wait to see the entire proposal before making any decisions, two White House sources said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/white-house-open-ending-lng-export-pause-push-ukraine-aid-sources-say-2024-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">AK5CEGJQYROYFBLBNRIWLI34AU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 19:59:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[山姆-班克曼-弗里德检察官称编码员的合作加快了案件进程]]></title><description><![CDATA[其中一名检察官周二表示，美国检察官之所以能在加密货币交易所倒闭后不久起诉 FTX 创始人山姆-班克曼-弗里德（Sam Bankman-Fried），部分原因是他们获得了该交易所首席软件工程师的合作。【原文：U.S. prosecutors were able to charge FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried shortly after the cryptocurrency exchange's collapse in part because they secured the cooperation of its chief software engineer, one of the prosecutors said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/sam-bankman-fried-prosecutor-says-coders-cooperation-sped-up-case-2024-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5A7NOFQPL5OC5PNAQKW7OZPV4I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 19:19:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国钢铁工会拒绝新日铁的收购支持呼吁]]></title><description><![CDATA[代表美国钢铁公司员工的工会周二表示，不会支持日本新日铁公司为收购美国钢铁公司而争取支持的协议草案。【原文：The union representing employees of United States Steel on Tuesday said it would not support Japanese firm Nippon Steel's draft agreement to gain support for its takeover of the U.S. company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/us-steel-union-rejects-nippon-steels-appeal-takeover-support-2024-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZDEXXZNUNBIXLHJZAZZOFY7IZQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 19:16:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞银任命三位高管领导美洲股票资本市场]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞银集团任命了三位银行业资深人士领导其在美国的股票资本市场（ECM）部门，这家全球最大的财富管理公司在去年收购瑞士信贷（Credit Suisse）后，因亏损严重而寻求加强其他部门。【原文：UBS appointed three banking veterans to lead its equity capital markets (ECM) unit in the U.S., as the world's biggest wealth manager looks to ramp up other divisions after its takeover of Credit Suisse last year saddled it with losses.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ubs-appoints-three-executives-lead-americas-equity-capital-markets-2024-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7BVT3ELZ3ROXTGK4IC2ODN6QBQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 19:15:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席戴利称今年降息三次 "合理]]></title><description><![CDATA[旧金山联邦储备银行行长玛丽-戴利（Mary Daly）周二表示，她认为今年降息三次是一个 "合理 "的预期，如果通胀率保持稳定，美联储准备减少降息次数；如果劳动力市场动荡或通胀率下降速度超过预期，美联储准备增加降息次数。
"戴利在内华达州拉斯维加斯举行的一次活动上说："按兵不动是目前正确的政策。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of San Francisco President Mary Daly on Tuesday said she believes three interest-rate cuts this year is a "reasonable" expectation, with the Fed ready to do less if inflation stays sticky or more if the labor market falters or inflation falls faster than anticipated.
"Standing pat is the right policy for the moment," Daly said at an event in Las Vegas, Nevada.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-daly-says-3-rate-cuts-this-year-reasonable-2024-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2AT2K6DD6JMOBF7GK3KSMQMNUQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 19:07:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亲属称司法部将于 4 月 24 日与波音客机失事家庭会面]]></title><description><![CDATA[两架波音 737 MAX 飞机坠毁，造成 346 人死亡，美国司法部计划在政府决定是否继续进行刑事立案调查时，与遇难者家属会面。【原文：The U.S. Justice Department plans to meet with the families of the of the victims of two Boeing 737 MAX crashes that killed 346 people as the government decides whether to move ahead with a criminal case, relatives of the victims said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/justice-department-meet-with-boeing-crash-families-april-24-relatives-say-2024-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">43TJDXJVJVMV3ND47HQ644BYIA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 18:38:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，阿拉巴马州的奔驰工人最快将于本周申请工会投票]]></title><description><![CDATA[三位熟悉内情的人士周二表示，梅赛德斯-奔驰阿拉巴马州装配厂的工人正在努力加入美国汽车工人工会，他们计划最快于本周向美国监管机构提交申请。【原文：Factory workers at Mercedes Benz's assembly plant in Alabama are moving forward with efforts to join the United Auto Workers union, and they plan to file a petition as soon as this week with U.S. regulators, three people familiar with the matter said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/mercedes-workers-alabama-file-union-vote-soon-this-week-sources-say-2024-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FFTR3WXY25IOZKDPROGH6F74R4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 18:29:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博新闻社称霍尼韦尔考虑出售其 COVID 防护装备部门]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博新闻社周二援引知情人士的话报道，霍尼韦尔国际公司正在考虑出售其个人防护设备（PPE）部门，交易价值可能超过 20 亿美元。【原文：Honeywell International is considering selling its personal protective equipment (PPE) division in a deal that could value the unit at more than $2 billion, Bloomberg News reported on Tuesday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/honeywell-considering-selling-its-covid-protective-gear-unit-bloomberg-news-says-2024-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CRV6FM5WPZPBJCZNBGHHXHGVWU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 18:04:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Citadel 旗舰基金第一季度上涨 5.75% -消息来源]]></title><description><![CDATA[据一位熟悉内情的消息人士称，肯-格里芬的对冲基金 Citadel 在第一季度的所有基金策略中都取得了积极的业绩，其中旗舰基金惠灵顿基金的收益率达到 5.75%。【原文：Ken Griffin's hedge fund Citadel capped the first quarter with a positive performance in all its funds strategies, with the flagship Wellington fund posting gains of 5.75%, according to a source familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/citadel-flagship-fund-rose-575-q1-source-2024-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XFWHY3QNLNNMJIVOHN5VWMVGF4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 17:45:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国参议员敦促拜登审查新日铁被指与中国的关系]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国会两党反对新日铁斥资 149 亿美元收购美国钢铁公司（U.S. Steel Corp.），美国参议院银行委员会主席周二以国家安全为由，敦促白宫审查新日铁与中国钢铁业之间的关系。【原文：The head of the U.S. Senate Banking Committee on Tuesday urged the White House to scrutinize the relationship between Nippon Steel and the Chinese steel industry, citing national security concerns amid bipartisan opposition in Congress to the Japanese company's $14.9 billion deal to acquire U.S. Steel Corp .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/us-senator-urges-biden-review-alleged-nippon-steel-ties-china-2024-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">34YPN4QZ4FKL7JYXAZQOTNDR3M</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 17:08:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者希望通用电气分拆上市能打破历来分拆上市的不良记录]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着通用电气公司以 1,919 亿美元完成分拆，看涨的投资者打赌它将打破过去几十年来许多公司分拆后股价表现低迷的局面。【原文：As General Electric completes its $191.9 billion breakup, bullish investors are betting it will defy the lackluster share price performance that has followed many corporate spinoffs over the last few decades.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/investors-hope-ge-spinoff-will-defy-poor-track-record-breakups-2024-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PLOVDWG7ERNSZHYYHEPYYZXOXA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 16:54:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[雅虎收购 Instagram 联合创始人的人工智能新闻平台 Artifact]]></title><description><![CDATA[雅虎周二表示，已收购Instagram联合创始人的人工智能新闻平台Artifact，并将在这家美国网络服务提供商的新闻和其他网站上采用其技术。【原文：Yahoo said on Tuesday it had acquired Instagram co-founders' AI-driven news platform, Artifact, and will incorporate its technology across the U.S. web services provider's news and other sites.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/yahoo-acquires-instagram-co-founders-ai-news-platform-artifact-2024-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5GAESOBCQFNR5CXRCDSLQTBDQU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 16:51:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国与制药公司就医疗保险药品价格谈判迈出下一步]]></title><description><![CDATA[拜登政府周二表示，已对被选中参加美国医疗保险计划首次定价谈判的 10 种高价药生产商的报价做出回应，但未提供详细信息。【原文：The Biden administration said on Tuesday it has responded to offers from the manufacturers of 10 high-cost drugs selected for the U.S. Medicare program's first-ever pricing negotiations, but provided no details.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-takes-next-step-medicare-drug-price-negotiations-with-pharma-companies-2024-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3MTGFXNH5NJ73CIQSRKFYCV5AI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 16:47:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[银湖拟以 130 亿美元的股权交易将 Endeavor 私有化]]></title><description><![CDATA[Endeavor Group Holdings 周二表示，它将被银湖集团（Silver Lake）以 130 亿美元的价格私有化。【原文：Endeavor Group Holdings said on Tuesday it will be taken private by Silver Lake in an equity deal of $13 billion.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/silver-lake-take-endeavor-private-equity-deal-13-bln-2024-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OHFRNZ3YDRNF5FNW7CJJ2HUP7Q</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 16:43:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[古驰前首席执行官比扎里尼成立投资公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[路透社周二看到的文件显示，古驰（Gucci）前高管马可-比扎里（Marco Bizzarri）最近离开了凯灵（Kering）旗下的古驰品牌，并成立了一家新的投资公司。【原文：Former Gucci executive Marco Bizzarri has set up a new investment company after recently leaving the Kering-owned brand, documents seen by Reuters on Tuesday showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/lifestyle/former-gucci-ceo-bizzarri-sets-up-investment-company-2024-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5PE53Q2C35M73JA3ORXKKT6LEE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 16:35:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 FDA 称，礼来公司生产的部分剂量的 Mounjaro 在 4 月份前供应紧张]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国食品和药物管理局网站显示，由于需求激增，礼来公司的四剂糖尿病药物Mounjaro到2024年仍将供应紧张。【原文：Four doses of Eli Lilly's diabetes drug Mounjaro would remain in tight supply through 2024 due to soaring demand, the U.S. Food and Drug Administration's website showed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/some-doses-lillys-mounjaro-tight-supply-through-april-us-fda-says-2024-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LERI5IH5H5ONVDZRO3OZPBBHFA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 16:22:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储梅斯特预计今年降息，但希望在行动前获得更多数据]]></title><description><![CDATA[克利夫兰联邦储备银行行长洛雷塔-梅斯特（Loretta Mester）周二表示，她仍然认为央行有望在今年降息，但仍需要看到数据证实降息是可能的。【原文：Federal Reserve Bank of Cleveland President Loretta Mester said on Tuesday she continues to think the central bank is on track to cut rates this year but still needs to see the data confirm such a move is possible.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-mester-eyes-rate-cuts-this-year-wants-more-data-before-acting-2024-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BBNDFK7A2BKQTJ7BCOQNMJTACM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 16:12:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告称，随着游戏玩家工作时间的减少，个人电脑和游戏机的增长将落后于大流行前的水平]]></title><description><![CDATA[研究公司 Newzoo 的数据显示，由于游戏玩家的游戏时间减少，预计到 2026 年，个人电脑和游戏机的收入增长仍将低于流行前的水平。【原文：Personal computing and console gaming revenue growth is expected to remain below pre-pandemic levels through 2026 as gamers record fewer hours of playtime, according to research firm Newzoo.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/pc-console-growth-lag-pre-pandemic-levels-gamers-clock-fewer-hours-report-says-2024-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VGNEBZQW7BKITN23ETIOXNYPXA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 16:09:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[通用汽车第一季度美国汽车销量下滑 1.5%]]></title><description><![CDATA[通用汽车公司（General Motors）周二公布的第一季度美国汽车销量下降了 1.5%，主要是受商业客户交付量减少的影响。【原文：General Motors on Tuesday reported a 1.5% fall in first-quarter U.S. auto sales, hurt by lower deliveries to commercial customers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/gms-first-quarter-us-auto-sales-slip-15-2024-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VZVARWPUGRMKLLQIPL6SHRCA6U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 16:03:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国财政部部长耶伦重返中国，强调产能过剩威胁]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国财政部周二表示，美国财政部长珍妮特-耶伦（Janet Yellen）将于本周重返中国，继续与中国高层官员进行经济对话，并再次强调亚洲超级大国不断增长的过剩工业产能对全球构成的威胁。【原文：U.S. Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen will return to China this week to continue her economic dialogue with top Chinese officials amid a new emphasis on the global threat posed by the Asian superpower's growing excess industrial capacity, the Treasury Department said on Tuesday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us-treasurys-yellen-return-china-emphasize-excess-capacity-threat-2024-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ZOIJTME7IZP4ZGH74SUYD42V3U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 15:42:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[丰田第一季度美国汽车销量大增 20]]></title><description><![CDATA[丰田汽车北美公司（TMNA）周二公布，受经济型轿车、跨界越野车和皮卡需求的推动，第一季度美国汽车销量增长了约20%。【原文：Toyota Motor North America (TMNA) reported an about 20% rise in first-quarter U.S. auto sales on Tuesday, helped by demand for its affordable sedans, crossovers SUVs and pickup trucks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/toyota-reports-20-jump-first-quarter-us-auto-sales-2024-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GQSXDZW2BBM3RIVDMWLBQLRIXE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 15:35:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[塔吉特购物者数据和流媒体电视广告是其销售的关键]]></title><description><![CDATA[在宝宝打盹时，一位新妈妈正在播放她最喜欢的电视节目，屏幕上突然出现了 Enfamil NeuroPro 婴儿配方奶粉的广告。【原文：While streaming a favorite TV show as her baby naps, an ad for Enfamil NeuroPro infant formula pops on a new mother's screen.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/target-shopper-data-streaming-tv-ads-are-key-its-sales-2024-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IDXQIFN67VNLTCTTY4EYHSXJZY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 14:52:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 2 月份工厂订单稳步增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着制造业重新站稳脚跟，受机械和商用飞机需求的推动，2 月份美国制成品新订单反弹幅度超过预期。【原文：New orders for U.S.-manufactured goods rebounded more than expected in February, boosted by demand for machinery and commercial aircraft as manufacturing regains its footing.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-factory-orders-increase-solidly-february-2024-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KZD2ZUIA2VMKNHJOMTK33G3B3U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 14:44:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 2 月份职位空缺变化不大；辞职人数增加]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国 2 月份的职位空缺保持在较高水平，而辞职人数略有上升。【原文：U.S. job openings held steady at higher levels in February, while the number of people quitting their jobs rose marginally.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-job-openings-little-changed-february-quits-edge-up-2024-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">TWNRIWGLRZNUHHNOGG46VX2VBY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 14:24:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 FDA 批准雅培的心脏瓣膜修复装置]]></title><description><![CDATA[雅培实验室（Abbott Laboratories）周二表示，美国食品和药物管理局（FDA）已批准其心脏瓣膜修复装置，该装置专为在开胸手术中面临并发症或死亡风险的患者设计。【原文：Abbott Laboratories said on Tuesday the U.S. FDA has approved its heart valve repair device designed for patients at risk of complications or death during open-heart surgeries.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-fda-approves-abbotts-heart-valve-repair-device-2024-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ART5B2DOMRP4BK357QQSWEBROA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 13:36:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[WeWork 目标于 5 月 31 日前退出美国和加拿大破产保护程序]]></title><description><![CDATA[WeWork 周二表示，它的目标是在 5 月 31 日前摆脱美国和加拿大的破产保护。【原文：WeWork said on Tuesday it was targeting to emerge from Chapter 11 bankruptcy in the U.S. and Canada by May 31.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/wework-targets-chapter-11-exit-us-canada-by-may-31-2024-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LIWU6QHIVZMKLCN2AJJCMI2FEM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 13:13:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉第一季度交付量不及预期]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉周二公布的第一季度交付量未达预期，原因是该公司在主要市场上面临着来自后起之秀和老牌企业的竞争，同时还面临着其老旧电动汽车阵容需求疲软的问题。【原文：Tesla missed estimates for first-quarter deliveries on Tuesday, as it battled competition from upstarts and established players in major markets, while facing a softness in demand for its aging line-up of electric cars.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/teslas-first-quarter-deliveries-miss-expectations-2024-04-02/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MBVJHAMKNZLKBAOJQUVBQAV5QI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 13:08:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>