<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 16:26:44 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 16:26:39 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[美国向苹果发起挑战，遏制大型科技公司的努力蓄势待发]]></title><description><![CDATA[苹果公司周四遭到美国司法部的起诉，这是监管机构针对大型科技公司采取的最新反垄断行动，这些公司被指控垄断经营和滥用权力。【原文：Apple was on Thursday sued by the U.S. Department of Justice, the latest antitrust action against Big Tech firms accused by regulators of operating monopolies and abusing their power.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-takes-apple-efforts-curtail-big-tech-gather-momentum-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CO4CX3PDM5KWRLDGQOZPT4LDYM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:58:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，苹果、Meta、谷歌将面临欧盟数字市场法案调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[知情人士透露，苹果公司、Meta Platforms 和 Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司将接受调查，以确定它们是否未能遵守欧盟的《数字市场法》。【原文：Apple , Meta Platforms and Alphabet's Google are set to be investigated on whether they have fallen short in complying with the European Union's Digital Markets Act, people with direct knowledge of the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-meta-google-set-face-eu-digital-markets-act-probes-sources-say-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">P6WPBFTB2BKSBMZFZ5CMNALGHQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:48:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高盛资产管理公司为新基金筹资逾 7 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛资产管理公司（Goldman Sachs Asset Management）周四表示，它已为一个新基金筹集了超过 7 亿美元的资金，该基金将与外部经理人合作，在公共和私人市场上寻找投资机会。【原文：Goldman Sachs Asset Management said on Thursday it had raised over $700 million for a new fund that will work with external managers to identify investment opportunities in both public and private markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/goldman-sachs-asset-management-raises-over-700-mln-new-fund-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2TBI2WOWVFMEVO5PF6QVU4CATU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:40:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博法律报道：根据欧盟新数字法，苹果和谷歌将面临调查]]></title><description><![CDATA[据彭博法律周刊周四报道，苹果公司和 Alphabet 旗下的谷歌公司将面临欧盟对其遵守针对大型科技公司的新法律的调查，这将为可能的巨额罚款铺平道路。【原文：Apple and Alphabet's Google are set to face European Union investigations into their compliance with a new law for Big Tech firms, paving the way for potentially hefty fines, Bloomberg Law reported on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-google-set-face-probes-under-new-eu-digital-law-bloomberg-law-reports-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">GUEEI3SNQBPPTPQ6D4SCE6CBNE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:34:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国债主要收益率曲线反转时间创历史最长纪录]]></title><description><![CDATA[尽管美国经济远未出现增长萎缩的迹象，但债券市场即将出现衰退的一个关键信号已经连续闪烁了有史以来最长的时间。【原文：A key bond market signal of an upcoming recession has flashed red continuously for the longest time ever, even if the U.S. economy is far from showing signs of a growth contraction.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/us-treasury-key-yield-curve-inversion-becomes-longest-record-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3HOFPPRUINPX7GSTBBYLNQKFDA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:32:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，西方银行警告欧盟攫取俄罗斯资产计划的风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[业内资深人士说，一些西方银行已经开始游说欧盟，反对重新分配被冻结的俄罗斯资产所赚取的数十亿欧元利息的建议，担心这会导致代价高昂的诉讼。【原文：Some western banks have begun lobbying against EU proposals to redistribute billions of euros in interest earned on frozen Russian assets, senior industry sources said, fearing it could lead to costly litigation.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/western-banks-warn-risks-eu-plan-grab-russian-assets-sources-say-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">PF6F3P33K5NFJPBFBOHGL35Z6E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:25:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中国中芯国际可能违反美国出口禁令生产华为芯片--官方报道]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国商务部一位高级官员在周四的听证会上表示，中国受制裁最严重的芯片制造商中芯国际可能违反了美国的出口法规，因为它生产的芯片为华为 Mate 60 Pro 手机提供了动力。【原文：China's top sanctioned chipmaker SMIC may have violated U.S. export regulations by producing a chip to power Huawei's Mate 60 Pro phone, a senior Commerce Department official said during a hearing on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/chinas-smic-may-have-violated-us-export-curbs-make-huawei-chip-official-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VROX6ZIDDNO3XNFBMO2YJE3RZY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:17:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士开始降息，市场已做好准备]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士周四意外降息后，市场竞相押注大型央行降低借贷成本，但分析师警告说，其他国家的决策者不会轻易放弃抗击通胀的努力。【原文：Markets are racing ahead to bet on big central banks lowering borrowing costs after Switzerland on Thursday delivered a surprise rate cut, but analysts cautioned that policymakers elsewhere won't find it as easy to call time on the inflation fight.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/markets-ready-more-switzerland-starts-clock-rate-cuts-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KSZSK4BHDJMWFGYK36WI3TUSRQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:11:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国监管机构敦促国会调查杂货店利润]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国联邦贸易委员会周四建议，政策制定者应进一步调查食品杂货店经营者自大流行病以来持续走高的利润，以及消费品制造商向零售商提供的促销活动。【原文：The U.S. Federal Trade Commission recommended Thursday that policymakers look further into profits at grocery store operators that remain elevated since the pandemic and promotions that consumer products makers offer retailers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-regulators-urge-congress-look-into-grocery-profits-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LX3QRCMGDBNPRODKSKOMBLARTM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:04:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[麦当劳与法国足球甲级联赛签署为期三年的赞助协议]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国快餐连锁店周四签署了一份为期三年的赞助协议，法国顶级足球联赛将从 7 月 1 日起成为麦当劳法甲联赛。【原文：France's top soccer league will become the McDonald's Ligue 1 from July 1 after the U.S. fast food chain signed a three-year sponsorship deal on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sports/soccer/mcdonalds-signs-three-year-sponsorship-deal-with-french-soccers-ligue-1-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MGU2TBEMCZKZRG5X62VYXVAUCM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:02:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[降息在即，加拿大银行存款争夺战白热化]]></title><description><![CDATA[分析师和高管表示，随着利率可能降低，客户将存放在高收益固定收益产品中的资金转向风险更高的投资以寻求更好的回报，加拿大银行之间争夺客户存款的竞争预计将加剧。【原文：Competition for customer deposits among Canadian banks is expected to intensify with the likely onset of lower interest rates as clients divert funds parked in high-yielding fixed income products to riskier investments in search of better returns, analysts and executives say.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/battle-canadian-bank-deposits-seen-heating-up-rate-cuts-loom-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QSMO3KFUVNKXTNUGI6URV2ZZW4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 14:57:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[高乐氏将出售部分拉美业务，收费 2.33 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[漂白剂生产商高乐氏（Clorox）周四表示，将向私募股权基金 Apex Capital 出售其在阿根廷、乌拉圭和巴拉圭的业务，因为该公司希望收紧投资组合以提高盈利能力，并将为此一次性支出约 2.33 亿美元。【原文：Bleach maker Clorox said on Thursday that it would sell its operations in Argentina, Uruguay and Paraguay to private equity fund Apex Capital, as it looks to tighten its portfolio to be more profitable, and take a one-time charge of about $233 million related to the sale.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/clorox-sell-some-latin-american-operations-take-233-mln-charge-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7TEXC4AWAFPCTGLYMPDCUJ3JVI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 14:49:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国联邦存款保险公司（FDIC）提案草案：超过 1000 亿美元的银行兼并需接受额外审查]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据美国联邦存款保险公司（U.S. Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation）周四发布的指导草案，可能导致资产超过 1,000 亿美元的银行兼并应受到该机构更严格的审查。【原文：Mergers that could result in banks with more than $100 billion in assets should expect heightened scrutiny from the U.S. Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation, according to draft guidance the agency released Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-fdic-draft-proposal-bank-mergers-above-100-bln-get-extra-scrutiny-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">25HW5SXPWBKZHCLVZXPCFZCMBE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 14:42:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国在反垄断诉讼中起诉苹果公司]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国司法部周四起诉苹果公司，这是拜登政府针对这家 iPhone 制造商的首次重大反垄断行动，指控其垄断智能手机市场。【原文：The U.S. Department of Justice on Thursday sued Apple , the first major antitrust effort against the iPhone maker by the Biden administration, alleging it monopolized smartphone markets.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-takes-apple-antitrust-lawsuit-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">45JGEZ4IBZINFN6R3AOB7AQEB4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 14:33:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：参议员伊丽莎白-沃伦敦促美国证券交易委员会调查特斯拉董事会独立性问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周四援引一封信报道，美国参议员伊丽莎白-沃伦（Elizabeth Warren）敦促美国证券交易委员会调查特斯拉是否违反了有关上市公司董事会独立性的规定。【原文：U.S. Senator Elizabeth Warren has urged the Securities and Exchange Commission to investigate whether Tesla violated regulations over board independence at public companies, the Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday, citing a letter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/senator-elizabeth-warren-urges-sec-probe-tesla-over-board-independence-wsj-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DSR4GSXLARMD3JTAQHJP2ODI7I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 14:14:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[流媒体订阅推动 2023 年录制音乐收入增长--报告]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四的一份报告称，2023 年全球录制音乐收入连续第九年增长，增长了 10.2%，达到 286 亿美元，这主要得益于付费流媒体用户的增加。【原文：Global recorded music revenues grew for the ninth year running in 2023, increasing 10.2% to $28.6 billion mainly thanks to a rise in paid streaming subscribers, a report said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/streaming-subscriptions-boost-2023-recorded-music-revenues-report-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OYGBGBEKBJNYZNC3DHK2AKYRAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 14:11:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 2 月成屋销售升至一年新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着供应量的增加，2 月份美国现房销售量创下一年来的新高，这一趋势加上抵押贷款利率的下降，可能会支持春季销售旺季的活动。【原文：U.S. existing home sales increased to a one-year high in February as supply improved, a trend that together with retreating mortgage rates could support activity during the spring selling season.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-existing-home-sales-rise-one-year-high-february-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3HAYFLNPRJNAJDNAQUA4P33AG4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 14:03:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士意外降息，下一个会是谁？]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士国家银行周四启动了降息，这是继不按常理出牌的日本央行 17 年来首次加息之后，本周第二个重要的央行决策。【原文：The Swiss National Bank kicked off rate cuts on Thursday, the week's second momentous central bank decision after the non-conformist Bank of Japan delivered its first rate hike in 17 years.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/switzerland-surprises-with-rate-cut-whos-next-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LVCDDIUUYNOHRIQFI64PK36OSU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 13:59:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lyft 与尼尔森签订协议，测量应用内广告]]></title><description><![CDATA[数据分析公司尼尔森（Nielsen）周四表示，尼尔森与 Lyft 已签署协议，将对该打车公司移动应用程序上的广告进行测量。【原文：Nielsen and Lyft have signed an agreement to measure advertisements on the ride-hailing company's mobile app, the data analytics firm said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/lyft-inks-deal-with-nielsen-measure-in-app-ads-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UG46DEC3BNISZFVUFXQ7R7FFYE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 13:54:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国 3 月商业活动稳定；通胀回升]]></title><description><![CDATA[3 月份，美国商业活动保持稳定，但物价全面上涨，表明通胀在年初回升后可能继续走高。【原文：U.S. business activity held steady in March, but prices increased across the board, suggesting that inflation could remain elevated after picking up at the start of the year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-business-activity-stable-march-inflation-picks-up-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KIXFVNO6MBIZVL6IQACD5RNRHY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 13:51:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[在激烈的代理权争夺战中，ISS 支持激进分子佩尔茨进入迪士尼董事会]]></title><description><![CDATA[周四，激进分子纳尔逊-佩尔茨（Nelson Peltz）获得了强有力的支持，代理咨询公司机构股东服务公司（ISS）建议迪士尼股东选举他进入这家娱乐集团的董事会，这对该公司是一个打击。【原文：Activist Nelson Peltz received a powerful endorsement on Thursday when proxy advisory firm Institutional Shareholder Services (ISS) recommended Disney shareholders elect him to the entertainment conglomerate's board, in a blow to the company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/proxy-advisory-firm-iss-recommends-disney-shareholders-elect-nelson-peltz-board-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6PNPSX7HNJM5ZKZ7NT6XZAJVIU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 13:47:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国迫使 Raiffeisen 放弃俄罗斯交易，Raiffeisen 股票和债券再次下跌]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社本周早些时候报道，华盛顿正在向这家奥地利银行施压，要求其取消与一名受制裁的俄罗斯富豪达成的交易，此后，该银行的股票和债券在周四再次下跌。【原文：Raiffeisen's share and bonds fell again on Thursday, after Reuters reported earlier this week that Washington was pressing the Austrian bank to cancel a deal with a sanctioned Russian tycoon.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/raiffeisen-shares-bonds-fall-again-us-presses-bank-drop-russia-deal-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XE5TJYPMSRODRC6VFG5VIQXOA4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 13:37:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CalPERS 称埃克森公司应撤销针对气候意识投资者的诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国最大的公共养老基金计划要求埃克森美孚撤销对投资者的诉讼，因为投资者提交了一份股东决议，要求这家美国石油巨头更快地控制温室气体排放。【原文：The largest U.S. public pension fund plans to ask Exxon Mobil to drop a lawsuit against investors that filed a shareholder resolution asking the U.S. oil major to curb greenhouse gas emissions faster.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/calpers-says-exxon-should-drop-lawsuit-against-climate-conscious-investors-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">A57BPXN7VZNBVCWKJKNQEELHQQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 13:24:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[报告显示，3月份美国新车销量将有所增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[据行业咨询公司J.D. Power和GlobalData周四联合发布的一份报告称，受强劲需求和车辆供应的推动，3月份美国新车销量预计将增长12.1%。【原文：U.S. new vehicle sales are expected to rise 12.1% in March, fueled by strong demand and vehicle availability, according to a joint report by industry consultants J.D. Power and GlobalData on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/us-new-vehicles-sales-set-rise-march-report-shows-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HQUSHJ4FHNOFDCCAW3LQPK33LM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 13:20:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国第四季度经常账户赤字收窄]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国政府周四公布的数据显示，由于二次收入增加，美国第四季度经常账户赤字收窄至近三年来的最低水平。【原文：The U.S. current account deficit narrowed in the fourth quarter to the lowest level in nearly three years amid an increase in secondary income, government data showed on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-current-account-deficit-narrows-fourth-quarter-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">75QSHU6VIJLPXK3WIPPSWH3AEA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 13:18:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Shake Shack 任命约翰爸爸首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[Shake Shack 周四表示，该公司已任命约翰爸爸国际公司首席执行官罗布-林奇（Rob Lynch）为首席执行官，接替在这家汉堡连锁店工作了二十多年后即将退休的兰迪-加鲁蒂（Randy Garutti）。【原文：Shake Shack said on Thursday it has named Papa John's International's CEO Rob Lynch as its chief, succeeding Randy Garutti, who is retiring after spending more than two decades at the burger chain.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/shake-shack-names-papa-johns-chief-its-ceo-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">WWXOZ54VPFOFXJDRCL5DURYFAU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 12:51:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》报道，美国航空公司首席执行官要求与波音董事会会面，以解决生产问题]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周四援引知情人士的话报道，美国主要航空公司负责人已要求与波音公司董事会会面，以表达对阿拉斯加航空公司事故和生产问题的担忧。【原文：Major U.S. airline chiefs have requested a meeting with Boeing's board to express concerns over an Alaska Airlines accident and production problems, the Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/us-airline-ceos-request-meeting-with-boeing-board-address-production-problems-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">G6KJEBM2RBK7HJ2CCEBBIYEIU4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 12:45:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国每周申请失业救济人数意外下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[上周新申请失业救济的美国人数意外下降，表明 3 月份就业增长依然强劲。【原文：The number of Americans filing new claims for unemployment benefits unexpectedly fell last week, suggesting that job growth remained strong in March.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-weekly-jobless-claims-unexpectedly-fall-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JZK3I4P36VL3JDIELUKVET4CEM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 12:41:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[长江实业集团李嘉诚称香港需要维护金融中心地位]]></title><description><![CDATA[企业集团长江实业集团（CK Group）主席李泽钜（Victor Li）周四表示，经过多年动荡之后，香港政府需要保护香港的国际金融中心地位。【原文：The Hong Kong government needs to protect the city's international financial hub status after years of upheaval, chairman of conglomerate CK Group Victor Li said on Thursday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/ck-groups-li-says-hong-kong-needs-safeguard-financial-hub-status-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VDPDL63I4VJVTA3L747MY5GAD4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 12:35:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[英国央行认为经济 "朝着正确方向发展 "有利于降息]]></title><description><![CDATA[英国央行行长安德鲁-贝利（Andrew Bailey）表示，英国经济正 "朝着正确的方向发展"，英国央行可以开始降息，他的两位同事放弃了对加息的投票。【原文：Britain's economy is "moving in the right direction" for the Bank of England to start cutting interest rates, Governor Andrew Bailey said as two of his colleagues dropped their vote for a rate hike.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/bank-england-sees-economy-moving-right-direction-rate-cuts-2024-03-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">W4JHQJFVBRJCFMNINJHZSV7UJY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 12:03:03 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>