<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 09:16:03 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 09:16:03 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉将全自动驾驶软件的价格降低三分之一，降至 8,000 美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉网站周六显示，特斯拉全自动驾驶辅助软件在美国的售价从1.2万美元降至8000美元。【原文：Tesla slashed the price of its Full Self-Driving driver assistant software to $8,000 from $12,000 in the United States, its website showed on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-cuts-price-full-self-driving-software-by-third-8000-2024-04-21/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LX4QZOEDH5PLFM3IFKHFKLPEYE</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 04:04:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[多边开发银行希望在 10 年内增加多达 4000 亿美元的贷款]]></title><description><![CDATA[美洲开发银行周六表示，10 家多边开发银行的领导人承诺在五个关键领域采取行动，包括在未来十年内提供总额达 3,000-4,000 亿美元的额外贷款。【原文：The Inter-American Development Bank on Saturday said leaders of 10 multilateral development banks committed to take action in five critical areas, including additional lending headroom totaling $300-400 billion over the next decade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/multilateral-development-banks-eye-up-400-bln-more-lending-over-10-years-2024-04-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UHRHS54BAZJ2PJI7YTQHPTMLWI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 18:20:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞士国家银行行长称增长过低，但必须关注物价稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞士国家银行行长托马斯-乔丹（Thomas Jordan）在周六播出的讲话中表示，货币政策应继续关注物价稳定。【原文：Monetary policy should remain focused on price stability, Swiss National Bank Chairman Thomas Jordan said in remarks aired on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/europe/growth-is-too-low-focus-must-be-price-stability-snbs-jordan-2024-04-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">B63O3NDDO5PJBDDXUET5UYBKPA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 18:03:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（IMF）的戈皮纳特说美国的高需求推动了经济增长和利率上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（International Monetary Fund）第一副总裁吉塔-戈皮纳特（Gita Gopinath）周六表示，美国需要增加收入以降低高额预算赤字，尽管这些赤字正在通过刺激美国国内需求来推动全球经济增长。【原文：The United States needs to raise revenues to bring down high budget deficits even though they are helping to fuel global growth by stoking domestic U.S. demand, International Monetary Fund First Deputy Managing Director Gita Gopinath said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/imfs-gopinath-says-high-us-demand-fueling-growth-higher-interest-rates-2024-04-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3N4K73YKCVMSLIDW7S2FTRWX7Y</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 16:56:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织和世界银行指导委员会强调改革推进过程中的问责制]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织和世界银行的指导委员会周六强调，在这两个机构实施改革以帮助各国应对气候变化和其他冲击的过程中，需要建立更广泛的问责制。【原文：The steering committee for both International Monetary Fund and the World Bank on Saturday emphasized the need for broader accountability as the institutions implemented reforms to help countries grapple with climate change and other shocks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/imf-world-bank-steering-committee-stresses-accountability-reforms-advance-2024-04-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4USBBUZGAJMNTG4RYTC3TU6PXE</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 14:40:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[大众工厂获胜后，UAW 将目光投向阿拉巴马州的奔驰工厂]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国汽车工人联合会（United Auto Workers）在美国南部的一家汽车厂赢得了首次工会投票，创造了历史。现在，它需要在下个月于阿拉巴马州的梅赛德斯工厂取得第二次胜利，以证明这一成功并非侥幸。【原文：The United Auto Workers has made history by winning its first unionization vote at an auto factory in the U.S. South. Now it needs to prove the success wasn't a fluke by pulling off a second victory at a Mercedes plant in Alabama next month.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/after-vw-plant-victory-uaw-sets-its-sights-mercedes-alabama-2024-04-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DUVY7B6CIJKSVCJG6C6YRF6KBY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 13:07:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[迪拜洪灾后阿联酋航空和迪拜国际航空恢复正常运营]]></title><description><![CDATA[迪拜旗舰航空公司阿联酋航空（Emirates）和姊妹航空公司迪拜国际航空（flydubai）周六表示，在本周早些时候暴雨导致阿联酋各地发生严重洪灾后，两家航空公司已恢复正常运营。【原文：Dubai's flagship carrier Emirates and sister airline flydubai have restored normal operations after heavy rains caused severe flooding across the United Arab Emirates earlier this week, the airlines said on Saturday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/emirates-flydubai-resume-normal-operations-after-dubai-floods-2024-04-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">S7XSE6BSWFN4NGWEZA5VRIARQ4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 10:56:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[X 誓言 "强烈质疑 "澳大利亚删除刺伤帖子的命令]]></title><description><![CDATA[社交媒体平台 X 周六表示，它将在法庭上对澳大利亚监管机构要求该公司删除一些与悉尼一名主教被刺事件有关的帖子的命令提出质疑。【原文：Social media platform X said on Saturday it would challenge in court an order from an Australian regulator demanding the company remove some posts related to the stabbing of a bishop in Sydney.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/x-vows-robustly-challenge-australia-order-remove-stabbing-posts-2024-04-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CSH2CPZYWBIE7LBIRBLGMU7QPU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 05:56:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉将 Y、X 和 S 车型的美国售价下调 2000 美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉周五将其 Model Y、Model X 和 Model S 汽车在美国的售价各下调 2000 美元，几天前这家全球最有价值汽车制造商的第一季度交付量未能达到市场预期。【原文：Tesla cut the U.S. prices of its Model Y, Model X and Model S vehicles by $2,000 each on Friday, days after the first-quarter deliveries of the world's most valuable automaker missed market expectations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-cuts-us-prices-models-y-x-s-by-2000-2024-04-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3GOZHU5BABO7TBCVZYEPXORQBI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 05:32:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[UAW 在大众田纳西工厂取得分水岭式的工会胜利]]></title><description><![CDATA[大众汽车田纳西州工厂的工人已投票决定加入美国汽车工人工会，该工会周五表示，在非官方统计结果显示大多数符合条件的工人投票支持加入工会后，该工厂取得了胜利。【原文：Workers at Volkswagen's Tennessee plant have voted to join the United Auto Workers, the union said on Friday, calling victory after an unofficial tally showed a majority of eligible workers had cast ballots in favor of the union.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/uaw-clinches-watershed-union-victory-volkswagen-tennessee-factory-2024-04-20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5BXGNW7JCVMG7GL2JOP7AMSK5M</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 02:14:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[日本央行上田表示，如果通胀持续上升，"很有可能 "加息]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本央行行长上田一夫周五表示，如果基本通胀率继续上升，央行将 "很有可能 "提高利率。【原文：Bank of Japan Governor Kazuo Ueda said on Friday the central bank will "very likely" be raising interest rates if underlying inflation continued to go up.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/bojs-ueda-says-very-likely-hike-rates-if-inflation-keeps-rising-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DK62B7EJWBIARCMIDBR67VEUYE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 21:58:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西航空工业公司第一季度交付 25 架喷气机，积压量创 7 年新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[巴西飞机制造商巴西航空工业公司（Embraer）周五表示，该公司在2024年第一季度交付了25架飞机，其中包括7架商用飞机和18架公务机，同比增长67%。【原文：Brazilian planemaker Embraer said on Friday it delivered 25 aircraft - seven commercial planes and 18 executive jets - in the first quarter of 2024, a 67% increase on a yearly basis.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/brazils-embraer-delivers-25-jets-q1-backlog-hits-7-year-high-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4A7464ZCZFI4VENV2QEEYEQSYE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 21:45:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[耐克将在俄勒冈州总部裁员 740 人]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五的一封信显示，耐克将在其位于俄勒冈州的全球总部裁员约 740 人，因为这家顶级运动服装制造商在发出 2025 财年上半年收入下滑的警告后，正寻求控制成本。【原文：Nike will lay off about 740 employees at its world headquarters in Oregon, a letter showed on Friday, as the top sportswear maker looks to rein in costs after warning of a revenue dip in the first half of fiscal 2025.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/nike-lay-off-740-employees-oregon-headquarters-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QDQDI3XVEVM3DACGTH76X35AP4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 20:57:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[本田到 2030 年将在巴西投资 8.08 亿美元]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本汽车制造商本田公司的一位高管周五表示，到2030年，该公司将在巴西的伊蒂拉皮纳工厂投资42亿雷亚尔（约合8.0774亿美元），并补充说，该公司的目标是在南美国家开发一种混合动力柔性车。【原文：Japanese automaker Honda will invest 4.2 billion reais ($807.74 million) in its Itirapina plant in Brazil by 2030, an executive said on Friday, adding the company aims to develop a hybrid-flex vehicle in the South American country.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/honda-invest-808-million-brazil-by-2030-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XEGZHTNG2JKUPFE32UDI2KY3QU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 20:52:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥央行副行长认为利率维持时间将比预期更长]]></title><description><![CDATA[墨西哥央行副行长乔纳森-希思（Jonathan Heath）周五表示，基准利率保持不变的时间可能比市场预期的要长，并指出在 5 月份的政策会议上，基准利率可能会维持在 11% 不变，而 6 月份的决定将取决于数据。【原文：Bank of Mexico Deputy Governor Jonathan Heath said on Friday the benchmark interest rate is likely to remain unchanged for longer than expected by markets, noting it would likely stay put at 11% at the May policy meeting and that the June decision would be data dependent.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/bank-mexico-deputy-governor-sees-rates-hold-longer-than-expected-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5GHOCXSDGNLFPHNSSKI7CJDOMI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 20:34:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储称 1,804 家银行和其他机构使用了紧急贷款机制]]></title><description><![CDATA[美联储周五表示，约有 1804 家存款机构利用了去年 3 月硅谷银行倒闭后设立的紧急贷款机制，约占所有符合条件公司的 20%。【原文：Some 1,804 depository institutions tapped the emergency lending facility set up last March in the wake of Silicon Valley Bank's collapse, amounting to about 20% of all eligible firms, the Federal Reserve said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/fed-says-1804-banks-other-institutions-tapped-emergency-lending-facility-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">J5FLSVJYANI6NPHJ6VWBXRCZUY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 20:08:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储报告指出通胀和美国大选是金融稳定的主要风险]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美联储对美国中央银行联系人的最新调查中，持续通胀和更高更长的利率被认为是金融稳定的主要风险，地缘政治问题和2024年美国总统大选也被认为是 "潜在的重大冲击源"。【原文：Persistent inflation and higher-for-longer interest rates were cited as key risks to financial stability in the Federal Reserve's latest survey of U.S. central bank contacts, with geopolitical troubles and the 2024 U.S. presidential election also mentioned as "a potentially significant source of shocks."】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/fed-report-cites-inflation-us-election-key-financial-stability-risks-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XYO3UHXK7ZOK5DVVXQSUA3VMQE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 20:04:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lululemon 关闭华盛顿分销中心，裁员 128 人]]></title><description><![CDATA[服装零售商 Lululemon Athletica 周五告诉路透社，公司将于今年年底关闭位于华盛顿州的分销中心，并裁员 100 多人。【原文：Lululemon Athletica will close its distribution center in the state of Washington at the end of the year and lay off more than 100 employees, the apparel retailer told Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/lululemon-shutter-washington-distribution-center-lay-off-128-employees-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">YYUPQUG5KFIFZB72GAMGHMDEJE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 20:01:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[低收入国家面临的债务和财政挑战令国际货币基金组织担忧]]></title><description><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织（IMF）总裁克里斯塔琳娜-格奥尔基耶娃（Kristalina Georgieva）周五表示，国际货币基金组织的股东们本周就应对低收入国家所面临的挑战的重要性达成了一致，其中许多国家正面临着不可持续的债务负担。【原文：Shareholders of the International Monetary Fund agreed this week on the importance of addressing challenges faced by low-income countries, many of which are facing unsustainable debt burdens, IMF Managing Director Kristalina Georgieva said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/debt-fiscal-challenges-facing-low-income-countries-worry-imf-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6N5L4FDJCJLYDKRJUO6YZBNNJA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 19:56:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[行业组织表示，政府必须促成当地对矿山的支持]]></title><description><![CDATA[一个知名行业组织的负责人说，世界各国政府必须采取更多措施，说服当地社区和土著团体支持那些生产能源转型和应对气候变化所需的关键矿产的矿山。【原文：The world's governments must do more to convince local communities and Indigenous groups to support mines that produce critical minerals needed to power the energy transition and fight climate change, the head of a prominent industry group said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/official-governments-must-broker-local-support-mines-industry-group-says-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IMGU234MUVNRZHGSPN5MXODKOU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 19:52:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[UnitedHealth 首席执行官将就技术部门遭受网络攻击一事向美国众议院小组作证]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国能源与商业委员会（Energy and Commerce Committee）周五表示，UnitedHealth 首席执行官安德鲁-威蒂（Andrew Witty）将于 5 月 1 日在美国众议院小组委员会作证，说明该公司技术部门最近遭受的网络攻击及其对患者和医疗服务提供者的影响。【原文：UnitedHealth CEO Andrew Witty will testify before a U.S. House subcommittee on May 1 about a recent cyberattack at the company's technology unit and its impact on patients and providers, the Energy and Commerce Committee said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/unitedhealth-ceo-testify-before-us-house-panel-cyberattack-tech-unit-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">FLBLRHPVFZMJBCJ2QRDGNUJU6Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 19:45:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[富国银行债券女销售员就 "毫无保留的性别歧视 "工作场所提起诉讼]]></title><description><![CDATA[富国银行（Wells Fargo）在一起诉讼中被一名债券销售员指控性别歧视，她说这家美国第四大银行拒绝给予男性薪酬和晋升机会，并容忍 "毫不掩饰性别歧视 "的工作场所。【原文：Wells Fargo was accused of sex discrimination in a lawsuit by a bond saleswoman who said the fourth-largest U.S. bank denied pay and promotions available to men and tolerated an "unapologetically sexist" workplace.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/wells-fargo-bond-saleswoman-sues-over-unapologetically-sexist-workplace-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5TBGNSOPIFJ6HF6XOYX75T2G4E</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 19:29:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[聚焦：百事公司的特斯拉 Semi 卡车供不应求，因为其竞争对手使用了同类电动大卡车]]></title><description><![CDATA[特斯拉的主要客户百事公司在 2017 年支付了 100 辆特斯拉 Semis 的首批款项，打算用电动卡车车队将其 Cheetos、Lays 薯片和百事苏打汽水运往零售商。【原文：Key Tesla customer PepsiCo made initial payments for 100 Tesla Semis in 2017, intending to use the electric-truck fleet to haul its Cheetos, Lays potato chips and Pepsi soda pop to retailers.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-semi-trucks-short-supply-pepsico-its-rivals-use-competing-ev-big-rigs-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LXSXVVODLRKCPJUE2JZQVFJYIM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 19:04:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧洲央行行长拉加德称通胀更有可能缓解，但风险双向存在]]></title><description><![CDATA[欧洲央行行长克里斯蒂娜-拉加德（Christine Lagarde）周五表示，欧元区通胀率可能会进一步下降，如果符合其长期以来的物价增长标准，欧洲央行可能会降息。【原文：Euro zone inflation is likely to decline further and the European Central Bank may cut interest rates if its long-standing price growth criteria are met, ECB President Christine Lagarde said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/ecbs-lagarde-says-inflation-more-likely-ease-risks-both-ways-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UIE2I4UDWBLHHMZ6NQI4AN3BHY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 19:03:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[政治热潮促使日韩联手应对弱势货币]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本和韩国本周成功地在与美国的联合声明中加入了对本国货币表示担忧的措辞，这凸显了它们因汇率疲软而加剧的严重通货膨胀所面临的政治压力。【原文：The success of Japan and South Korea at inserting language voicing concern over their currencies in a joint statement with the U.S. this week underscores the political heat they face from stiff inflation that is being aggravated by weak exchange rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/political-heat-prods-japan-south-korea-team-up-weak-currencies-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JJZ5KMGWONKMLADTGAL2VJDPAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 18:21:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊广告主管离职履新]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚马逊公司的广告主管科琳-奥布里（Colleen Aubrey）已担任该职务近三年，她将调任该公司一个未公开的新职位。【原文：Amazon.com's advertising chief Colleen Aubrey, who has held that role for nearly three years, is moving to a new undisclosed position at the company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/amazon-advertising-chief-steps-aside-new-role-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OMPCQHOB3NPXXBYWOJWA3QOCHI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 18:13:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[首席执行官：稳定币 Tether 作为新兴市场的美元替代品受到提振]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tether 首席执行官保罗-阿尔多诺（Paolo Ardoino）周五告诉路透社，稳定币 Tether 近期的增长主要是受其在新兴市场作为美元替代品的使用所推动，而不是受加密货币交易需求的推动。【原文：Stablecoin Tether's recent growth is being driven by its use as an alternative to the U.S. dollar in emerging markets, rather than by demand for cryptocurrency trading, Tether CEO Paolo Ardoino told Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/stablecoin-tether-gets-boost-dollar-alternative-emerging-markets-ceo-says-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4DKWIPU6KBLTNIIBFJDAMIPMYY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 18:04:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：美国监管机构酝酿限制华尔街高管奖金]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周五报道，美国银行业监管机构正计划重提一项提案，要求大银行推迟高管薪酬，并在亏损累累时收回更多奖金。【原文：U.S. banking regulators are planning to revive a proposal that would require big banks to defer executive compensation and claw back more of their bonuses if losses pile up, the Wall Street Journal reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-regulators-mulling-bid-limit-bonuses-wall-street-execs-wsj-reports-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KEG7PI3PO5KSBJU5O5O4XRCY6Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:51:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌废除针对供应商和人才派遣公司的最低工资和福利规定]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet Inc.旗下的谷歌公司（Google）周五表示，将取消美国供应商和人才派遣公司向员工支付至少15美元时薪并提供医疗保险和其他福利的要求，此举可能使这家科技巨头避免与工会讨价还价。【原文：Alphabet Inc's Google on Friday said it will roll back requirements that U.S. suppliers and staffing firms pay their employees at least $15 an hour and provide health insurance and other benefits, a move that could allow the tech giant to avoid bargaining with unions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/google-scraps-minimum-wage-benefits-rules-suppliers-staffing-firms-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KETP2AWEYJOITCG3S5ZDTLCI3A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:47:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拜登推动清洁能源发展，阿尔贝马勒和康明斯获得税收减免]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据美国能源部（DOE）周五公布的详细资料，Albemarle、康明斯和西门子能源等公司根据《通货膨胀削减法》（IRA）的一项条款获得了税收减免。【原文：Albemarle , Cummins and Siemens Energy are some companies that received tax credit under a section of the Inflation Reduction Act (IRA), according to details released on Friday by the U.S. Department of Energy (DOE).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/albemarle-cummins-receive-tax-credits-under-bidens-clean-energy-drive-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IK53CBMAYJLKDFMCQAVJDJLJKU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:34:16 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>