<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:47:07 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:47:07 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[对冲基金四月转为看跌，高盛称]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛（Goldman Sachs）的一份报告称，全球对冲基金今年以来对股市的看跌程度最高，原因是通胀持续高企和地缘政治担忧重燃拖累股市走低。【原文：Hedge funds globally have turned the most bearish they've been on equities this year, a Goldman Sachs note said, as sticky inflation and renewed geopolitical concern have dragged stock markets lower.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/hedge-flow-hedge-funds-turn-bearish-april-goldman-says-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U565DXU56BPCZM7Z524KXO27II</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:02:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，摩根士丹利消费者 IPO 银行家 Passi 即将离职]]></title><description><![CDATA[据熟悉内情的人士透露，摩根士丹利北美消费者和零售股权资本市场（ECM）主管 Tilli Dias Passi 将离开该行。【原文：Morgan Stanley's North America head of consumer and retail equity capital markets (ECM) Tilli Dias Passi will leave the bank, according to people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/morgan-stanley-consumer-ipo-banker-passi-leaving-bank-sources-say-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z5GS2JC4GNIOJOKW2LGW5U2E5A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 14:55:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席古尔斯比称通胀进展 "停滞 "令政策搁置]]></title><description><![CDATA[芝加哥联储主席奥斯汀-古尔斯比（Austan Goolsbee）周五表示，今年在降低通胀率方面的进展 "停滞不前"，他是最新一位不再关注即将到来的降息需求的美国央行行长。【原文：Progress on bringing down inflation has "stalled" this year, Chicago Federal Reserve President Austan Goolsbee said on Friday, becoming the latest U.S. central banker to retreat from an earlier focus on the coming need for interest rate cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-goolsbee-says-stalled-inflation-progress-puts-policy-hold-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2XG5DR6CSVMIDEXXI7GPBD5FZU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 14:39:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易紧张局势加剧，中国对进口一种美国化学品征收反倾销税]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国周五对从美国进口的一种广泛用于食品、饲料、杀虫剂和医疗领域的酸征税，与华盛顿在双边贸易问题上的紧张关系加剧。【原文：China on Friday slapped a levy on imports of an acid from the United States widely used in food, feed, pesticides and medical fields, amid heightened tensions with Washington over bilateral trade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/china-slaps-anti-dumping-levy-import-us-chemical-amid-rising-trade-tensions-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6GD4GJBWGJLPNEXVWG5TWZDIJE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 13:39:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国债务前景恶化更多体现在黄金和比特币上而非债券上]]></title><description><![CDATA[市场观察人士表示，对美国政府债务快速上升的担忧是近期金价和比特币飙升的部分原因，尽管迄今为止国债市场对美国的财政之路仍相对乐观。【原文：Concern about the rapidly rising U.S. government debt is partly behind recent surges in gold prices and bitcoin, even as the Treasury market so far remains relatively sanguine about the country's fiscal path, market observers say.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/worsening-us-debt-outlook-seen-more-gold-bitcoin-than-bonds-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4OEUCAS4TRIV5MWZO22KQG255U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 13:35:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[伊朗扣押船只后，航运业敦促联合国保护船只]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着中东地区袭击事件的升级，商船和海员在海上面临的危险与日俱增，联合国必须采取更多措施保护供应链。【原文：Merchant ships and seafarers are increasingly in peril at sea as attacks escalate in the Middle East and the United Nations must do more to protect supply chains, the industry said in a letter released on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/shipping-industry-urges-un-protect-vessels-after-iran-seizure-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XBEQCHZFSNN3XMND7U6UYYZKZI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 13:13:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者为长期高利率做好准备，美国股票基金资金大幅流出]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至 4 月 17 日的七天内，美国股票基金遭遇了大幅资金外流，原因是投资者预计在美国经济复苏的同时，通胀顽固，利率将长期受到限制。【原文：U.S. equity funds suffered sharp outflows in the seven days to April 17 as investors anticipated prolonged restrictive interest rates amid stubborn inflation in a resilient U.S. economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-equity-funds-see-sharp-outflows-investors-brace-extended-high-rates-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I2RX73PMVBLUVATLPDVCCJD5U4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 13:03:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华纳兄弟首席执行官 2023 年薪酬增长近 27]]></title><description><![CDATA[华纳兄弟 Discovery 首席执行官大卫-扎斯拉夫（David Zaslav）周五向美国证券交易委员会（SEC）提交的一份文件显示，2023 年，他的年薪将增长近 27%，达到 4,970 万美元。【原文：Warner Bros Discovery CEO David Zaslav's annual compensation rose nearly 27% to $49.7 million in 2023, a filing with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/warner-bros-ceo-pay-rose-nearly-27-2023-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MLRRWXTPPNJAXJNW67N4IOHT6M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 12:48:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中东紧张局势升级给世界市场带来新的冲击]]></title><description><![CDATA[有报道称，以色列对伊朗领土的袭击可能会将中东拖入更深的冲突，这给世界市场带来了地缘政治风险，可能会迅速改变从石油到债券等任何事物的走向，并再次引发通胀风险。【原文：Reports of an Israeli attack on Iranian soil that possibly drags the Middle East into a deeper conflict has jolted world markets with geopolitical risks that can swiftly change the direction of anything from oil to bonds and renew inflation risks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-middle-east-graphic-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">27QYUJFLZFLEZDB2AIUYSF2WLI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 11:59:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Archer Aviation 计划明年在印度开始电动空中出租车试验]]></title><description><![CDATA[Archer Aviation 公司首席执行官周五告诉路透社，该公司得到了 Stellantis 和波音公司的支持，目标是明年在印度开始试验其电动空中出租车，计划于 2026 年投入商业运营。【原文：Archer Aviation , backed by Stellantis and Boeing , aims to begin trials of its electric air taxi in India next year, ahead of a planned commercial launch in 2026, the company's chief executive told Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/archer-aviation-aims-start-electric-air-taxi-trials-india-next-year-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UJD3MITMA5PRFOGKIJC5QTTXQ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 11:52:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[降息希望破灭，全球股票基金资金外流激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于市场猜测美国联邦储备委员会将推迟降息，投资者情绪受挫，截至 4 月 17 日的七天内，全球股票基金的资金流出量大幅增加。【原文：Global equity funds saw a jump in outflows in the seven days through April 17 as speculation the U.S. Federal Reserve will delay cutting interest rates dampened investor sentiment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-flows-graphic-pix-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JYP62X2EERNE3OEUN2XTKBQXQY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 11:49:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[利息收入减少导致第五季公司利润下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[Fifth Third Bancorp 周五公布的第一季度利润下降了 10%，原因是存款成本上升拖累了该银行的利息收入。【原文：Fifth Third Bancorp posted a 10% drop in first-quarter profit on Friday as higher deposit costs weighed on the lender's interest income.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/fifth-third-bancorps-quarterly-profit-falls-lower-interest-income-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MVKY4R5MLJJIPLPDCNGKOKEEZI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 11:41:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国运通利润超出预期，富裕客户消费强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，美国运通的第一季度利润超过了华尔街的预期，其主要原因是随着经济衰退的担忧减弱，富裕客户群增加了消费。【原文：American Express's first-quarter profit vaulted past Wall Street estimates on Friday, driven by an affluent customer base that increased spending as recession fears receded.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/american-express-beats-profit-estimates-strong-spending-by-wealthy-customers-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MSFFWPTFFFOELAEGQG3SYGYHPQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 11:12:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[宝洁上调年度核心利润预期，原因是需求回升和价格上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[宝洁公司周五上调了年度核心利润预期，原因是美国和欧洲市场对其清洁和家用产品的价格上涨和需求回升。【原文：Procter &amp; Gamble raised its annual core profit forecast on Friday on price increases and resilient demand for its cleaning and household products in the United States and Europe.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/pg-raises-annual-core-profit-forecast-resilient-demand-price-hikes-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2VT7CXJ54FLZZHSGT4CL5ONP6I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 11:04:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[油田公司SLB利润因国际钻井需求而增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，顶级油田服务公司 SLB 公布第一季度利润增长 14%，符合分析师的预期，原因是中东和非洲强劲的油气钻探需求帮助抵消了北美活动的疲软。【原文：Top oilfield services firm SLB reported a 14% rise in first-quarter profit on Friday, in line with analysts' estimates, as strong oil and gas drilling demand in the Middle East and Africa helped offset weakness in North American activity.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/oilfield-firm-slbs-profit-rises-international-drilling-demand-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6K2HZG5CJBKLPGT27S5Y3MW4EQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 10:58:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 美股 "拥挤 "的大盘交易等待财报考验]]></title><description><![CDATA[下周，市场上最大的几家科技和成长型公司将公布财报，这将是对美股涨势的一次重要考验。【原文：Next week’s earnings reports from some of the market’s biggest technology and growth companies could prove an important test for the U.S. stock rally, which has flagged as expectations for interest cuts fade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-st-week-ahead-crowded-megacap-trade-us-stocks-awaits-earnings-test-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BR42Y6NC6VIXFKB4CCMMT7DIQU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 10:12:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电动汽车增长放缓，通用汽车和福特寄希望于燃油卡车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国汽车制造商通用汽车和福特汽车在下周公布第一季度业绩时面临着一个共同的挑战：在电动汽车增长放缓的情况下，如何向投资者解释未来几个月利润增长的来源。【原文：U.S. automakers General Motors and Ford face a challenge in common when they report first-quarter results next week: Explaining to investors where profit growth will come from in the months ahead as EV growth slows.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/gm-ford-count-gas-powered-trucks-ev-growth-slows-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OD4I7ZD5GNIQXKIJC3A3APVMCM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 10:06:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[早间竞标：以色列与伊朗针锋相对，市场动荡不安]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mike Dolan 展望美国和全球市场的未来一天【原文：A look at the day ahead in U.S. and global markets from Mike Dolan】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-view-usa-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K7P2SDSXZFJZDCX4ZULN5Z7DLY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 10:03:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国汽车工会有望在大众田纳西工厂取得分水岭式的工会胜利]]></title><description><![CDATA[汽车工人联合会（United Auto Workers）寄希望于周五在大众汽车田纳西州工厂的工会投票中取得一场震撼性的胜利--这场胜利将使反对工会的美国南部地区向有组织的劳工开放。【原文：The United Auto Workers is counting on scoring a seismic victory at Volkswagen's Tennessee plant as unionization votes are tallied on Friday - one that opens up the anti-union U.S. South to organized labor.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/uaw-hopeful-watershed-union-victory-volkswagen-tennessee-factory-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LAYPFYZUJ5MTXJ2HZFLYGL576M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 10:02:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊可能很快被迫承认英国 GMB 工会]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国科技和零售巨头亚马逊可能很快就会被要求正式承认其英国考文垂仓库的 GMB 工会，此前一个政府机构做出了有利于该工会的裁决。【原文：U.S. technology and retail giant Amazon could soon be required to formally recognise the GMB union at its Coventry warehouse in Britain, after a government body ruled in the union's favour.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/amazon-could-soon-be-forced-recognise-uks-gmb-union-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2KOVJYCOVFINJKLDA6LMQEL7OA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 09:57:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[比拜登加征关税更令人担忧的是中国钢铁行业]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国总统乔-拜登（Joe Biden）推动对中国进口钢铁征收三倍关税，这对一个面临更大担忧的行业来说，主要是象征性的打击，因为当地需求不振，而且中国出口激增可能带来更强烈的反击。【原文：U.S. President Joe Biden's push to triple tariffs on Chinese steel imports strikes a mostly symbolic blow on an industry facing bigger concerns over faltering local demand and threats of even stronger blowback against China's surging exports.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/chinas-steel-sector-has-bigger-worries-than-biden-tariff-hike-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JWPKG5N4X5NNVMQE7GZHHQAUPM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 09:50:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者从现金中提取资金支付税款并抛售美股 - 美国银行]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据美国银行援引数据提供商 EPFR 提供的基金流动和资产配置情况发布的周报，截至本周三的一周内，现金等价物基金因税收原因流出 1600 亿美元，而美股则遭遇了第二周的资金外流。【原文：Cash equivalent funds saw a $160 billion tax-related outflow in the week to Wednesday, according to a Bank of America's weekly report that cites fund flows and asset allocation from data provider EPFR, while U.S. stocks suffered their second week of outflows.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/global-markets-flows-bofa-update-1-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">22DP6NKTGNLQHMN3Y2SZW4WFCM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 09:48:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局称，特斯拉将因油门踏板故障召回 3878 辆 Cybertrucks]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国国家公路交通安全管理局（NHTSA）周五表示，特斯拉将召回3878辆Cybertrucks，以修复一个可能松动并卡在内饰中的油门踏板垫。【原文：Tesla is recalling 3,878 Cybertrucks to fix an accelerator pedal pad that could come loose and become lodged in the interior trim, the U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA) said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/tesla-recall-3878-cybertrucks-nhtsa-says-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7TISIWYNVJMKFKDQRIFIBEZIUU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 09:34:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[派拉蒙因索尼影业和阿波罗影业讨论联合收购的报道一跃而起]]></title><description><![CDATA[据路透社报道，索尼影视娱乐公司（Sony Pictures Entertainment）和阿波罗全球管理公司（Apollo Global Management）正在讨论联合竞购派拉蒙全球传媒公司（Paramount Global）的事宜，该公司股价在周五的盘前交易中上涨了 9% 以上。【原文：Shares of Paramount Global rose more than 9% in premarket trade on Friday, after Reuters reported Sony Pictures Entertainment and Apollo Global Management were discussing a joint bid to acquire the media company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/paramount-jumps-report-sony-pictures-apollo-discussing-joint-buyout-bid-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">VA3Z6EWKFFM3HA4NAJ3F4NZZSY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 09:29:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Netflix 停止统计用户数量，第二季度营收预期不乐观，业绩下滑]]></title><description><![CDATA[Netflix 的股价在周五的盘前交易中最多下跌 6.22%，至 572.58 美元，此前该公司出人意料地表示将不再提供用户数量，同时其第二季度营收预期也低于华尔街预期。【原文：Netflix's shares fell as much as 6.22% to $572.58 in premarket trading on Friday after the company unexpectedly said it would no longer provide subscriber counts, while its second-quarter revenue forecast fell short of Wall Street expectations.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/netflix-slips-after-stopping-subscriber-tally-report-downbeat-q2-revenue-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">HFIETNLPDBORHAHWEVJZ5BCV7M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 09:25:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[汉莎航空就收购 ITA 股份一事寻求说服欧盟监管机构]]></title><description><![CDATA[汉莎航空公司高管和律师将于周五在布鲁塞尔出席为期一天的听证会，试图说服欧盟反垄断监管机构批准该公司收购意大利竞争对手 ITA 航空公司的少数股权。【原文：Lufthansa executives and lawyers will attend a day-long hearing in Brussels on Friday to try to convince EU antitrust regulators to clear the company's bid for a minority stake in Italian rival ITA Airways.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/lufthansa-seeks-persuade-eu-regulators-over-ita-stake-buy-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">K54G4PBM5NKTPPZKAETUWHD3DI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 08:36:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[受降息和中东忧虑影响，华尔街 "恐惧指数 "创逾五个月新高]]></title><description><![CDATA[受美国降息预期大幅回落和地缘政治紧张局势升级的影响，华尔街的 "恐惧指数 "周五创下五个多月来的最高值。【原文：Wall Street's "fear gauge" hit its highest in more than five months on Friday due to a sharp pullback in interest U.S. rate cut expectations and escalating geopolitical tensions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-streets-fear-gauge-over-5-month-high-rate-cut-mideast-worries-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">NXKVYUEDGBLOHOHS36ANNWVWGU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 08:29:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧莱雅第一季度销售超预期，股价大涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国化妆品巨头欧莱雅周四晚间公布第一季度销售额同比增长 9.4%，超过预期的 6.1%，欧莱雅股价在周五早盘交易中上涨超过 4%。【原文：Shares in L'Oreal rose more than 4% % in early Friday trading after the French cosmetics giant reported a 9.4% rise in first quarter sales on a like-for-like basis on Thursday evening, beating expectations of 6.1% growth.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/loreal-shares-shine-after-q1-sales-beat-expectations-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">DK7F5MH44NLLXOU575I3QBWRMU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 07:15:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[挪威财富基金支持分拆高盛首席执行官和董事长职位的股东提案]]></title><description><![CDATA[挪威 1.6 万亿美元的主权财富基金是全球最大的投资者之一，该基金周五表示，将再次投票支持一项要求分拆高盛首席执行官和董事会主席职务的决议。【原文：Norway's $1.6 trillion sovereign wealth fund, one of the world's largest investors, said on Friday it would again vote in favour of a resolution calling for a split of the CEO and board chair roles at Goldman Sachs .】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/norway-wealth-fund-backs-shareholder-proposal-split-goldman-ceo-chair-roles-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">V4GCVXCRTVNULB5SRD72DSOV7Y</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 07:12:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Take Five：与美元共舞]]></title><description><![CDATA[就在降息似乎随时都会到来的时候，通货膨胀又抬头了，美元的强势迫使其他央行行长保护本国货币，重新考虑他们的政策选择。【原文：Just when it looked like rate cuts were coming any minute now, inflation has reared its head and the strength of the dollar is forcing other central bankers to protect their currencies and reconsider their policy choices.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/take-five/global-markets-themes-graphic-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JZ4IN5JEG5PB5AT5MGHE4VYMAE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 07:07:39 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>