<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是一个追踪Reuters-Businessnews的种子]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><atom:link href="https://www.reuters.com/business" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><generator>新世界</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 18:46:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://i.postimg.cc/gL4c5Jnz/reutersbiz.jpg</url><link>https://www.reuters.com/business</link><title><![CDATA[Reuters-Business]]></title></image><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 18:46:58 GMT</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[政治热潮促使日韩联手应对弱势货币]]></title><description><![CDATA[日本和韩国本周成功地在与美国的联合声明中加入了对本国货币表示担忧的措辞，这凸显了它们因汇率疲软而加剧的严重通货膨胀所面临的政治压力。【原文：The success of Japan and South Korea at inserting language voicing concern over their currencies in a joint statement with the U.S. this week underscores the political heat they face from stiff inflation that is being aggravated by weak exchange rates.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/political-heat-prods-japan-south-korea-team-up-weak-currencies-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JJZ5KMGWONKMLADTGAL2VJDPAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 18:21:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[亚马逊广告主管离职履新]]></title><description><![CDATA[亚马逊公司的广告主管科琳-奥布里（Colleen Aubrey）已担任该职务近三年，她将调任该公司一个未公开的新职位。【原文：Amazon.com's advertising chief Colleen Aubrey, who has held that role for nearly three years, is moving to a new undisclosed position at the company.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/amazon-advertising-chief-steps-aside-new-role-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OMPCQHOB3NPXXBYWOJWA3QOCHI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 18:13:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[首席执行官：稳定币 Tether 作为新兴市场的美元替代品受到提振]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tether 首席执行官保罗-阿尔多诺（Paolo Ardoino）周五告诉路透社，稳定币 Tether 近期的增长主要是受其在新兴市场作为美元替代品的使用所推动，而不是受加密货币交易需求的推动。【原文：Stablecoin Tether's recent growth is being driven by its use as an alternative to the U.S. dollar in emerging markets, rather than by demand for cryptocurrency trading, Tether CEO Paolo Ardoino told Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/stablecoin-tether-gets-boost-dollar-alternative-emerging-markets-ceo-says-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4DKWIPU6KBLTNIIBFJDAMIPMYY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 18:04:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街日报》报道：美国监管机构酝酿限制华尔街高管奖金]]></title><description><![CDATA[据《华尔街日报》周五报道，美国银行业监管机构正计划重提一项提案，要求大银行推迟高管薪酬，并在亏损累累时收回更多奖金。【原文：U.S. banking regulators are planning to revive a proposal that would require big banks to defer executive compensation and claw back more of their bonuses if losses pile up, the Wall Street Journal reported on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/us-regulators-mulling-bid-limit-bonuses-wall-street-execs-wsj-reports-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KEG7PI3PO5KSBJU5O5O4XRCY6Q</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:51:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[谷歌废除针对供应商和人才派遣公司的最低工资和福利规定]]></title><description><![CDATA[Alphabet Inc.旗下的谷歌公司（Google）周五表示，将取消美国供应商和人才派遣公司向员工支付至少15美元时薪并提供医疗保险和其他福利的要求，此举可能使这家科技巨头避免与工会讨价还价。【原文：Alphabet Inc's Google on Friday said it will roll back requirements that U.S. suppliers and staffing firms pay their employees at least $15 an hour and provide health insurance and other benefits, a move that could allow the tech giant to avoid bargaining with unions.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/google-scraps-minimum-wage-benefits-rules-suppliers-staffing-firms-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">KETP2AWEYJOITCG3S5ZDTLCI3A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:47:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[拜登推动清洁能源发展，阿尔贝马勒和康明斯获得税收减免]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据美国能源部（DOE）周五公布的详细资料，Albemarle、康明斯和西门子能源等公司根据《通货膨胀削减法》（IRA）的一项条款获得了税收减免。【原文：Albemarle , Cummins and Siemens Energy are some companies that received tax credit under a section of the Inflation Reduction Act (IRA), according to details released on Friday by the U.S. Department of Energy (DOE).】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/albemarle-cummins-receive-tax-credits-under-bidens-clean-energy-drive-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">IK53CBMAYJLKDFMCQAVJDJLJKU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:34:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[韩国央行总裁关注中东紧张局势，审查外汇和经济增长前景]]></title><description><![CDATA[韩国央行行长周五表示，采取进一步政策行动稳定下滑的韩元的可能性现在取决于中东事件的发展，因为该行已准备好在必要时采取措施稳定外汇市场。【原文：South Korea's central bank chief on Friday said odds for any further policy action to stabilize the slumping Korean won now depend on how events in the Middle East unfold as the bank is ready to take steps to stabilize forex markets if needed.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/bank-korea-chief-watching-middle-east-tensions-fx-growth-outlook-reviews-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I5NDWRLTEZL6TDT7VM7RW3IQUM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:33:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美股涨势乏力，卖空者挽回损失]]></title><description><![CDATA[在过去的 30 天里，由于对美国联邦储备委员会提前降息的押注减弱，引发了股票市场的大跌，卖空者赚得盆满钵满。【原文：Short sellers have been raking it in over the last 30 days as receding bets of an early interest rate cut by the U.S. Federal Reserve triggered a selloff in the equity market.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/short-sellers-recoup-losses-rally-us-stocks-loses-steam-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">T5ZP7F7LQFLLNHB7BCX4VE6CPE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:08:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[充足的石油供应限制了中东冲突对价格的影响]]></title><description><![CDATA[据分析师和交易商称，一些最大原油等级的充足供应限制了中东冲突对基准石油期货价格的影响。【原文：Plentiful supplies of some of the biggest crude grades are limiting the impact on benchmark oil futures prices of conflict in the Middle East, according to analysts and traders.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/ample-oil-supplies-limit-impact-mideast-flare-up-prices-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3GSP7A4KPNLDLFBXEWCOAAQIVQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:58:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美股波动加剧，华尔街 "恐惧指数 "闪烁]]></title><description><![CDATA[利率焦虑和地缘政治紧张局势交织在一起，使美国股市投资者处于防御状态，并使华尔街最密切关注的波动率指数达到了半年来的最高水平。【原文：A cocktail of interest rate anxiety and geopolitical tensions is keeping U.S. stock investors defensive and driving Wall Street’s most closely watched volatility gauge to its highest level in half a year.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-street-fear-gauge-flashes-volatility-dogs-us-stocks-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">QBAJQHHPMFIANLV3MFJL6NRY54</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:54:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿尔斯通以约 6.7 亿美元出售北美常规信号业务]]></title><description><![CDATA[法国火车制造商阿尔斯通周五表示，已同意以约 6.3 亿欧元（6.71 亿美元）的价格将其北美传统铁路信号业务出售给德国铁路系统制造商克诺尔集团。【原文：French train manufacturer Alstom has agreed to sell its North American conventional rail signalling business to German rail systems manufacturer Knorr-Bremse AG for around 630 million euros ($671 million), it said on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/alstom-sells-north-american-conventional-signalling-business-around-670-mln-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6UUSF6UGN5LHVPMEYKTVCAQASI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:54:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[特朗普媒体股价上涨，因其提醒纳斯达克注意 "潜在的市场操纵行为]]></title><description><![CDATA[唐纳德-特朗普（Donald Trump）的媒体和技术公司要求纳斯达克交易所帮助防止 "裸 "卖空其股票，该公司股价周五上涨超过 3%。【原文：Shares of Donald Trump's media and technology company were up more than 3% on Friday after it asked the Nasdaq exchange to help prevent "naked" short-selling in its shares.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/trump-media-shares-gain-it-alerts-nasdaq-potential-market-manipulation-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MOJFOMQPNBLUXIOFGYLHFXAAAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:47:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，苹果开放 "即点即用 "技术的提议将于下月获得欧盟批准]]></title><description><![CDATA[熟悉内情的人士称，苹果公司在对部分条款进行调整后，向竞争对手开放其 "即点即付 "移动支付系统的提议最快将于下月获得欧盟反垄断监管机构的批准。【原文：Apple's offer to open its tap-and-go mobile payments system to rivals is set to be approved by EU antitrust regulators as soon as next month after it tweaked some of the terms, people familiar with the matter said.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/apples-offer-open-up-tap-and-go-tech-be-approved-by-eu-next-month-sources-say-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3NYPU4KC6ZORNF46NTQ6XSZ4TU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:45:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[对冲基金四月转为看跌，高盛称]]></title><description><![CDATA[高盛（Goldman Sachs）的一份报告称，全球对冲基金今年以来对股市的看跌程度最高，原因是通胀持续高企和地缘政治担忧重燃拖累股市走低。【原文：Hedge funds globally have turned the most bearish they've been on equities this year, a Goldman Sachs note said, as sticky inflation and renewed geopolitical concern have dragged stock markets lower.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/hedge-flow-hedge-funds-turn-bearish-april-goldman-says-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">U565DXU56BPCZM7Z524KXO27II</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:02:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[消息人士称，摩根士丹利消费者 IPO 银行家 Passi 即将离职]]></title><description><![CDATA[据熟悉内情的人士透露，摩根士丹利北美消费者和零售股权资本市场（ECM）主管 Tilli Dias Passi 将离开该行。【原文：Morgan Stanley's North America head of consumer and retail equity capital markets (ECM) Tilli Dias Passi will leave the bank, according to people familiar with the matter.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/morgan-stanley-consumer-ipo-banker-passi-leaving-bank-sources-say-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Z5GS2JC4GNIOJOKW2LGW5U2E5A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 14:55:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美联储主席古尔斯比称通胀进展 "停滞 "令政策搁置]]></title><description><![CDATA[芝加哥联储主席奥斯汀-古尔斯比（Austan Goolsbee）周五表示，今年在降低通胀率方面的进展 "停滞不前"，他是最新一位不再关注即将到来的降息需求的美国央行行长。【原文：Progress on bringing down inflation has "stalled" this year, Chicago Federal Reserve President Austan Goolsbee said on Friday, becoming the latest U.S. central banker to retreat from an earlier focus on the coming need for interest rate cuts.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/feds-goolsbee-says-stalled-inflation-progress-puts-policy-hold-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2XG5DR6CSVMIDEXXI7GPBD5FZU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 14:39:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[贸易紧张局势加剧，中国对进口一种美国化学品征收反倾销税]]></title><description><![CDATA[中国周五对从美国进口的一种广泛用于食品、饲料、杀虫剂和医疗领域的酸征税，与华盛顿在双边贸易问题上的紧张关系加剧。【原文：China on Friday slapped a levy on imports of an acid from the United States widely used in food, feed, pesticides and medical fields, amid heightened tensions with Washington over bilateral trade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/china-slaps-anti-dumping-levy-import-us-chemical-amid-rising-trade-tensions-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6GD4GJBWGJLPNEXVWG5TWZDIJE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 13:39:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国债务前景恶化更多体现在黄金和比特币上而非债券上]]></title><description><![CDATA[市场观察人士表示，对美国政府债务快速上升的担忧是近期金价和比特币飙升的部分原因，尽管迄今为止国债市场对美国的财政之路仍相对乐观。【原文：Concern about the rapidly rising U.S. government debt is partly behind recent surges in gold prices and bitcoin, even as the Treasury market so far remains relatively sanguine about the country's fiscal path, market observers say.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/worsening-us-debt-outlook-seen-more-gold-bitcoin-than-bonds-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4OEUCAS4TRIV5MWZO22KQG255U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 13:35:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[伊朗扣押船只后，航运业敦促联合国保护船只]]></title><description><![CDATA[随着中东地区袭击事件的升级，商船和海员在海上面临的危险与日俱增，联合国必须采取更多措施保护供应链。【原文：Merchant ships and seafarers are increasingly in peril at sea as attacks escalate in the Middle East and the United Nations must do more to protect supply chains, the industry said in a letter released on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/shipping-industry-urges-un-protect-vessels-after-iran-seizure-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">XBEQCHZFSNN3XMND7U6UYYZKZI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 13:13:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[投资者为长期高利率做好准备，美国股票基金资金大幅流出]]></title><description><![CDATA[截至 4 月 17 日的七天内，美国股票基金遭遇了大幅资金外流，原因是投资者预计在美国经济复苏的同时，通胀顽固，利率将长期受到限制。【原文：U.S. equity funds suffered sharp outflows in the seven days to April 17 as investors anticipated prolonged restrictive interest rates amid stubborn inflation in a resilient U.S. economy.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-equity-funds-see-sharp-outflows-investors-brace-extended-high-rates-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">I2RX73PMVBLUVATLPDVCCJD5U4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 13:03:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华纳兄弟首席执行官 2023 年薪酬增长近 27]]></title><description><![CDATA[华纳兄弟 Discovery 首席执行官大卫-扎斯拉夫（David Zaslav）周五向美国证券交易委员会（SEC）提交的一份文件显示，2023 年，他的年薪将增长近 27%，达到 4,970 万美元。【原文：Warner Bros Discovery CEO David Zaslav's annual compensation rose nearly 27% to $49.7 million in 2023, a filing with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) showed on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/warner-bros-ceo-pay-rose-nearly-27-2023-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MLRRWXTPPNJAXJNW67N4IOHT6M</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 12:48:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[中东紧张局势升级给世界市场带来新的冲击]]></title><description><![CDATA[有报道称，以色列对伊朗领土的袭击可能会将中东拖入更深的冲突，这给世界市场带来了地缘政治风险，可能会迅速改变从石油到债券等任何事物的走向，并再次引发通胀风险。【原文：Reports of an Israeli attack on Iranian soil that possibly drags the Middle East into a deeper conflict has jolted world markets with geopolitical risks that can swiftly change the direction of anything from oil to bonds and renew inflation risks.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-middle-east-graphic-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">27QYUJFLZFLEZDB2AIUYSF2WLI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 11:59:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Archer Aviation 计划明年在印度开始电动空中出租车试验]]></title><description><![CDATA[Archer Aviation 公司首席执行官周五告诉路透社，该公司得到了 Stellantis 和波音公司的支持，目标是明年在印度开始试验其电动空中出租车，计划于 2026 年投入商业运营。【原文：Archer Aviation , backed by Stellantis and Boeing , aims to begin trials of its electric air taxi in India next year, ahead of a planned commercial launch in 2026, the company's chief executive told Reuters on Friday.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/archer-aviation-aims-start-electric-air-taxi-trials-india-next-year-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">UJD3MITMA5PRFOGKIJC5QTTXQ4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 11:52:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[降息希望破灭，全球股票基金资金外流激增]]></title><description><![CDATA[由于市场猜测美国联邦储备委员会将推迟降息，投资者情绪受挫，截至 4 月 17 日的七天内，全球股票基金的资金流出量大幅增加。【原文：Global equity funds saw a jump in outflows in the seven days through April 17 as speculation the U.S. Federal Reserve will delay cutting interest rates dampened investor sentiment.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/global-markets-flows-graphic-pix-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">JYP62X2EERNE3OEUN2XTKBQXQY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 11:49:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[利息收入减少导致第五季公司利润下降]]></title><description><![CDATA[Fifth Third Bancorp 周五公布的第一季度利润下降了 10%，原因是存款成本上升拖累了该银行的利息收入。【原文：Fifth Third Bancorp posted a 10% drop in first-quarter profit on Friday as higher deposit costs weighed on the lender's interest income.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/fifth-third-bancorps-quarterly-profit-falls-lower-interest-income-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MVKY4R5MLJJIPLPDCNGKOKEEZI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 11:41:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国运通利润超出预期，富裕客户消费强劲]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，美国运通的第一季度利润超过了华尔街的预期，其主要原因是随着经济衰退的担忧减弱，富裕客户群增加了消费。【原文：American Express's first-quarter profit vaulted past Wall Street estimates on Friday, driven by an affluent customer base that increased spending as recession fears receded.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/american-express-beats-profit-estimates-strong-spending-by-wealthy-customers-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MSFFWPTFFFOELAEGQG3SYGYHPQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 11:12:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[宝洁上调年度核心利润预期，原因是需求回升和价格上涨]]></title><description><![CDATA[宝洁公司周五上调了年度核心利润预期，原因是美国和欧洲市场对其清洁和家用产品的价格上涨和需求回升。【原文：Procter &amp; Gamble raised its annual core profit forecast on Friday on price increases and resilient demand for its cleaning and household products in the United States and Europe.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/pg-raises-annual-core-profit-forecast-resilient-demand-price-hikes-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2VT7CXJ54FLZZHSGT4CL5ONP6I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 11:04:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[油田公司SLB利润因国际钻井需求而增长]]></title><description><![CDATA[周五，顶级油田服务公司 SLB 公布第一季度利润增长 14%，符合分析师的预期，原因是中东和非洲强劲的油气钻探需求帮助抵消了北美活动的疲软。【原文：Top oilfield services firm SLB reported a 14% rise in first-quarter profit on Friday, in line with analysts' estimates, as strong oil and gas drilling demand in the Middle East and Africa helped offset weakness in North American activity.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/commodities/oilfield-firm-slbs-profit-rises-international-drilling-demand-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6K2HZG5CJBKLPGT27S5Y3MW4EQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 10:58:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[华尔街一周前瞻 美股 "拥挤 "的大盘交易等待财报考验]]></title><description><![CDATA[下周，市场上最大的几家科技和成长型公司将公布财报，这将是对美股涨势的一次重要考验。【原文：Next week’s earnings reports from some of the market’s biggest technology and growth companies could prove an important test for the U.S. stock rally, which has flagged as expectations for interest cuts fade.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/wall-st-week-ahead-crowded-megacap-trade-us-stocks-awaits-earnings-test-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">BR42Y6NC6VIXFKB4CCMMT7DIQU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 10:12:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[电动汽车增长放缓，通用汽车和福特寄希望于燃油卡车]]></title><description><![CDATA[美国汽车制造商通用汽车和福特汽车在下周公布第一季度业绩时面临着一个共同的挑战：在电动汽车增长放缓的情况下，如何向投资者解释未来几个月利润增长的来源。【原文：U.S. automakers General Motors and Ford face a challenge in common when they report first-quarter results next week: Explaining to investors where profit growth will come from in the months ahead as EV growth slows.】]]></description><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/gm-ford-count-gas-powered-trucks-ev-growth-slows-2024-04-19/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OD4I7ZD5GNIQXKIJC3A3APVMCM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 10:06:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>